[Script Info]
Title:Mayochiki BD 07 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: opjp,DFPMaruGothic-SB,17,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正粗圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,8,1
Style: edcn,华康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.26,0:01:23.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.11,0:01:26.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.07,0:01:31.70,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}抱きしめて翔べ　遙か遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.57,0:01:49.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ゲームセットなんてない日々　イメージして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.69,0:01:55.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}叶えたい未来　数えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.05,0:02:01.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}打ち明け合ったら約束　あきらめない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.13,0:02:06.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夢を形にするまで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.08,0:02:11.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}好きなこと　全力で追いかけようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.72,0:02:14.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一緒に…ね!?　楽しくね!!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.38,0:02:19.25,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}希望の羽広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.26,0:02:23.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.13,0:02:26.03,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.12,0:02:30.65,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.74,0:02:31.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.72,0:02:34.46,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}未知数のドアだって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.50,0:02:37.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怖がらず開けてね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.21,0:02:39.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.76,0:02:45.33,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}舞い上がれ　彼方へと
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.26,0:01:23.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.11,0:01:26.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.07,0:01:31.70,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怀着这份心情 飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.57,0:01:49.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想像着没有尽头的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.69,0:01:55.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}细数着想要实现的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.05,0:02:01.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}说出心里话的我们约定 不要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.13,0:02:06.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}直到将梦想变成现实
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.08,0:02:11.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}喜欢的东西 就要全力追寻
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.72,0:02:14.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一起来吧 很开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.38,0:02:19.25,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}张开希望的羽翼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.26,0:02:23.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.13,0:02:26.03,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.12,0:02:30.65,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}带着勇气启程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.74,0:02:31.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.72,0:02:34.46,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}就算是未知数的门
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.50,0:02:37.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}也能毫不畏惧地打开
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.21,0:02:39.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.76,0:02:45.33,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飞扬空中 直至彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}声に出して　楽しいって言っちゃったら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雲一つ無い青空　この胸に広がってくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハートシグナル　キュンと立てて　飛び込んだ世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はみ出しちゃえ!　私と言うキャパシティ拡張　楽しいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}止まらないスピードになって恋してたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}急ごっ!　二人だけの時空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3　飛び越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に逢いたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}突き抜ける風になって届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうちょっと　可愛くアプローチ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハート型の未来になって
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君にご奉仕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そばにいたいから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只要将快乐说出声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}万里无云的蓝天 就会在这心中展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在突然闯入的世界 怦然心跳地发射心灵的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}冲破界线 我将快乐的容量扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想以无法停止的速度恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧 只属于两人的时空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3 越过阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想与你相见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想化作穿透一切的风向你传递
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}略带可爱地接近
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变成心形的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为您效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因为想在你身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.81,0:00:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.29,0:00:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.80,0:00:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.41,0:00:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.04,0:00:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.48,0:00:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.86,0:00:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.10,0:00:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我有话想对你说
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.85,0:00:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.85,0:00:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.21,0:00:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起私奔吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.37,0:00:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？私奔…？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.43,0:00:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然说这种话 我知道你会不明所以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.62,0:00:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.97,0:00:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要次郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.34,0:00:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦…？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.75,0:00:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 只会有点犯困而已
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.17,0:00:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.35,0:01:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.82,0:01:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管家不能违抗主人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.25,0:01:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.24,0:01:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是错觉吗 次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.35,0:01:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得有股土豆炖肉的味道…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.71,0:01:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 像是女生的味道…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.66,0:02:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私奔吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.24,0:03:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.46,0:03:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.46,0:03:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.79,0:03:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太糟了！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.77,0:03:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜某人所赐 我被灌了奇怪的东西啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.09,0:03:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我也不想采取那种强硬手段的…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.55,0:03:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.81,0:03:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.63,0:03:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也说的有些过了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.36,0:03:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果就那样一睡不醒的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.36,0:03:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我实在很担心该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.62,0:03:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.89,0:03:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是7点钟的新闻…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.38,0:03:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上7点？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.49,0:03:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇到近卫的时候应该刚过中午…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.99,0:03:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实药好像有点太管用了 嘻嘻
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.99,0:03:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}（注：「てへぺろ(?ω<)」是声优日笠阳子最先使用的\N因为天然而做错了事情时候使用的用语 曾获得2009年的声优流行语大奖）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.02,0:03:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.87,0:03:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.63,0:03:49.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 凉月同学
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.20,0:03:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里到底是哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.31,0:03:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你切换得这么快真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.69,0:03:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是某处海边的温泉旅馆哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.61,0:04:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温泉旅馆？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.92,0:04:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.88,0:04:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和我家很有渊源的豪华旅馆
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.51,0:04:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且奢侈的是 还被我们包下了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.73,0:04:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 吃惊了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.05,0:04:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 与其说是吃惊…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.93,0:04:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要来这种地方？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.92,0:04:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微发生了些事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.88,0:04:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.86,0:04:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离家出走了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.29,0:04:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.46,0:04:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父母竟然说暑假要去国外旅行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.02,0:04:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无视我的意见
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.56,0:04:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.00,0:04:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不认为这样擅自决定很过分吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.82,0:04:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是仅有一次的高二暑假啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.48,0:04:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不也擅自决定了我的计划吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.19,0:04:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我觉得这也是个好机会
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.92,0:04:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在为了治疗次郎同学的女性恐惧症 开始集训
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.73,0:04:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.72,0:04:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经准备得很充分了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.44,0:04:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经拜托红羽妹妹把换洗衣物准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.15,0:05:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是为了我们的旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.35,0:05:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还真是辛苦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.32,0:05:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说我想换衣服了 能请你回自己房间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.57,0:05:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢 这里是我们的房间哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.24,0:05:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.26,0:05:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 次郎同学 想知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.70,0:05:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什 什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.22,0:05:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们同住一间房的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.91,0:05:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和旅行的名义有关
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.41,0:05:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名义？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.36,0:05:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私～奔～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.02,0:05:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没听昴说过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.68,0:05:35.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是私奔到这间旅馆的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.66,0:05:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.04,0:05:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早饭准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.67,0:05:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 昴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.41,0:05:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天要去海边 得好好补充营养才行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.29,0:05:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.53,0:05:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.90,0:05:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才和大小姐 是想要…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.54,0:06:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ki ki kiss吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.79,0:06:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静点 这怎么可能！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.86,0:06:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 你们的脸靠得这么近！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.74,0:06:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是凉月在捉弄我而已！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.41,0:06:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 怎么可能那么随便就kiss呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.56,0:06:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.15,0:06:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我们也去吃早饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.94,0:06:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.65,0:06:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 坂町大人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.13,0:06:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次能光临本旅馆 真是非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.30,0:06:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.42,0:06:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说还真是不得了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.35,0:06:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奏大人和坂町大人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.13,0:06:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.15,0:06:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然互许终身 却因为周围人的反对而私奔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.95,0:06:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.75,0:06:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过请放心 我们支持两位
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.59,0:07:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.80,0:07:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么这次旅行是私奔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.02,0:07:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 没听大小姐提过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.87,0:07:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我只听说她和父母吵架 离家出走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.51,0:07:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.86,0:07:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.93,0:07:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也好 凉月也好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.02,0:07:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整天把别人玩弄于股掌之中还完全不作说明
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.72,0:07:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎不也有事瞒着我吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.44,0:07:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？你说的是什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.33,0:07:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.85,0:07:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.53,0:07:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.65,0:07:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只说是离家出走的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.34,0:07:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定会被打小报告 带我回家不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.16,0:07:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算这么说…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.87,0:07:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.96,0:07:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想说怎么这么慢呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.01,0:08:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 别害羞了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.43,0:08:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次 次郎 怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.35,0:08:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐为我选的泳衣…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.47,0:08:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我觉得不错哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.65,0:08:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.08,0:08:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.66,0:08:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们去游泳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.67,0:08:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这之前…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.23,0:08:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万众期待的治疗程序开始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.93,0:08:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮我涂防晒油吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.58,0:08:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.11,0:08:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快 而且 好强
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.90,0:08:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 已经…怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.14,0:08:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明只是手指～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.27,0:08:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是故意的吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.10,0:08:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经结束了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.74,0:08:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「猜在背上写了什么字」的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.17,0:08:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 结束了！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.00,0:09:01.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 如果现在流鼻血的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.69,0:09:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的人生就完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.24,0:09:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.81,0:09:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的背上写了不少下流的话呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.57,0:09:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「不要 次郎同学 不要～」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.47,0:09:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.48,0:09:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁写了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.76,0:09:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敲西瓜和堆沙子…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.46,0:09:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能体验的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.09,0:09:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎更喜欢哪样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.76,0:09:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敲西瓜和…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.67,0:09:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堆沙子…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.90,0:09:39.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…还是都免了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.99,0:09:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去买点饮料！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.16,0:09:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐 那件事还没告诉次郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.98,0:09:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是我们两个之间的秘密哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.41,0:09:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生意还真好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.48,0:10:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的吗 听说店员都穿的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.06,0:10:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 而且好像水准相当高哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.76,0:10:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还真是狡猾的买卖
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.47,0:10:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.06,0:10:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀 这要洗一下才行了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.39,0:10:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.56,0:10:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 您…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.55,0:10:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有着一副很适合戴眼镜的好身材呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.85,0:10:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要带上眼镜就能身体健康
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.19,0:10:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体重减轻 身高也会增长
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.26,0:10:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肌肉发达的你会coming here
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.52,0:10:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.15,0:10:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是守望会的…！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.83,0:10:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 你也来戴上眼镜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.44,0:10:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊 奈香流！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.55,0:10:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋胆小鬼？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.00,0:10:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.46,0:10:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 哥哥？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.81,0:10:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈～？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.02,0:11:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开炒了哦 笨蛋！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.06,0:11:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是流
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.50,0:11:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「嘻嘻」是啥意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.65,0:11:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵～谢谢你请客 坂町前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.12,0:11:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不打工了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.48,0:11:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法啊 从早上起就什么也没吃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.86,0:11:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不是去集训了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.24,0:11:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 那是因为啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.62,0:11:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们本来正游泳前往集训地的无人岛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.37,0:11:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(658,75,-34,75)}{\fs20\1c9F60E7\bord0\shad0}前辈们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.11,0:11:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,途中和大家游散了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.98,0:11:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就来到了这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.52,0:11:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(159,100,85,176)}{\fs20\1c9F60E7\bord0\shad0}前辈们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.47,0:11:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(85,176,0,265)}{\fs20\1c9F60E7\bord0\shad0}前辈们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.89,0:11:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为行李都是由部长管理的 我们身无分文
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.03,0:11:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥能在这里真是帮大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.34,0:11:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和姐姐大人她们的旅行 就是在这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.42,0:11:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有姐姐来着？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.70,0:12:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.76,0:12:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人就是哥哥的同班同学凉月前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.81,0:12:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.44,0:12:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你会和那个凉月奏一起旅行？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.29,0:12:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不 那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.32,0:12:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.93,0:12:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是昴大人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.52,0:12:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.89,0:12:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么怎么了 去买个饮料也太久了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.74,0:12:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个 因为发生了很多事…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.64,0:12:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 我们马上就过去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.76,0:12:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要来！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.33,0:12:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.42,0:12:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之不能来！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.43,0:12:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使你这样说…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.25,0:12:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.92,0:12:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.02,0:12:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去接她们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.47,0:12:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫 现在立刻把这个戴上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.66,0:12:55.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是指 这副眼镜吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.96,0:12:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 这也是为了你自己 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.89,0:13:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也倒是没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.47,0:13:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 次郎喜欢这一类的吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.06,0:13:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 够了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.65,0:13:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 你在干什么呢 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.12,0:13:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然就从店里跑出来…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.31,0:13:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.12,0:13:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近…近卫前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.92,0:13:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为 为 为什么这副打扮
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.21,0:13:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊 红羽妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.35,0:13:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子怎么看都是女生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.37,0:13:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.23,0:13:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是昴的表妹
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.17,0:13:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住在这附近的昴的母亲的娘家
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.95,0:13:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴过会儿应该也会过来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.22,0:13:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫前辈要来…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.90,0:13:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新介绍一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.79,0:13:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴的表妹 叫做小鸟游普纽露
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.18,0:13:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.91,0:13:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 很前卫很可爱的名字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.95,0:13:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不管怎么说都太牵强了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.53,0:13:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 普纽露小姐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.53,0:13:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个可爱的名字啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.82,0:13:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还真信了…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.62,0:14:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽妹妹 普纽露和你一样 也是高中一年级
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.64,0:14:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用在名字后面加上「小姐」也行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.70,0:14:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺带一提 这个孩子这样亲切地称呼我的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.29,0:14:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「奏姐姐」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.10,0:14:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了普纽露 像平时一样叫「奏姐姐」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.60,0:14:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奏…奏…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.02,0:14:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奏姐姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.47,0:14:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说不定发掘出了一个很可怕的怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.14,0:14:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀 那副眼镜是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.40,0:14:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她自己的掉在海里了 所以借用一下你的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.77,0:14:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.68,0:14:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那孩子是个美女
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.25,0:14:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为它找主人我费了不少工夫呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.49,0:14:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还真是挺让小奈流中意的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.49,0:14:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}（注：原话为お眼鏡に適った 直译为适合眼镜的人 这里是一语双关的冷笑话）
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.12,0:15:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 红羽妹妹真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.00,0:15:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好笑～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.63,0:15:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋胆小鬼 为什么要说这种谎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.96,0:15:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 那是因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.94,0:15:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微 有点受打击了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.08,0:15:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.74,0:15:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不打算对别人的兴趣说三道四
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.42,0:15:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没想到居然昴大人的女装癖那么严重
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.76,0:15:26.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太幸运了 往好的方向误会了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.13,0:15:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 很厉害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.98,0:15:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说 和女生没什么区别
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.76,0:15:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 非常可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.71,0:15:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还对近卫…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.64,0:15:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 那件事我已经放弃了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.74,0:15:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在一起还是会紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.67,0:15:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 偷听别人说话不是个好爱好啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.61,0:15:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午安 宇佐美同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.64,0:15:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然在这里巧遇
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.17,0:15:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么和笨蛋胆小鬼一起旅行啊 凉月奏
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.10,0:16:03.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和次郎同学是朋友 旅行什么的很平常吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.36,0:16:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不平常
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.66,0:16:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真没办法 我就把真相告诉你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.07,0:16:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.80,0:16:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我的未婚夫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.16,0:16:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怎么可能啊 你突然乱说些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.65,0:16:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是骗人的哦 我和他正在私奔的途中
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.85,0:16:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私奔！？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.30,0:16:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺带一提 旅馆的房间也是同一间哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.29,0:16:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同一间房间…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.46,0:16:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.27,0:16:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 昨天晚上也是睡在一起的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.46,0:16:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.36,0:16:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.49,0:16:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人？你是说我在骗你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.48,0:16:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月奏 我对你是一点点也不会相信的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.47,0:16:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我很早开始就这么认为
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.01,0:16:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「你说的话全是撒谎」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.11,0:16:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的胡扯对我是行不通的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.65,0:16:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我不太擅长对付你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.55,0:17:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 刚才全部都是在胡扯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.58,0:17:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有自信吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.44,0:17:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.96,0:17:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你比起来 相信笨蛋胆小鬼…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.33,0:17:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信朋友不是理所当然的吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.71,0:17:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政宗…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.06,0:17:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 因为我们是关系很好的朋友！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.99,0:17:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也请笨蛋胆小鬼吃过土豆炖肉 就在我家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.81,0:17:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 让人在意的发言
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.15,0:17:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.10,0:17:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅如此
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.23,0:17:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最早看到这件泳衣的也是笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.46,0:17:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后的肌肤之亲…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.72,0:17:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 别说让人误会的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.86,0:17:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我换个说法
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.33,0:17:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 互相摩擦…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.33,0:17:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得更容易误会了！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.91,0:17:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土豆炖肉和女生的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.29,0:17:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.78,0:17:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.22,0:18:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇佐美同学
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.65,0:18:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干 干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.25,0:18:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今晚要住在哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.85,0:18:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.49,0:18:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然在和宇佐美交往吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.19,0:18:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.76,0:18:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 我没生气
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.21,0:18:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.05,0:18:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而作为朋友应该祝福吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.37,0:18:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要管我了 快点到你女朋友那里去…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.73,0:18:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在误会些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.71,0:18:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 次郎在宇佐美的家里…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.82,0:18:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在不想提这事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.12,0:18:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是去了那家伙的家里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.51,0:18:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为约好要请我吃亲手做的菜
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.91,0:18:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美味
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.99,0:18:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.25,0:18:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就多多赞扬我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.49,0:18:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很美味
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.92,0:18:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调味恰好 肉和洋葱也柔软到仿佛会在舌头上融化
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.99,0:18:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最重要的是很好地突出了粉条的触感
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.60,0:18:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那想必很美味吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.85,0:19:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有点意外啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.65,0:19:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是好事也就到此为止了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.65,0:19:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 太美味了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.27,0:19:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 差不多该…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.20,0:19:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开 开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.86,0:19:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.89,0:19:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…在做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.13,0:19:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要移开视线
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.06,0:19:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 你上当了笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.86,0:19:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可惜我里面穿的是泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.65,0:19:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 治疗开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.98,0:19:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就努力忍住吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.72,0:19:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.44,0:19:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛苦 太痛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.62,0:19:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 不要乱动 笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.20,0:19:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙了 鼻血出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.67,0:19:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 在回来的路上就被你灌了药…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.74,0:20:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太不知廉耻了次郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.33,0:20:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才不想说的…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.38,0:20:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么和宇佐美…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.12,0:20:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么也没有
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.61,0:20:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.72,0:20:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.12,0:20:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了啾 奏大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.41,0:20:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请让我住进旅馆啾
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.82,0:20:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底在做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.24,0:20:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.28,0:20:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在想让宇佐美同学也住进旅馆里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.10,0:20:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后她就自发地用可爱的姿势…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.22,0:20:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你说让我这么做的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.27,0:20:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽妹妹你们也一起住下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.55,0:20:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人多一定很有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.64,0:20:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么什么都不让这些家伙做啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.23,0:20:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚似乎会很热闹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.27,0:20:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许无视我！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.60,0:20:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常可惜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.47,0:20:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愉快的逃避之行已经到此为止了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.45,0:21:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来接您了 奏大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.85,0:21:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你知道这个人是谁吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.87,0:21:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不认识的人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.12,0:21:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是因为不常见面忘了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.70,0:21:15.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫做近卫流
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.27,0:21:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是昴的父亲哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.80,0:21:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.37,0:21:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊 昴
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.94,0:21:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看 是父亲登场了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.84,0:21:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可怕哦 奏姐姐 不认识的人靠过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.31,0:21:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流 稍微冷静一下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.07,0:21:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普纽露很害怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.76,0:21:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普纽露？是谁啊 那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.77,0:21:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奏姐姐 这个人好恶心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.09,0:21:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴 别闹了 一起回家吧 帮我说服大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.49,0:21:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是昴！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.29,0:21:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 要装到什么时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.79,0:21:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请适可而止！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.05,0:21:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然的话 我就叫警察了
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.30,0:23:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能行吗…？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.25,0:23:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能行的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.48,0:23:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 会痛的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.60,0:23:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.90,0:23:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这样可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.13,0:23:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.14,0:23:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.68,0:23:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很敏感的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.65,0:23:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 放松
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.41,0:24:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎 好痛 血 好多血
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.83,0:24:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法这是献血啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.25,0:24:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集「迷茫管家与懦弱的我」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.45,0:24:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第8话 「第一次」


