[Script Info]
Title:Mayochiki BD 12 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: opjp,DFPMaruGothic-SB,17,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正粗圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,8,1
Style: edcn,华康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.26,0:01:00.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.11,0:01:03.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.07,0:01:08.70,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}抱きしめて翔べ　遙か遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.57,0:01:26.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ゲームセットなんてない日々　イメージして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.69,0:01:32.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}叶えたい未来　数えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.05,0:01:38.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}打ち明け合ったら約束　あきらめない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.13,0:01:43.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夢を形にするまで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.08,0:01:48.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}好きなこと　全力で追いかけようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.72,0:01:51.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一緒に…ね!?　楽しくね!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.38,0:01:56.25,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}希望の羽広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.26,0:02:00.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.13,0:02:03.03,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.12,0:02:07.65,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.74,0:02:08.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.72,0:02:11.46,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}未知数のドアだって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.50,0:02:14.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怖がらず開けてね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.21,0:02:16.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.76,0:02:22.33,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}舞い上がれ　彼方へと
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.26,0:01:00.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.11,0:01:03.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.07,0:01:08.70,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怀着这份心情 飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.57,0:01:26.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想像着没有尽头的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.69,0:01:32.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}细数着想要实现的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.05,0:01:38.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}说出心里话的我们约定 不要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.13,0:01:43.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}直到将梦想变成现实
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.08,0:01:48.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}喜欢的东西 就要全力追寻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.72,0:01:51.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一起来吧 很开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.38,0:01:56.25,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}张开希望的羽翼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.26,0:02:00.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.13,0:02:03.03,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.12,0:02:07.65,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}带着勇气启程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.74,0:02:08.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.72,0:02:11.46,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}就算是未知数的门
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.50,0:02:14.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}也能毫不畏惧地打开
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.21,0:02:16.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.76,0:02:22.33,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飞扬空中 直至彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}声に出して　楽しいって言っちゃったら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雲一つ無い青空　この胸に広がってくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハートシグナル　キュンと立てて　飛び込んだ世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はみ出しちゃえ!　私と言うキャパシティ拡張　楽しいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}止まらないスピードになって恋してたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}急ごっ!　二人だけの時空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3　飛び越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に逢いたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}突き抜ける風になって届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうちょっと　可愛くアプローチ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハート型の未来になって
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君にご奉仕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そばにいたいから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只要将快乐说出声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}万里无云的蓝天 就会在这心中展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在突然闯入的世界 怦然心跳地发射心灵的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}冲破界线 我将快乐的容量扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想以无法停止的速度恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧 只属于两人的时空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3 越过阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想与你相见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想化作穿透一切的风向你传递
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}略带可爱地接近
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变成心形的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为您效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因为想在你身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.54,0:00:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋胆小鬼！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.54,0:00:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么啊 笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.78,0:00:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政宗 为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.04,0:00:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月奏打来电话了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.61,0:00:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说联络不到你和昴大人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.77,0:00:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 我得过去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.08,0:00:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.25,0:00:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇～条纹…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.76,0:00:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在看什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.49,0:00:38.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.72,0:00:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫 我现在就过去
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.33,0:02:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷茫管家与懦弱的我
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.64,0:02:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛啊 笨蛋胆小鬼！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.01,0:02:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前面 看前面
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.05,0:02:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.31,0:02:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人真的在这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.01,0:02:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.97,0:02:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么会知道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.57,0:03:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我和那家伙是好友
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.26,0:03:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 好友
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.02,0:03:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.16,0:03:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.80,0:03:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好地 好好地把昴大人带回来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.16,0:03:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.10,0:03:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然…在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.93,0:03:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.84,0:03:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候的烟花 真美呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.13,0:03:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来干什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.71,0:03:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是因为担心你了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.02,0:04:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去吧 凉月也在担心你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.65,0:04:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算回去…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.72,0:04:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也已经没有我的容身之地了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.33,0:04:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没那回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.92,0:04:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直以来 当好管家对我来说意味着一切
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.82,0:04:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么身份都没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.39,0:04:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你不再是管家
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.40,0:04:24.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不也还是我的朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.86,0:04:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.32,0:04:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天不想回家
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.64,0:04:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.81,0:04:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板娘不知道昴的秘密 小心点哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.39,0:04:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.07,0:04:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过真遗憾呢 次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.83,0:04:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.05,0:04:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不是那种体质的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.73,0:04:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定就能初体验了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.38,0:04:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果发生那种事的话就宰了你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.38,0:04:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宰了你宰了你宰了你…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.08,0:04:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了吗 次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.63,0:05:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没事…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.14,0:05:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明次郎没必要一起住下的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.93,0:05:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能扔下你一个人回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.15,0:05:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.12,0:05:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请进
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.83,0:05:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 还没有用完餐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.99,0:05:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.35,0:05:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的 近卫大人 请慢用
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.70,0:05:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来坂町大人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.81,0:05:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之后和奏大小姐发展得怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.28,0:05:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不是 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.59,0:05:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要气馁 要向前看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.06,0:05:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会我来铺被子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.01,0:05:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被子…也就是说今晚要在这里二人世界！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.88,0:05:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.01,0:05:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 没什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.74,0:05:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.87,0:06:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(220,350)}我去洗澡了！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.87,0:06:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(420,350)}我去洗澡了！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.75,0:06:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说来这家伙是进男浴池的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.99,0:06:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经睡着了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.80,0:06:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能睡得着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.96,0:06:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.72,0:06:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎也睡不着吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.28,0:06:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种情况下怎么睡得着啊 一般来说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.44,0:06:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种情况…？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.83,0:06:40.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和女孩子两个人睡在同一间房
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.23,0:06:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…这种情况一般会怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.03,0:06:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.55,0:06:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定就能初体验了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.98,0:06:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡了！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.34,0:06:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.94,0:06:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想做KISS之后的事情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.51,0:07:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初体验
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.87,0:07:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初体验…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.02,0:07:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正 正常男生肯定都想啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.46,0:07:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我又是这种体质
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.25,0:07:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…要是次郎的话可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.51,0:07:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.24,0:07:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初体验
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.96,0:07:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初体验
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.24,0:07:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初体验
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.26,0:07:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初体验
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.83,0:07:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初体验
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.82,0:07:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初体验
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.03,0:07:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初体验
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.20,0:07:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初体验！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.43,0:07:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在…不会做的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.75,0:07:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要等到 怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.25,0:07:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是勉强或者一时冲动
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.12,0:07:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是打心底里希望和对方在一起的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.44,0:08:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打心底里…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.41,0:08:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.54,0:08:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样真的好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.24,0:08:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真暖和
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.99,0:08:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近 近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.21,0:08:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.20,0:08:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.64,0:08:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只 只是想和你一起睡而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.16,0:08:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那会生不如死的说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.33,0:08:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 小时候睡不着的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.29,0:08:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母亲也是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.34,0:08:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.55,0:09:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天会回去的 也不想再给次郎添麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.04,0:09:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 已经做不回管家了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.86,0:09:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.04,0:09:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当个普通的女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.39,0:09:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是太刺激了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.41,0:09:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没对我家女儿做什么吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.46,0:09:37.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.72,0:09:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.62,0:09:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 托您的福睡得很好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.24,0:09:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 太好了呢 昴
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.92,0:09:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是太遗憾了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.28,0:09:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在期待什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.35,0:09:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐 您的伤…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.99,0:09:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有些肿 不过没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.71,0:09:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去学校吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.92,0:10:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先回趟家吧 次郎同学也送你回去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.87,0:10:09.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 真的担心死你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.95,0:10:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 真的抱歉！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.38,0:10:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过突然和近卫前辈去旅行…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.34,0:10:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.96,0:10:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是对BL觉醒了吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.28,0:10:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,颜面固！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.95,0:10:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双翅固！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.14,0:10:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,元祖巴洛！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.67,0:10:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有觉醒啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.13,0:10:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可担心你了啦 昴～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.87,0:10:34.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雨
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.03,0:10:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该说「我回来了 姐姐」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.14,0:10:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候成你妹妹了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.19,0:10:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这手感 张力 柔软度
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.01,0:10:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然最棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.67,0:10:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混水摸鱼…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.72,0:10:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雨 放开昴
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.21,0:10:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得去学校了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.13,0:10:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.28,0:10:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样真的好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.86,0:10:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.62,0:11:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.33,0:11:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.32,0:11:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴 转学了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.39,0:11:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初～体验
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.00,0:11:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还是…第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.81,0:11:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.08,0:11:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然不当管家了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.92,0:11:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有昴大人的学校…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.32,0:11:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像没有受的攻一样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.31,0:11:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.26,0:11:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫前辈 不当管家了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.19,0:11:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们坐好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.70,0:11:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天介绍转校生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.45,0:12:02.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵喵！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.22,0:12:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.64,0:12:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是转校生小鸟游普纽露
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.64,0:12:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请…请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.52,0:12:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普纽露 能再见到你太高兴了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.45,0:12:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起讨论眼镜的话题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.23,0:12:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多关照 鸣海同学 坂町同学
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.50,0:12:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 叫我红羽就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.01,0:12:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫去了哪里的学校
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.08,0:12:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.03,0:12:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛要隐瞒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.98,0:12:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.13,0:12:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.62,0:12:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.98,0:12:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普纽露她啊 转到我们的班上来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.37,0:12:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是同班同学了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.34,0:12:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请…请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.26,0:12:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普纽露 在学校也叫我奏姐姐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.67,0:12:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 奏…姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.49,0:12:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们先走了 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.53,0:12:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回头见
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.87,0:12:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回头见
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.45,0:12:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.66,0:13:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起吃午饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.77,0:13:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普…普纽露！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.45,0:13:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥居然搭讪了！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.32,0:13:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.02,0:13:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗 普纽露
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.39,0:13:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌的话推辞掉就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.35,0:13:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥从来没有受女孩子欢迎过
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.94,0:13:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你不可怜他也…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.18,0:13:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她已经答应了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.73,0:13:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.75,0:13:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 为什么昴大人会穿女装来上学
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.87,0:13:31.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 待会见 坂町前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.99,0:13:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等等 普纽露
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.35,0:13:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 这样的话早点告诉我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.03,0:13:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.90,0:13:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 次郎同学 用公主抱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.80,0:13:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.06,0:13:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的腿 下楼可是很辛苦的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.72,0:13:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.79,0:13:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 就这样交给我了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.56,0:13:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为昴不在 也只有靠你了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.45,0:14:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.63,0:14:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.21,0:14:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错呢 公主的待遇
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.89,0:14:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意外地轻 还很柔软 凉月的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.10,0:14:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部也非常…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.85,0:14:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 害你上课也迟到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.20,0:14:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.02,0:14:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 普纽露
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.74,0:14:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然眼镜娘瞄得比较准
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.97,0:14:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好期待运动会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.39,0:14:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎…嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.75,0:14:41.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.19,0:14:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎 让你久等了 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.40,0:14:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你不来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.81,0:15:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生们一直和我搭话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.92,0:15:02.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.71,0:15:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.16,0:15:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.36,0:15:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像你没什么精神
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.87,0:15:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没那回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.89,0:15:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然还是想重新当管家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.04,0:15:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想 如果可以的话 我想这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.84,0:15:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.03,0:15:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然觉得普通的女高中生也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.56,0:15:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但总觉得很寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.31,0:15:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要永远保护大小姐 永远鼓励她
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.86,0:15:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但其实是我被大小姐 被管家这份工作鼓励了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.60,0:15:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂了 交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.35,0:15:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.82,0:16:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这非比寻常的杀气…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.82,0:16:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.45,0:16:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将昴大人的初吻夺走
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.33,0:16:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然有脸来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.33,0:16:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为你不争气昴大人才转学的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.38,0:16:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.49,0:16:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得手了！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.44,0:16:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.13,0:16:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙 好强…！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.77,0:16:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的母亲是职业摔跤手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.97,0:16:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且每天早上都要被妹妹锻炼着
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.09,0:16:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是今天来这里是因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.04,0:16:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 请帮帮我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.38,0:16:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我怎么样都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.38,0:16:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是为了救近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.13,0:16:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少现在请和我联手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.19,0:17:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要和普纽露一起悠闲地聊眼镜的话题
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.16,0:17:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的话现在到我家去玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.81,0:17:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 请务必帮帮我们
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.77,0:17:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「守望会」和「S4」在…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.98,0:17:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.05,0:17:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请务必以大家的力量让近卫重新当回管家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.38,0:17:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.27,0:17:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请来签名
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.19,0:17:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也来帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.65,0:17:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政宗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.97,0:17:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让昴大人继续当管家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.72,0:17:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 我也来帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.53,0:17:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流也是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.30,0:17:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽 奈香流
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.54,0:17:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里签上名就行了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.80,0:17:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.38,0:17:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想让昴永远当我的管家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.59,0:17:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这是那个孩子的愿望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.33,0:17:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.80,0:17:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普纽露也来签名吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.79,0:17:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.26,0:17:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.62,0:18:01.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然普纽露可能不太了解昴
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.17,0:18:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫做近卫昴的学生 是被大家喜爱的 出色的管家
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.33,0:18:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.97,0:18:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.86,0:18:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.44,0:18:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收集了这么多
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.16,0:18:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由我去拿给父亲大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.91,0:18:34.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 大小…不对 奏姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.90,0:18:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐 请
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.73,0:18:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.18,0:18:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫前辈 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.53,0:18:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你复职
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.11,0:19:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.27,0:19:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想让普纽露看看昴前辈的管家装扮
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.62,0:19:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普纽露她啊 又转学了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.58,0:19:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？但是 会再见面的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.71,0:19:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见面之前再见了 普纽露
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.84,0:19:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么大家都没注意到啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.86,0:19:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个显而易见的变装
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.18,0:19:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.71,0:19:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.84,0:19:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.46,0:19:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 是你支持了昴 保护了她
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.88,0:19:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直想成为一个能够保护他人的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.90,0:19:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经足以保护你所珍惜的人了哦 次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.53,0:19:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 如果我身上发生了什么 你会保护我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.00,0:19:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.85,0:19:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也对你…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.69,0:19:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.96,0:19:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.38,0:19:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来日方长呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.04,0:20:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫…「马上过来」是什么意思…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.68,0:20:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.19,0:20:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想对次郎道谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.81,0:20:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道谢？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.05,0:20:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了次郎 我才能重新当管家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.26,0:20:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 真的很感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.60,0:20:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很高兴 你能恢复精神
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.61,0:20:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎真的很温柔呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.39,0:20:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…打扮成这样是想要道谢…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.99,0:20:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道谢的话已经说过了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.45,0:20:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.07,0:20:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能做到的事…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.97,0:21:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭上眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.18,0:21:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是好友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.84,0:21:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是身为管家的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.65,0:21:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是作为女孩子的昴
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.10,0:21:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要道谢…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.41,0:21:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.19,0:21:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌…吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.69,0:21:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能讨厌吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.78,0:21:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.07,0:21:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.56,0:21:25.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是讨厌吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.48,0:21:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能讨厌吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.48,0:21:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.56,0:21:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.82,0:21:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点KISS啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.83,0:21:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则的话 就由我来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.49,0:21:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.95,0:21:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你指使的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.73,0:21:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.72,0:21:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.97,0:21:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不快点治好你的女性恐惧症的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.38,0:21:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不能更进一步发展了吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.27,0:22:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷茫管家与懦弱至极的我的故事才刚开始
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.00,0:22:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天充满勇气的男孩与专一女孩的故事也会开始吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.70,0:23:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽妹妹 奈香流也想变得和红羽妹妹一样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.66,0:23:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.62,0:23:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 所以请揉奈香流的胸部吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.86,0:23:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一把抓住 猛烈的 用力的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.34,0:23:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.28,0:23:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.45,0:23:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.88,0:23:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 忍得住
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.36,0:23:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想变得和红羽妹妹一样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.56,0:24:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小奈流就那么喜欢我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.61,0:24:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 小小的平平的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.39,0:24:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么小还真是抱歉啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.11,0:24:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集「迷茫管家与懦弱的我」第13话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.34,0:24:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「请揉吧！」


