[Script Info]
Title:Mayochiki BD 08 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: opjp,DFPMaruGothic-SB,17,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正粗圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,8,1
Style: edcn,华康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.26,0:01:39.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.11,0:01:42.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.07,0:01:47.70,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}抱きしめて翔べ　遙か遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.57,0:02:05.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ゲームセットなんてない日々　イメージして
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.69,0:02:11.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}叶えたい未来　数えて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.05,0:02:17.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}打ち明け合ったら約束　あきらめない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.13,0:02:22.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夢を形にするまで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.08,0:02:27.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}好きなこと　全力で追いかけようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.72,0:02:30.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一緒に…ね!?　楽しくね!!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.38,0:02:35.25,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}希望の羽広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.26,0:02:39.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.13,0:02:42.03,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.12,0:02:46.65,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.74,0:02:47.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.72,0:02:50.46,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}未知数のドアだって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.50,0:02:53.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怖がらず開けてね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.21,0:02:55.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.76,0:03:01.33,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}舞い上がれ　彼方へと
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.26,0:01:39.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.11,0:01:42.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.07,0:01:47.70,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怀着这份心情 飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.57,0:02:05.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想像着没有尽头的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.69,0:02:11.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}细数着想要实现的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.05,0:02:17.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}说出心里话的我们约定 不要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.13,0:02:22.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}直到将梦想变成现实
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.08,0:02:27.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}喜欢的东西 就要全力追寻
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.72,0:02:30.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一起来吧 很开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.38,0:02:35.25,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}张开希望的羽翼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.26,0:02:39.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.13,0:02:42.03,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.12,0:02:46.65,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}带着勇气启程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.74,0:02:47.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.72,0:02:50.46,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}就算是未知数的门
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.50,0:02:53.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}也能毫不畏惧地打开
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.21,0:02:55.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.76,0:03:01.33,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飞扬空中 直至彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}声に出して　楽しいって言っちゃったら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雲一つ無い青空　この胸に広がってくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハートシグナル　キュンと立てて　飛び込んだ世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はみ出しちゃえ!　私と言うキャパシティ拡張　楽しいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}止まらないスピードになって恋してたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}急ごっ!　二人だけの時空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3　飛び越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に逢いたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}突き抜ける風になって届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうちょっと　可愛くアプローチ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハート型の未来になって
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君にご奉仕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そばにいたいから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只要将快乐说出声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}万里无云的蓝天 就会在这心中展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在突然闯入的世界 怦然心跳地发射心灵的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}冲破界线 我将快乐的容量扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想以无法停止的速度恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧 只属于两人的时空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3 越过阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想与你相见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想化作穿透一切的风向你传递
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}略带可爱地接近
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变成心形的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为您效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因为想在你身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.95,0:00:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回见 我去洗澡了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.95,0:00:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我也要去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.47,0:00:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知为何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.24,0:00:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在在温泉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.56,0:00:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.44,0:00:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.28,0:00:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这 这是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.71,0:00:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次猜谜大会的奖品
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.53,0:00:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有这张券 什么命令都能服从对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.07,0:00:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.32,0:00:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.08,0:00:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能请你朗读一下这本书吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.06,0:00:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.40,0:00:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧张 期待
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.21,0:00:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎金与巴鲁斯 爱的私奔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.84,0:00:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.90,0:00:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎金 我是第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.09,0:00:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么啊 这本少儿不宜的小说
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.68,0:00:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 这时候前辈会摘下眼镜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.56,0:01:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁斯…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.63,0:01:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎金
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.52,0:01:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.85,0:01:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.75,0:01:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼镜…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.06,0:01:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼镜 就这么戴着…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.85,0:01:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就 就可以了…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.79,0:01:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I～CAN～FLY～
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.93,0:03:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.75,0:03:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.18,0:03:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我会遇到这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.85,0:03:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.45,0:03:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么在男浴池？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.08,0:04:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.57,0:04:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这 这倒也是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.11,0:04:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我们说普纽露回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.60,0:04:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勉强瞒混过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.33,0:04:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.64,0:04:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先出去了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.64,0:04:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先出去了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.36,0:04:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先出去吧 次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.96,0:04:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.26,0:04:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲！？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.37,0:04:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎 快点来这边
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.39,0:04:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 你在啊 混账小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.38,0:04:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.29,0:05:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 你和我家女儿是什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.17,0:05:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.85,0:05:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.85,0:05:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是朋友 关系不错的同班同学
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.40,0:05:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.39,0:05:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.39,0:05:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 我也觉得昴不会有问题
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.61,0:05:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过最近感觉昴都很期待去学校
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.38,0:05:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您这么担心她啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.36,0:05:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有不担心自己孩子的父母
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.14,0:05:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更何况还是那个可爱的昴！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.49,0:05:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然看久了你的脸就火大
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.08,0:05:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没法和你呆在同一个浴池
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.66,0:05:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在大叔回去之前暂时先等会
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.46,0:05:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你为什么来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.77,0:06:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你虽然说什么私奔和治疗我的女性恐惧症的集训什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.21,0:06:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但连大叔都出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.40,0:06:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有什么理由才来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.27,0:06:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.08,0:06:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 混账小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.06,0:06:15.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 你还在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.00,0:06:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现了女式内裤
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.98,0:06:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是谁的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.01,0:06:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我有这种嗜好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.19,0:06:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊那种借口
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.64,0:06:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴的内裤也是这样子的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.39,0:06:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么会知道！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.83,0:06:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.89,0:06:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.61,0:06:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙 和昴混浴…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.52,0:06:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 冷静点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.10,0:06:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴流氓！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.33,0:07:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.93,0:07:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普纽露会来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.05,0:07:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 一定会的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.43,0:07:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 我昨晚的事想不起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.00,0:07:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我会睡在浴室来着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.99,0:07:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.92,0:07:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.62,0:07:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 普纽露真的会来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.65,0:07:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.73,0:07:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那态度是在小瞧我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.40,0:07:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.98,0:07:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是怎么回事啊 你的脖子歪成那样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.44,0:08:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是睡落枕了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.16,0:08:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.54,0:08:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微耽误了一会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.29,0:08:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了挑眼镜花了不少时间
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.86,0:08:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普纽露 好想你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.22,0:08:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人去哪了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.41,0:08:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点事拜托他做
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.34,0:08:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 发生了什么事…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.06,0:08:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.13,0:08:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.66,0:08:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…喂 放手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.00,0:09:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说凉月奏 为什么和笨蛋胆小鬼牵着手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.22,0:09:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他是我的未婚夫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.66,0:09:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是骗人的吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.42,0:09:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真没办法 告诉你真实情况好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.03,0:09:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他其实有女性恐惧症
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.56,0:09:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为 为什么你知道这个
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.10,0:09:20.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼～看来你也知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.25,0:09:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.97,0:09:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.96,0:09:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要玩射击吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.18,0:09:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇佐美同学也一起玩如何
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.52,0:09:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 求之不得
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.27,0:09:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.61,0:09:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嘞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.43,0:09:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦抱歉 把兔子打死了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.70,0:09:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是打倒了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.31,0:09:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有我不是兔子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.31,0:09:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是宇～佐～美！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.55,0:09:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你们在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.72,0:09:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人开始多了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.20,0:09:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上活动就要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.07,0:09:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活动是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.31,0:10:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浴衣选美大会和…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.30,0:10:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大逃杀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.22,0:10:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.45,0:10:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说最后还会放烟花
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.17,0:10:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真期待呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.76,0:10:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 普纽露
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.67,0:10:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 普纽露不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.00,0:10:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚还在一起的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.31,0:10:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.74,0:10:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫在哪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.26,0:10:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.38,0:10:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面开始说绕口令
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.97,0:10:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管家流记忆消除术 管家流记…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.92,0:10:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁斯 我想看到你的全部
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.25,0:10:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去 别碍事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.25,0:10:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碍事？近卫在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.32,0:10:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.57,0:10:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会没关系！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.79,0:10:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是她的朋友！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.01,0:11:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天是昴母亲的忌日
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.15,0:11:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游家的墓就在这附近
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.79,0:11:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.87,0:11:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是私奔的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.96,0:11:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结婚的时候发生了很多事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.23,0:11:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以她葬在了小鸟游家的墓地里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.45,0:11:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奏小姐如果去海外旅行的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.46,0:11:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴也必须同行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.59,0:11:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话忌日就无法来扫墓了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.53,0:11:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那凉月是为了近卫才…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.19,0:11:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.23,0:11:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.09,0:11:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想参加活动
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.07,0:11:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我去报下名
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.85,0:11:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.83,0:11:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全听到了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.24,0:11:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.25,0:11:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴说无论如何 要对你保密
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.33,0:11:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么意思啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.20,0:11:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是秘密了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.09,0:11:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.83,0:12:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是那孩子和你的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.10,0:12:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才帮你把流赶走了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.03,0:12:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.97,0:12:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎 为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.31,0:12:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说了 关于你母亲的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.27,0:12:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.87,0:12:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈一直在担心我的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.29,0:12:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担心着我有没有交到朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.14,0:12:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也和妈妈所担心的一样 一直没有朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.03,0:12:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直是一副爱理不理的样子 害怕和别人接触
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.24,0:12:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是没办法的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.18,0:12:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直都隐藏着自己是女孩子这个秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.38,0:13:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了不暴露秘密 逃避与人接触
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.67,0:13:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉次郎 请让我一个人呆会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.42,0:13:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想和次郎一起来这里…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.42,0:13:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.71,0:13:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.27,0:13:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.77,0:13:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你别管了…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.80,0:13:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎明明有女性恐惧症
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.23,0:13:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样做的话 又会失去意识的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.01,0:13:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.78,0:13:36.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了 不要再忍耐了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.93,0:13:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.05,0:13:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.32,0:13:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经…不想再让妈妈担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.62,0:13:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.55,0:13:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明已经约好不再哭泣的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.02,0:14:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想把你介绍给妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.68,0:14:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后告诉她 这是我第一次交到的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.03,0:14:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 妈妈已经不在了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.76,0:14:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和次郎来这里的话 又会让我感觉到这一点
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.42,0:14:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会哭出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.56,0:14:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不想和次郎一起来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.22,0:14:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 真是抱歉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.00,0:14:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说近卫 不介绍一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.65,0:14:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我介绍给你妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.62,0:14:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 这是坂町近次郎 次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.81,0:14:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的…我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.65,0:15:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.62,0:15:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.30,0:15:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.37,0:15:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.20,0:15:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓了我一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.80,0:15:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去接普纽露回来的路上摔倒撞到头了？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.84,0:15:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差不多也该走了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.48,0:15:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.61,0:15:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大逃杀
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.24,0:15:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要出场吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.16,0:15:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 因为优胜者能拿到奖金和沉默羔羊的大型公仔
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.14,0:15:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫也喜欢那个的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.87,0:15:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还追加浴衣选美大会优胜者的亲亲
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.63,0:15:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.44,0:15:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新介绍一次浴衣美女
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.43,0:15:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟游普纽露小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.51,0:15:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了沉默的羔羊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.92,0:15:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 怎么回事啊 那是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.23,0:15:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈 我绝对不让前辈获得优胜的！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.45,0:15:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为前辈会被普纽露亲亲
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.94,0:16:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈是天生的BL
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.78,0:16:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不允许前辈和昴大人以外的人发生那么美味的情节
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.67,0:16:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参加大逃杀的各位
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.11,0:16:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀杀杀杀 吻吻吻 杀杀…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.20,0:16:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,规则非常简单
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.99,0:16:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要沾上一滴染料就算GAME OVER
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.71,0:16:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,优胜者能得到豪华奖品和浴衣女王的吻
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.46,0:16:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 咦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.73,0:16:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么现在 游戏开始
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.99,0:16:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先是第一个
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.19,0:16:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.20,0:16:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.87,0:16:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.15,0:16:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 现在不是做这种事情的时候吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.08,0:16:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不先打倒那个家伙的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.91,0:16:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.30,0:16:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.31,0:16:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 前辈 你在这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.93,0:17:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦 那是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.31,0:17:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙 那孩子 喝碳酸饮料会醉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.10,0:17:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.21,0:17:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇佐美前辈还真是少女品味啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.49,0:17:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱衣醉拳
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.97,0:17:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱衣醉拳？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.53,0:17:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙 有醉了就脱别人的特殊癖好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.75,0:17:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇佐美前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.83,0:17:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.22,0:17:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.79,0:17:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有机可乘！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.18,0:17:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是小菜一碟
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.80,0:17:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战斗力的话可是我占上风哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.03,0:17:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对眼镜的爱能超越一切
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.32,0:17:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗 骗人…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.71,0:17:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看招看招看招
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.45,0:17:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.74,0:18:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人能胜过奈香流的挠痒攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.49,0:18:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就轮到前辈了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.87,0:18:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心 眼镜我会帮你留下的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.33,0:18:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全裸眼镜 太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.23,0:18:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能输 绝对…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.90,0:18:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要赢！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.86,0:18:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.55,0:18:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.79,0:18:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸存下来的 好像只有我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.96,0:18:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.16,0:18:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你投降我就释放人质
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.49,0:18:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人质？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.38,0:18:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样 太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.15,0:18:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子有什么罪过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.83,0:18:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀…不…不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.99,0:18:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我投降了 所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.21,0:19:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要～达尼～
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.54,0:19:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦好像有既视感…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.04,0:19:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我的眼镜
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.74,0:19:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才是替身哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.10,0:19:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想到可能会发生这种事提前准备的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.84,0:19:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 你到底做了多少准备啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.35,0:19:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.06,0:19:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.74,0:19:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是个胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.07,0:19:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却拼命想要赢得比赛的你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.04,0:19:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那么一点帅气哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.18,0:19:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.35,0:19:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能让你获胜
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.09,0:19:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年大逃杀的优胜者是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.98,0:19:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月奏小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.44,0:20:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你醒了吗 次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.65,0:20:02.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是…？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.34,0:20:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不要误会了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.96,0:20:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你怎么也不醒我才这样做的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.95,0:20:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么特别的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.05,0:20:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是要偷偷看你的睡脸哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.38,0:20:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月她们呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.61,0:20:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为次郎眼镜被弄坏的奈香流
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.82,0:20:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把周围的人的衣服全都脱了引起了大骚动
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.86,0:20:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐去交涉了 没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.75,0:20:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想会稳妥解决的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.91,0:20:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.91,0:20:30.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.65,0:20:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐给我的礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.73,0:20:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.58,0:20:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然很恐怖啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.15,0:20:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.44,0:20:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎不能理解这可爱之处吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.66,0:20:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不巧 完全不能
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.61,0:20:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好看看 让人无法忍耐的这份可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.14,0:20:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.32,0:20:53.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.38,0:20:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 住手啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.62,0:21:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一种夏天结束的感觉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.05,0:21:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还只是8月的中旬哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.57,0:21:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实如此 大概因为夏天总是一眨眼就结束
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.17,0:21:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然暑假结束了很寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.07,0:21:22.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但到了第二学期又可以与次郎和大小姐一起度过
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.68,0:21:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…非常期待
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.39,0:21:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 第二学期看来也会变得很热闹吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.79,0:21:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经习惯了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.60,0:21:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是我们的日常生活啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.65,0:21:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错吧 我们也会永远是朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.00,0:21:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.74,0:21:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再是普通朋友
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.04,0:23:43.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不行了 我…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.69,0:23:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要出来了 出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.19,0:23:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.02,0:23:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 人家已经忍不住了…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.30,0:23:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.00,0:23:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.85,0:23:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 不觉得害羞吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.99,0:23:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害羞什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.18,0:23:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请次郎同学守望着我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.43,0:24:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么羞耻PLAY啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.70,0:24:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢 我出来的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.27,0:24:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集「迷茫管家与懦弱的我」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.62,0:24:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第9话 「出门旅行一下」


