[Script Info]
Title:Mayochiki BD 09 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: opjp,DFPMaruGothic-SB,17,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正粗圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,8,1
Style: edcn,华康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.26,0:00:44.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.11,0:00:47.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.07,0:00:52.70,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}抱きしめて翔べ　遙か遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.57,0:01:10.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ゲームセットなんてない日々　イメージして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.69,0:01:16.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}叶えたい未来　数えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.05,0:01:22.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}打ち明け合ったら約束　あきらめない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.13,0:01:27.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夢を形にするまで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.08,0:01:32.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}好きなこと　全力で追いかけようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.72,0:01:35.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一緒に…ね!?　楽しくね!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.38,0:01:40.25,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}希望の羽広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.26,0:01:44.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.13,0:01:47.03,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.12,0:01:51.65,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.74,0:01:52.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.72,0:01:55.46,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}未知数のドアだって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.50,0:01:58.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怖がらず開けてね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.21,0:02:00.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.76,0:02:06.33,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}舞い上がれ　彼方へと
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.26,0:00:44.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.11,0:00:47.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.07,0:00:52.70,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怀着这份心情 飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.57,0:01:10.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想像着没有尽头的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.69,0:01:16.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}细数着想要实现的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.05,0:01:22.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}说出心里话的我们约定 不要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.13,0:01:27.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}直到将梦想变成现实
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.08,0:01:32.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}喜欢的东西 就要全力追寻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.72,0:01:35.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一起来吧 很开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.38,0:01:40.25,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}张开希望的羽翼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.26,0:01:44.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.13,0:01:47.03,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.12,0:01:51.65,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}带着勇气启程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.74,0:01:52.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.72,0:01:55.46,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}就算是未知数的门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.50,0:01:58.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}也能毫不畏惧地打开
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.21,0:02:00.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.76,0:02:06.33,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飞扬空中 直至彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}声に出して　楽しいって言っちゃったら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雲一つ無い青空　この胸に広がってくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハートシグナル　キュンと立てて　飛び込んだ世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はみ出しちゃえ!　私と言うキャパシティ拡張　楽しいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}止まらないスピードになって恋してたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}急ごっ!　二人だけの時空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3　飛び越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に逢いたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}突き抜ける風になって届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうちょっと　可愛くアプローチ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハート型の未来になって
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君にご奉仕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そばにいたいから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只要将快乐说出声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}万里无云的蓝天 就会在这心中展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在突然闯入的世界 怦然心跳地发射心灵的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}冲破界线 我将快乐的容量扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想以无法停止的速度恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧 只属于两人的时空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3 越过阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想与你相见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想化作穿透一切的风向你传递
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}略带可爱地接近
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变成心形的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为您效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因为想在你身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.46,0:00:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您回来了 主人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得更美味～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.26,0:00:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经为您施加了变得美味的魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.58,0:00:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您慢用
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.64,0:00:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你在偷什么懒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.48,0:00:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 笨蛋胆小鬼！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.50,0:02:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出门旅行一下
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.04,0:02:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快点洗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.18,0:02:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是工作
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.76,0:02:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.95,0:02:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.26,0:02:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打工的地方是这种店啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.05,0:02:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什 什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.49,0:02:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是喜欢才做的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.18,0:02:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这里薪水不错
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.24,0:02:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.20,0:02:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能穿到可爱的衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.18,0:02:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是只黑心兔子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.16,0:02:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想不到还有个这么少女情怀的理由啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.29,0:02:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 你应该感谢我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.15,0:02:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不光给你抄暑假作业
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.87,0:02:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还介绍打工的地方给你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.54,0:02:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这我是很感激啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.48,0:02:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 打电话的时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.07,0:03:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我是宇佐美…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.57,0:03:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很慌张的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.34,0:03:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在忙什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.91,0:03:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为…突然接到电话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.21,0:03:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓了一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.86,0:03:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓了一跳？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.95,0:03:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前不常有朋友打来电话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.26,0:03:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.08,0:03:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到铃声就知道是笨蛋胆小鬼的来电
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.58,0:03:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 还有我的专属铃声啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.48,0:03:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么铃声啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.41,0:03:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.47,0:03:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和你的形象比较相符的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.76,0:03:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万别是恐怖或是让人听了泄气的铃声啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.11,0:03:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要你管！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.20,0:03:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了她
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.49,0:03:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青春啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.49,0:03:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年轻真好 嗯嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.84,0:03:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.77,0:04:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长我也有点吃惊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.74,0:04:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店里流行夏季流感
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.94,0:04:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接二连三地有人请假
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.92,0:04:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慌慌张张地要找人替班的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.06,0:04:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小兔说带朋友过来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.67,0:04:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.67,0:04:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 你是她男友吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.91,0:04:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我不是她的男友…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.97,0:04:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.54,0:04:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来以为能靠这个捉弄小兔一阵子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.10,0:04:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是朋友！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.31,0:04:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样 今后也要和她好好相处哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.44,0:04:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小兔因为可爱 客人的评价都不错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.14,0:04:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是有点不亲近人 独行侠的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.36,0:04:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还担心她是不是没朋友呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.77,0:04:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你可以稍微休息会了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.59,0:04:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男友 吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.62,0:04:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再是普通朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.16,0:05:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 你刚刚说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.10,0:05:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.81,0:05:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.10,0:05:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.73,0:05:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就当什么都没听到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.07,0:05:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候近卫虽然那么说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.11,0:05:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.24,0:05:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 在这在这
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.70,0:05:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 现在快去大厅
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.57,0:05:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去帮小兔的忙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.04,0:05:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点快点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.61,0:05:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.49,0:05:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学 不是「咦」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.01,0:05:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你应该说「您回来了 大小姐」哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.17,0:05:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.75,0:05:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先坐下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.63,0:05:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚把你们两个的时间都买下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.60,0:05:43.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买下来了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.62,0:05:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嘞！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.32,0:05:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐吧坐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.70,0:05:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 所以我说大小姐什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.05,0:05:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经过这家店的时候 正好看到你和次郎同学了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.98,0:05:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想这店是非进不可了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.99,0:06:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么非进不可啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.45,0:06:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 近卫在哪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.84,0:06:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 刚刚我甩掉昴过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.98,0:06:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为想看看像被拿走了食物的仓鼠一样 慌慌张张的昴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.44,0:06:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.09,0:06:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是那么有性格啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.71,0:06:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 也没有那样啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.79,0:06:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,槽都懒的吐了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.07,0:06:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经事先发邮件给昴说要出门旅行一下了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.04,0:06:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别对近卫做太过分的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.35,0:06:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是对昴很温柔呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.10,0:06:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女仆小姐 这家店提供什么服务呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.22,0:06:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 请看一下这边的菜单…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.55,0:06:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 我为什么还得用敬语接待你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.92,0:06:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为我是客人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.64,0:06:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁要当你的女仆啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.13,0:06:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真过分啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.50,0:06:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没听你说「您回来了 大小姐」呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.98,0:06:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请回吧 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.17,0:06:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真傲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.04,0:07:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,标准的傲娇呢 小兔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.71,0:07:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这 这是店长擅自给我取的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.89,0:07:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 小兔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.20,0:07:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别叫我小兔！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.47,0:07:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 那叫小鳗鱼？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.55,0:07:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.87,0:07:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫 没事吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.13,0:07:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐 在哪…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.46,0:07:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 干嘛呢 好慢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.38,0:07:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快回去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.46,0:07:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.26,0:07:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个 等等…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.89,0:07:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.54,0:07:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您回来了 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.80,0:07:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您回来了 大小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.60,0:07:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您久等了 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.71,0:07:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 涂鸦蛋包饭的话能在上面写些什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.79,0:08:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写上love 心形也要哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.15,0:08:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.11,0:08:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不喂我吃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.87,0:08:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要求太多了！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.24,0:08:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.90,0:08:21.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 我还要追加服务里的合影
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.97,0:08:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学 能帮我们拍照吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.65,0:08:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以是可以 吓到你的话不关我事哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.28,0:08:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去驱下邪比较好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.99,0:08:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少多管闲事！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.66,0:08:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.80,0:08:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您要回去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.22,0:08:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你这么开心的样子更加不想回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.23,0:08:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快要3点了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.75,0:08:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是店里最忙的时候 快回去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.11,0:08:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 真没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.92,0:08:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您走好…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.04,0:09:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来晚了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.41,0:09:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 眼镜！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.65,0:09:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得了了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.90,0:09:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这声音是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.33,0:09:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.11,0:09:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点戴上眼镜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.29,0:09:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是你们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.99,0:09:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵喵！？ 哥哥？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.69,0:09:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么大家都在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.00,0:09:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂町 奈香流
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.29,0:09:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是来打临时工的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.71,0:09:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.43,0:09:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.42,0:09:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.98,0:09:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打工…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.62,0:09:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是巧克力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.32,0:09:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.14,0:09:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是唯夏织
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.14,0:09:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}（注：ゆいかおり 巧克力和牛奶的cv 小仓唯和石原夏织的组合）
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.63,0:09:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是宇佐美 我是政宗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.34,0:09:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是宇佐美政宗 你有意见啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.65,0:09:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连你们都来打工了啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.37,0:09:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没想到连小佐美前辈和姐姐大人都在店里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.34,0:09:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有间和这店同系列的管家咖啡厅
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.76,0:09:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是那里的常客
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.00,0:10:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后听说这里因为突然有很多人打工请假很头疼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.38,0:10:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管家咖啡厅？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.36,0:10:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您久等了 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.00,0:10:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个送去3号桌
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.76,0:10:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 给1号桌的大小姐添水
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.54,0:10:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 靠墙边的地板 积灰了麻烦清扫一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.78,0:10:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.03,0:10:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真专业呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.33,0:10:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我能走了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.93,0:10:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.76,0:10:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说我不是了！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.65,0:10:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,修理费得让你好好工作偿还才行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.68,0:10:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跑！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.53,0:10:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.83,0:10:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者 也可以用身体偿还哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.09,0:10:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.30,0:10:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 我是开玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.36,0:10:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是BL？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.40,0:10:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有空开玩笑 就快把这个送去！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.80,0:10:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级萝莉性感光线！

Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.66,0:11:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太天真了 看我奥特超级灼热飞腿！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.50,0:11:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一名！回家再练练吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.14,0:11:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完胜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.59,0:11:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际格斗的话绝对不会输的说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.39,0:11:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您真强啊大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.55,0:11:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.61,0:11:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为获胜的客人献上本店全体女仆祝贺胜利的飞吻
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.60,0:11:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.70,0:11:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.50,0:11:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人 请戴上眼镜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.87,0:11:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你快点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.26,0:11:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.07,0:11:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 排好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.37,0:11:35.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.85,0:11:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开～始
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.99,0:11:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人 祝贺您
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.11,0:11:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个恶魔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.34,0:11:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有没有什么更有趣的服务呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.23,0:11:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你还要待几个小时啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.30,0:12:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 因为红羽妹妹和奈香流都来打工了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.88,0:12:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有把大家都当成我的女仆才行不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.58,0:12:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没空陪你玩了 我去洗盘子了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.49,0:12:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种温热而柔软的触感
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.60,0:12:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.91,0:12:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.26,0:12:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.03,0:12:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经关门了 你就歇着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.43,0:12:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.69,0:12:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然就失去意识 怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.68,0:12:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 什么都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.01,0:12:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎没有发烧的样子…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.18,0:12:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…真的没事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.04,0:12:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你看上去身体不太舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.53,0:12:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是身体不舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.48,0:13:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是太兴奋了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.62,0:13:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.40,0:13:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是重度的女仆控
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.72,0:13:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.85,0:13:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实 之前到他家去玩的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.22,0:13:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他非逼我穿上女仆装
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.94,0:13:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你自己要穿的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.83,0:13:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要穿成那样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.83,0:13:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还用问 当然是为了好好侍奉他
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.49,0:13:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是女仆就不让我进家门
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.77,0:13:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 让姐姐大人打扮成女仆原来是有那么深的缘由啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.93,0:13:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道 哥哥原来是个女仆控！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.96,0:13:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.12,0:13:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥你这个色狼的百宝箱！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.27,0:13:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流去追她
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.65,0:13:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.32,0:13:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 萌是幸福的第一步
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.45,0:13:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂町也目击到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.71,0:13:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让凉月奏打扮成女仆的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.19,0:14:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇佐美
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.03,0:14:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 还把她绑在床上
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.01,0:14:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整晚用羽毛掸子挠痒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.57,0:14:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看起来像是会做这种古怪play的变态吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.62,0:14:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么在这种时候拘谨地缄口不言啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.13,0:14:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心一点 宇佐美同学
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.00,0:14:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他对女仆的 特别是吊袜带的执着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.13,0:14:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十分不寻常哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.70,0:14:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.67,0:14:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是觉得裙子只是为了压制吊袜带原本的力量的拘束具呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.30,0:14:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吊袜带居然有这种程度的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.10,0:14:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以至于不得不被名为裙子的拘束具掩藏起来的地步！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.96,0:14:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有那种力量！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.75,0:14:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.49,0:14:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我邀请你来打工的时候也是满口答应的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.30,0:14:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了这里我才知道的啊 打工的地方原来是女仆店
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.80,0:14:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也是 一边洗盘子一边用异样的眼神看着店里的女仆小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.48,0:15:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜 搞砸了…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.32,0:15:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请慢用
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.12,0:15:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用餐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.57,0:15:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 眼镜眼镜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.64,0:15:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.57,0:15:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没看！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.14,0:15:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盯…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.45,0:15:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 我刚才被这个女仆控碰到了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.06,0:15:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和他打招呼了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.15,0:15:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给他加油鼓劲了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.61,0:15:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过不是这样的！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.26,0:15:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有确认看看了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.28,0:15:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也这么认为
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.03,0:15:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底以为我的女仆控有多严重啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.30,0:15:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 要怎么确认
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.33,0:15:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心 我有办法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.41,0:15:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给他看看吊袜带就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.42,0:15:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…突然之间说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.05,0:15:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不明白吗 宇佐美同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.87,0:15:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你是如假包换 走到哪里都不会丢脸的女仆小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.73,0:16:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学如果能战胜你的诱惑力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.64,0:16:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就能证明他不是女仆控吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.57,0:16:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道理我明白
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.38,0:16:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但诱…诱…诱惑什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.75,0:16:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把裙子稍微往上翻一点 让他看到吊袜带就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.07,0:16:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.71,0:16:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然还要含着眼泪地小声说「请原谅我 主人」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.03,0:16:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么想都觉得是下流的play
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.04,0:16:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做不到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.57,0:16:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是次郎同学的朋友吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.52,0:16:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友的话这点小事应该能做得到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.44,0:16:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 难道说是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.63,0:16:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实 宇佐美同学喜欢他
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.41,0:16:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在喜欢的人面前不想做出这么害羞的事之类的？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.52,0:16:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才才…才不是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.45,0:16:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？不是喜欢而是很喜欢？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.80,0:16:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不…不是 我怎么可能喜欢上笨蛋胆小鬼啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.90,0:16:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 那么快点把裙子翻起来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.60,0:16:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要连内裤也一起让他看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.77,0:16:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他看的只是吊袜带
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.83,0:17:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要维持好这防线的极限就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.47,0:17:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.86,0:17:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.76,0:17:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的不是女仆控对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.05,0:17:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.24,0:17:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 我做
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.55,0:17:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 我是你的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.11,0:17:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.96,0:17:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请…请原谅我 主人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.24,0:17:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.86,0:17:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么一来你还敢说你不是女仆控 讨厌吊袜带吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.68,0:17:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.15,0:17:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不行了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.06,0:17:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我最喜欢女仆小姐和吊袜带了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.73,0:18:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐 我找您很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.58,0:18:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.43,0:18:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了很多事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.78,0:18:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 大小姐没事真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.42,0:18:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎也在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.87,0:18:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 偶然碰到的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.79,0:18:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 差不多该回家了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.30,0:18:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.45,0:18:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.46,0:18:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.92,0:18:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.20,0:18:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.49,0:18:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.87,0:18:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.17,0:18:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还行吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.97,0:18:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前说过的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.93,0:18:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.94,0:18:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「不要再是普通朋友」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.60,0:18:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 那不是告白哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.46,0:19:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.88,0:19:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好友…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.85,0:19:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.36,0:19:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 是好友
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.92,0:19:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的是和我成为亲密的好友
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.39,0:19:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好友…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.06,0:19:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 你不愿意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.65,0:19:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 你突然这么说 只是有点吃惊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.57,0:19:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好友 虽然听起来有点不好意思 但也不坏嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.97,0:19:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后也请多指教 好友
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.89,0:19:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊 我们是…好友
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.00,0:19:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.15,0:19:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.48,0:19:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 没事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.84,0:19:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.69,0:19:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐 电话打给谁的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.29,0:19:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽妹妹的手机
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.20,0:19:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解开她的误会了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.94,0:20:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟她说了次郎同学不是女仆控
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.08,0:20:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女仆控？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.44,0:20:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.78,0:20:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐 到底是怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.82,0:20:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.15,0:20:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.14,0:20:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就证明了你没有特殊癖好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.17,0:20:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的那一出也实在是够害羞的了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.61,0:20:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了啊 多亏了政宗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.47,0:20:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.89,0:20:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这首曲子真不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.70,0:20:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得是叫做「永远相信朋友」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.18,0:20:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.09,0:20:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 换衣服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.15,0:20:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 今后我大概再也不会来女仆店了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.90,0:20:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.48,0:20:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是这么说的吧 一天的临时工
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.03,0:20:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话虽如此…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.24,0:20:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.50,0:20:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.42,0:20:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说让你来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.77,0:21:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔来这里打工 店长也说了厨房人手不够
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.57,0:21:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 你来的话 以后也可以把作业借给你看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.20,0:21:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么不好吧 应该不是什么坏事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.18,0:21:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 有空会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.27,0:21:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.60,0:21:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.97,0:21:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.91,0:21:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.02,0:21:26.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…谢谢！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.09,0:21:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到铃声就知道是笨蛋胆小鬼的来电
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.64,0:21:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 还有我的专属铃声啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.68,0:21:52.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到了吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.72,0:21:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是巧合
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.31,0:21:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跑 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.75,0:21:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.04,0:22:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.98,0:22:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跑！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.22,0:23:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙 瞒着我穿内裤
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.56,0:23:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥才是 只穿了一条内裤
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.88,0:23:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我除了内裤什么都没穿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.86,0:23:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还是在便利店
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.02,0:23:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥的内裤什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.24,0:23:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全 完全一点也不喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.25,0:23:55.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的妹妹不可能穿那么可爱的内裤！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.42,0:23:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起内裤 拳头拳头拳头…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.38,0:24:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是出了一身汗 总之先请我大吃一顿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.99,0:24:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集「迷茫管家与懦弱的我」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.46,0:24:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第10话 「我不客气啦」


