[Script Info]
Title:Mayochiki BD 06 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: opjp,DFPMaruGothic-SB,17,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正粗圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,8,1
Style: edcn,华康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.26,0:00:55.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.11,0:00:58.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.07,0:01:03.70,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}抱きしめて翔べ　遙か遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.57,0:01:21.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ゲームセットなんてない日々　イメージして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.69,0:01:27.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}叶えたい未来　数えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.05,0:01:33.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}打ち明け合ったら約束　あきらめない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.13,0:01:38.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夢を形にするまで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.08,0:01:43.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}好きなこと　全力で追いかけようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.72,0:01:46.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一緒に…ね!?　楽しくね!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.38,0:01:51.25,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}希望の羽広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.26,0:01:55.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.13,0:01:58.03,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.12,0:02:02.65,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.74,0:02:03.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.72,0:02:06.46,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}未知数のドアだって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.50,0:02:09.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怖がらず開けてね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.21,0:02:11.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.76,0:02:17.33,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}舞い上がれ　彼方へと
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.26,0:00:55.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.11,0:00:58.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.07,0:01:03.70,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怀着这份心情 飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.57,0:01:21.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想像着没有尽头的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.69,0:01:27.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}细数着想要实现的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.05,0:01:33.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}说出心里话的我们约定 不要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.13,0:01:38.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}直到将梦想变成现实
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.08,0:01:43.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}喜欢的东西 就要全力追寻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.72,0:01:46.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一起来吧 很开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.38,0:01:51.25,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}张开希望的羽翼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.26,0:01:55.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.13,0:01:58.03,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.12,0:02:02.65,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}带着勇气启程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.74,0:02:03.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.72,0:02:06.46,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}就算是未知数的门
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.50,0:02:09.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}也能毫不畏惧地打开
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.21,0:02:11.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.76,0:02:17.33,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飞扬空中 直至彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}声に出して　楽しいって言っちゃったら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雲一つ無い青空　この胸に広がってくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハートシグナル　キュンと立てて　飛び込んだ世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はみ出しちゃえ!　私と言うキャパシティ拡張　楽しいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}止まらないスピードになって恋してたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}急ごっ!　二人だけの時空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3　飛び越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に逢いたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}突き抜ける風になって届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうちょっと　可愛くアプローチ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハート型の未来になって
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君にご奉仕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そばにいたいから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只要将快乐说出声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}万里无云的蓝天 就会在这心中展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在突然闯入的世界 怦然心跳地发射心灵的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}冲破界线 我将快乐的容量扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想以无法停止的速度恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧 只属于两人的时空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3 越过阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想与你相见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想化作穿透一切的风向你传递
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}略带可爱地接近
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变成心形的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为您效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因为想在你身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.65,0:00:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久 久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.65,0:00:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问还有别的吩咐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.62,0:00:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人 下面轮到这桌了！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.74,0:00:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 请稍等
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.90,0:00:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.45,0:00:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里为您点餐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.94,0:00:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请在座位上稍等
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.86,0:00:35.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多要换班了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.76,0:00:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩…泳装太暴露了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.37,0:00:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正有围围裙 稍微暴露点没事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.99,0:00:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对对 这是给客人的福利
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.41,0:02:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始战争吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.72,0:02:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 约会了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.18,0:02:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好带领我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.60,0:02:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带领你？我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.57,0:02:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.43,0:02:38.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情 情侣的话不是理所当然的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.27,0:02:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是什么 面对女生时就没自信了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.15,0:02:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是胆小鬼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.92,0:02:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你自己又怎样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.68,0:02:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别 别把我和你相提并论
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.06,0:02:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别看我这样 经验丰富着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.80,0:02:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就由你来带领好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.49,0:02:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个无聊的男人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.76,0:03:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我告诉你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.09,0:03:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会都是男生请客的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.57,0:03:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.15,0:03:11.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.82,0:03:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 想到是别人请客更觉得美味
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.69,0:03:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.81,0:03:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来就说声啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.07,0:03:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请爸妈吃点什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.91,0:03:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包在我身上～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.55,0:03:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真期待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.55,0:03:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边这边
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.50,0:03:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.51,0:03:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次约会结束以后 请你吃我做的菜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.96,0:03:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了啊 突然
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.96,0:03:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管这么多做什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.78,0:03:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是这样一直让你请客 有些过意不去而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.22,0:03:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 我是无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.24,0:03:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.65,0:03:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面没有章鱼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.38,0:03:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说了吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.47,0:03:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得装成情侣才行
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.35,0:03:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 快吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.94,0:03:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是很不好意思的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.65,0:03:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.93,0:04:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇佐美 你到底…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.61,0:04:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活该
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.92,0:04:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近 近卫！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.15,0:04:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来我要监视你！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.19,0:04:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.78,0:04:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是你的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.51,0:04:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友的话 有义务确定你是否在进行纯洁的交往
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.05,0:04:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.18,0:04:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙竟然泡了两个妹子！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.15,0:04:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静点 昴大人可是男人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.85,0:04:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了这份上 就算是男人也无关紧要了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.88,0:04:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个混蛋 太羡慕他了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.15,0:04:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你要跟到哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.84,0:04:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.78,0:04:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友的话 这种程度很普通的！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.91,0:04:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不普通好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.55,0:04:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 我可是情侣哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.25,0:04:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么！太狡猾了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.11,0:04:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.62,0:05:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动物咖啡厅？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.15,0:05:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微休息会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.24,0:05:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赞成！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.25,0:05:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs22}（动物咖啡厅）\N（凌晨两点的惨叫）
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.47,0:05:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.84,0:05:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.00,0:05:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 哥哥和…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.33,0:05:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佐美前辈！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.15,0:05:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临呢 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.15,0:05:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 没想到是你们班呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.15,0:05:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说小佐美前辈 真是吓了我一跳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.02,0:05:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你和我哥认识呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.25,0:05:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂町 你还记得我说过几次叫你别叫我这个绰号吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.83,0:05:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌啦 别这么傲嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.13,0:05:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是好朋友吗 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.73,0:05:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 住手 住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.30,0:05:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佐美前辈 皮肤真光滑
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.19,0:06:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.54,0:06:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别往奇怪的地方摸啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.00,0:06:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我适可而止！明明只是个后辈！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.94,0:06:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佐美前辈偶尔也来部里露露面哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.05,0:06:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎 这个怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.27,0:06:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫前辈 你来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.98,0:06:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是红羽妹妹的班级啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.80,0:06:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.69,0:06:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吊饰怎么样 还能配成一对哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.11,0:06:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你很怕红羽？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.05,0:06:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该说是羡慕吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.19,0:06:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羡慕？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.54,0:06:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢 她不是都活得像她自己吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.08,0:06:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天真烂漫又精力充沛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.98,0:06:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论何时都是那么的坦率
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.97,0:06:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,况且 还有你这个关系这么好的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.11,0:06:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉和你在一起都有点厌了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.79,0:06:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也去昴大人那里好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.05,0:06:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？那交易怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.63,0:07:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了 快点给我过去！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.61,0:07:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正你和我在一起也不觉得开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.78,0:07:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 那我就去近卫那里了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.07,0:07:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我说 什么颜色的好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.38,0:07:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们去买了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.48,0:07:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.38,0:07:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 绵羊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.93,0:07:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.96,0:07:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.70,0:07:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.04,0:07:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流的名字是鸣海奈香流
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.99,0:07:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是手艺部的一年级学生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.02,0:07:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是手艺部啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.15,0:07:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次自我介绍 坂町前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.51,0:07:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是「用温暖的目光守护昴大人会」的会长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.59,0:07:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸣海奈香流
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.30,0:07:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守望会？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.15,0:07:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我的眼镜已经只能映照出你了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.70,0:07:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.84,0:07:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我甜美的眼镜…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.31,0:08:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇～奈香流的代表作啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.17,0:08:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,画出这种乱七八糟漫画的人竟然是会长
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.27,0:08:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太奇怪了吧 守望会！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.16,0:08:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 哪里乱七八糟了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.95,0:08:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.79,0:08:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说了干嘛这么着重刻画眼镜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.44,0:08:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为眼镜才是人类文化的象征
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.56,0:08:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经有位伟人也留下了这样的格言
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.85,0:08:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「没有面包的话 戴上眼镜不就行了吗」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.48,0:08:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经十分了解你既是个腐女还是眼镜控了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.46,0:08:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢 会长大人找我有什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.16,0:08:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请快逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.40,0:08:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.16,0:08:41.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过会奈香流的守望会和S4的对决集会就要秘密开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.44,0:08:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,视结果而定 说不定前辈会遇到危险
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.23,0:08:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是那不是已经没问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.28,0:08:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想别太信任宇佐美前辈比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.28,0:08:55.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.57,0:08:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是提出了某种交易吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.60,0:09:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说散布「前辈们在交往」的消息
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.14,0:09:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算使守望会陷入混乱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.15,0:09:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是这种程度守望会是不会动摇的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.47,0:09:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们相信着前辈和昴大人～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.63,0:09:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,PASS！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.72,0:09:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 宇佐美的计划也不过是纸上谈兵吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.58,0:09:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.51,0:09:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇佐美前辈提出的好处
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.73,0:09:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是前辈的人身安全吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.37,0:09:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过那几乎可以肯定是谎话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.91,0:09:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为宇佐美前辈没可能统率S4…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.73,0:09:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大意了 没想到会藏在这种布偶里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.18,0:09:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的吗 宇佐美
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.53,0:09:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.64,0:09:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一开始就欺骗了你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.43,0:09:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.51,0:10:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎 这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.53,0:10:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然次郎觉得难以启齿 我不勉强你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.93,0:10:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.20,0:10:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少告诉我发生了什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.37,0:10:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.12,0:10:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在这个学校里…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.85,0:10:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的两个粉丝团在互相对抗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.15,0:10:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长是那家伙的守望会和…S4
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.70,0:10:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果过会儿在秘密集会上S4赢的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.47,0:10:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像我会有危险
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.32,0:10:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢 你打算怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.74,0:10:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.96,0:10:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我说你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.20,0:10:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.07,0:10:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴 昴大人！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.69,0:10:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话想问你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.26,0:10:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生 生 生鲜
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.02,0:10:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生鲜？是呢 我喜欢不戴套的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.70,0:11:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是要干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.00,0:11:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘 请别出声
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.88,0:11:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴今天各位都聚集在了这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.57,0:11:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.51,0:11:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始战争吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.40,0:11:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自我介绍晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.75,0:11:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的主持人由「Shooting Star Subaru Sama」代表
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.45,0:11:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浪岚学园二年生 凉月奏来担当
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.16,0:11:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.61,0:11:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 别那么大声
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.77,0:11:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.16,0:11:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照相照相
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.96,0:11:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个混蛋眼镜！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.04,0:11:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特地跑来送死 胆子还真不小
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.36,0:11:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请肃静
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.55,0:12:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在请不要争吵
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.43,0:12:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为包括「能如何处置那边的坂町同学」在内
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.08,0:12:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个活动的胜利者…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.43,0:12:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能完全征服失败者！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.54,0:12:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}（第一届 昴大人粉丝测试大会）
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.93,0:12:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴 在那边可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.82,0:12:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我选择让双方都不会受伤的做法
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.18,0:12:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.49,0:12:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.40,0:12:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙到底去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.28,0:12:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答正确
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.16,0:12:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真难对付啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.57,0:12:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.00,0:12:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天昴买了果汁的自动贩卖机
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.17,0:12:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,负责进货的公司的职员是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.76,0:12:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡洛斯上原
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.71,0:12:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答正确
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.63,0:13:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.13,0:13:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 关于我的问题自己竟然一道都不会
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.12,0:13:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个 其实从中间开始就已经和你几乎没有关系了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.70,0:13:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来 终于到了最终问题
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.59,0:13:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得分是5分
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.57,0:13:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答出这道问题的一方就是胜利者
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.78,0:13:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 请听问题
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.94,0:13:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴的初吻对象是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.55,0:13:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.40,0:13:27.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫 是机会
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.55,0:13:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要害羞快点回答
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.05,0:13:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说真的吗 次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.45,0:13:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分数是对方领先
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.49,0:13:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去的话 坂町前辈会被血祭…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.23,0:13:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.59,0:13:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 近卫 这是我一生的请求
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.63,0:13:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.37,0:13:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答正确！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.49,0:13:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就让我们来看看正确答案的录像
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.97,0:14:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋 坠入地狱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.50,0:14:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀呀～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.83,0:14:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 做点什么吧 凉月
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.44,0:14:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做点什么是指什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.66,0:14:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还用问 这样下去的话我会被那些家伙杀掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.51,0:14:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}下～地～狱～吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.00,0:14:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么愉快的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.69,0:14:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,S！你这个死S！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.42,0:14:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不是应该把我的初吻作为问题呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.10,0:14:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀真不得了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.67,0:14:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.78,0:14:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我喜欢的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.71,0:14:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是凉月奏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.84,0:14:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.48,0:15:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.53,0:15:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.63,0:15:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个混蛋 难道在劈腿
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.56,0:15:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 坂町同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.95,0:15:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是对不起 虽然你是个好人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.36,0:15:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得明白一点 也就只是个好人而已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.71,0:15:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为朋友你是一个很好的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.78,0:15:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但作为恋人的话就有点…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.10,0:15:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.55,0:15:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被甩了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.64,0:15:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 明明是个好人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.68,0:15:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以对不起了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.06,0:15:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.52,0:15:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的是个好人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.05,0:15:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等一下 给我等一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.27,0:15:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢我吧 次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.71,0:15:38.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我特地那么过分地甩了你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.24,0:15:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 谢谢你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.29,0:15:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我很生气呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.09,0:15:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是为了保命
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.71,0:15:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在那么多人面前进行假告白
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.03,0:15:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我受的伤可不浅啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.70,0:15:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不 那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.89,0:15:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是 我现在要报复
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.36,0:16:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.61,0:16:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 遭受相同境遇的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.08,0:16:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.34,0:16:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上后夜祭就要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.07,0:16:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易才得救 现在开始好好享受吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.70,0:16:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来参加活动的人中 有没有一个叫宇佐美的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.82,0:16:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没问她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.84,0:16:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是你的女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.79,0:16:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之你是知道的吧 那家伙和我的事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.68,0:16:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个孩子的话 在活动开始之前就退出「S4」了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.55,0:16:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然说是个有点轻浮的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.54,0:16:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但却没有和任何成员搞好关系的打算
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.95,0:16:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.22,0:16:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊 黑心兔子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.24,0:16:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我也会相信你的」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.27,0:16:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「所以 请相信我」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.07,0:16:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑 不全都是骗人的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.53,0:16:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「抱歉 笨蛋胆小鬼」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.25,0:17:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我一开始就欺骗了你」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.78,0:17:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫名其妙 这样做到底是想干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.64,0:17:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我很中意这里」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.20,0:17:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退学申请是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.67,0:17:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没告诉你这个地方就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.02,0:17:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候的昴大人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.01,0:17:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁都无法接近的 孤独的王子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.16,0:17:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我就在想
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.95,0:17:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「啊 莫非这个人也和我一样吗」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.22,0:17:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 这个人的话 昴大人的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.30,0:17:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该能够成为我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.81,0:17:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是昴大人他变了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.42,0:18:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了二年级 交到了朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.84,0:18:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.14,0:18:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你哦 笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.14,0:18:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「自从与你相遇后 昴大人就变了」我不禁这样想
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.48,0:18:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是有什么特殊的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.01,0:18:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.98,0:18:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果就是 我什么都没能改变
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.79,0:18:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我终于明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.63,0:18:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人一定是靠自己改变的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.66,0:18:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我的话就到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.22,0:18:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但最后让我说一句
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.95,0:18:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我果然讨厌你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.17,0:18:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也讨厌昴大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.61,0:18:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且比起任何人 我最讨厌这样的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.05,0:18:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.74,0:18:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学园祭还没有结束
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.48,0:18:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…去哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.61,0:18:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.01,0:18:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「伪装情侣到学园祭结束」是这样约定的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.93,0:18:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我 笨蛋胆小…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.75,0:19:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.65,0:19:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里不舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.21,0:19:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 刚才你把秘密告诉了我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.45,0:19:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次换我把秘密告诉你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.06,0:19:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.33,0:19:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女性恐惧症？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.12,0:19:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈…什么啊 那个羞耻的胆小体质
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.36,0:19:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了不要笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.80,0:19:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是很认真地在烦恼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.83,0:19:24.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.61,0:19:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为明明看不到他人的内心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.40,0:19:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却可以相处得很融洽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.20,0:19:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.61,0:19:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只会怀疑别人…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.15,0:19:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然说相信我也是骗人的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.15,0:19:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话打破约定也没什么关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.65,0:19:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约定？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.78,0:19:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你吃章鱼烧的时候 你说过的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.80,0:19:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「请你吃我做的菜」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.22,0:19:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信了 还很期待的说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.82,0:19:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.54,0:20:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都听大小姐说了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.04,0:20:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都是骗人的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.36,0:20:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 次郎同学喜欢我这件事自不必说
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.64,0:20:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和宇佐美同学在交往这件事也是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.57,0:20:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.78,0:20:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.17,0:20:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了保护我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.27,0:20:21.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉给你添麻烦了 次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.85,0:20:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要这样 近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.03,0:20:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我擅自做的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.77,0:20:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.81,0:20:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于这件事 你也有不对哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.67,0:20:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你误会了真抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.48,0:20:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 重新介绍一次
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.71,0:20:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇佐美政宗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.04,0:20:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.18,0:20:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.89,0:20:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎的朋友 就是我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.49,0:20:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.49,0:20:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.27,0:20:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 宇佐美前辈好狡猾
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.36,0:20:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴前辈要和我跳舞
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.08,0:21:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽妹妹 请把手给我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.50,0:21:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为交换 把我哥借给你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.51,0:21:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有宇佐美前辈是特例哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.69,0:21:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把人当作东西一样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.12,0:21:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.21,0:21:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.02,0:21:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也能改变吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.55,0:21:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我也…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.35,0:21:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要改变！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.27,0:21:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮你治
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.67,0:21:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.46,0:21:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的女性恐惧症
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.82,0:21:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么又提这事…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.13,0:21:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.99,0:21:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.83,0:21:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你是朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.83,0:21:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 今后叫我的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.37,0:21:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.77,0:21:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友之间这样很正常吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.51,0:21:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快点叫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.13,0:21:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政宗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.68,0:21:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再叫一次
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.25,0:21:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政宗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.39,0:22:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政宗政宗政宗政宗…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.75,0:22:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干吗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.59,0:22:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多关照 笨蛋胆小鬼
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.40,0:23:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.32,0:23:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.03,0:23:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.07,0:23:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.87,0:23:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.02,0:23:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.87,0:23:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.22,0:23:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人和女人做的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.92,0:23:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好 反正也就是一起学习一起逛街这种事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.50,0:23:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(388,323)\fs20}ochi
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.50,0:23:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道肯定会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.84,0:23:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.84,0:24:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集「迷茫管家与懦弱的我」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.09,0:24:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,323)\fs20}kake ochi
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.09,0:24:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第7话 「私奔吧」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.65,0:24:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个ochi对上了啊


