[Script Info]
Title:Mayochiki BD 10 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: opjp,DFPMaruGothic-SB,17,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正粗圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,8,1
Style: edcn,华康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,8,1
Style: injp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,15,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H009753FD,&H96FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,7,10,10,8,1
Style: incn,华康少女文字W5(P),15,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H009753FD,&H96FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,7,10,10,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.26,0:01:32.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.11,0:01:35.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.07,0:01:40.70,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}抱きしめて翔べ　遙か遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.57,0:01:58.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ゲームセットなんてない日々　イメージして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.69,0:02:04.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}叶えたい未来　数えて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.05,0:02:10.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}打ち明け合ったら約束　あきらめない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.13,0:02:15.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夢を形にするまで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.08,0:02:20.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}好きなこと　全力で追いかけようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.72,0:02:23.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一緒に…ね!?　楽しくね!!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.38,0:02:28.25,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}希望の羽広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.26,0:02:32.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.13,0:02:35.03,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.12,0:02:39.65,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.74,0:02:40.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.72,0:02:43.46,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}未知数のドアだって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.50,0:02:46.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怖がらず開けてね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.21,0:02:48.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.76,0:02:54.33,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}舞い上がれ　彼方へと
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.26,0:01:32.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.11,0:01:35.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.07,0:01:40.70,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怀着这份心情 飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.57,0:01:58.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想像着没有尽头的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.69,0:02:04.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}细数着想要实现的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.05,0:02:10.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}说出心里话的我们约定 不要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.13,0:02:15.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}直到将梦想变成现实
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.08,0:02:20.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}喜欢的东西 就要全力追寻
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.72,0:02:23.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一起来吧 很开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.38,0:02:28.25,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}张开希望的羽翼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.26,0:02:32.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.13,0:02:35.03,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.12,0:02:39.65,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}带着勇气启程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.74,0:02:40.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.72,0:02:43.46,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}就算是未知数的门
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.50,0:02:46.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}也能毫不畏惧地打开
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.21,0:02:48.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.76,0:02:54.33,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飞扬空中 直至彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.50,0:22:35.34,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}声に出して　楽しいって言っちゃったら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.73,0:22:43.40,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雲一つ無い青空　この胸に広がってくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.94,0:22:49.66,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハートシグナル　キュンと立てて　飛び込んだ世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.97,0:22:58.64,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はみ出しちゃえ!　私と言うキャパシティ拡張　楽しいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.38,0:23:04.82,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}止まらないスピードになって恋してたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.04,0:23:08.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}急ごっ!　二人だけの時空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.65,0:23:11.67,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3　飛び越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.71,0:23:14.51,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に逢いたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.59,0:23:18.99,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}突き抜ける風になって届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.25,0:23:22.51,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうちょっと　可愛くアプローチ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.83,0:23:27.85,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハート型の未来になって
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.91,0:23:30.59,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君にご奉仕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.26,0:23:36.01,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そばにいたいから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.50,0:22:35.34,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只要将快乐说出声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.73,0:22:43.40,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}万里无云的蓝天 就会在这心中展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.94,0:22:49.66,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在突然闯入的世界 怦然心跳地发射心灵的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.97,0:22:58.64,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}冲破界线 我将快乐的容量扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.38,0:23:04.82,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想以无法停止的速度恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.04,0:23:08.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧 只属于两人的时空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.65,0:23:11.67,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3 越过阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.71,0:23:14.51,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想与你相见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.59,0:23:18.99,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想化作穿透一切的风向你传递
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.25,0:23:22.51,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}略带可爱地接近
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.83,0:23:27.85,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变成心形的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.91,0:23:30.59,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为您效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.26,0:23:36.01,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因为想在你身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------INJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.85,0:09:51.65,injp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハッピーバースデー　トゥー　ユー　ハッピーバースデー　トゥー　ユー
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.79,0:09:59.93,injp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}私から　あなたへと　ハッピーハッピー　バースデー
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.81,0:10:24.50,injp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今日は特別な笑顔に会える日
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.76,0:10:32.77,injp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}その瞬間に願いは叶うんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.82,0:10:40.64,injp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}出会えたこと　それこそ　最高のギフト
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.78,0:10:49.02,injp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}さあ　ローソクの火を消して
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.85,0:10:58.59,injp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハッピーバースデー　トゥー　ユー　ハッピーバースデー　トゥー　ユー
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.80,0:11:06.54,injp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}私から　あなたへと　ハッピーハッピー　バースデー
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.81,0:11:17.18,injp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}私から　あなたへと　ハッピーハッピー　バースデー
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------INCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.85,0:09:51.65,incn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Happy birthday to you Happy birthday to you
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.79,0:09:59.93,incn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}由我向你献上的祝福 Happy happy birthday
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.81,0:10:24.50,incn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今天是与特别的笑容相会之日
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.76,0:10:32.77,incn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在那瞬间愿望将会实现
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.82,0:10:40.64,incn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你我相会 那正是至高无上的礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.78,0:10:49.02,incn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}来吧 吹熄这蜡烛的火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.85,0:10:58.59,incn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}Happy birthday to you Happy birthday to you
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.80,0:11:06.54,incn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}由我向你献上的祝福 Happy happy birthday
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.81,0:11:17.18,incn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}由我向你献上的祝福 Happy happy birthday
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.27,0:00:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs22\fad(500,0)}（游戏研究会）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.08,0:00:02.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.87,0:00:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔 理事长的女儿被攻略了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.73,0:00:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥暑假还要来学校玩恋爱游戏啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.27,0:00:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在家玩怕被父母发现啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.39,0:00:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月同学！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.18,0:00:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明还在放暑假您怎么来了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.98,0:00:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想请你们做一个游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.55,0:00:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs22\fad(0,170)}（计划书 制定人：凉月奏）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.92,0:00:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,25)\fs22}（三次元早已不存在希望！ 世界寄望于二次元的救赎！）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.43,0:00:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔 格斗游戏吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.92,0:00:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候要求完成？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.37,0:00:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,期限是到8月28日
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.94,0:00:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说到明天为止哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.37,0:00:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.20,0:00:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.60,0:00:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.29,0:00:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才…才不是非要拜托你们不可的呢…！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.43,0:01:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您是降临于三次元的天使！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.34,0:01:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.95,0:01:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天 呢～
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.56,0:01:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天明天
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.12,0:01:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真不敢相信
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.04,0:01:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再 再抱紧点
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.54,0:01:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒啦 这样一来明天就万无一失了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.76,0:01:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嘞 明天！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.29,0:03:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不客气啦
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.46,0:03:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Guten Morgen！ Hello 哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.96,0:03:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.95,0:03:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.71,0:03:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.70,0:03:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.41,0:03:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Hello 哥哥 我出去下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.24,0:03:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傍晚就会回来的」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.92,0:03:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.95,0:04:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？ 嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.60,0:04:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.69,0:04:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.80,0:04:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂町红羽 从今天起就16岁了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.01,0:04:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是可喜可贺
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.13,0:04:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇佐美前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.64,0:04:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.61,0:04:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 这是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.66,0:04:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.87,0:04:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佐美前辈吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.41,0:04:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过都是我掏钱的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.16,0:04:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓的事不用说啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.30,0:04:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.67,0:04:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 别客气吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.76,0:04:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我不客气啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.46,0:04:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.34,0:05:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 小佐美前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.10,0:05:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真会做菜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.21,0:05:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.85,0:05:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一个人住 所以小意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.05,0:05:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？ 刚才那里好像有喀哒喀哒的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.55,0:05:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似这间屋子有时会出现呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.48,0:05:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现…是指骚灵现象吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.08,0:05:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.37,0:05:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前住在这里的女人 被男友甩了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.85,0:05:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后想不开…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.08,0:05:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用头撞豆腐 被家犬咬到手
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.97,0:05:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 然后到后来终于…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.55,0:05:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.34,0:05:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌恐怖故事！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.59,0:05:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么大不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.40,0:05:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过有时候电视机自己会打开而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.96,0:05:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.69,0:05:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不会干坏事的 别担心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.59,0:05:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 刚好也热闹起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.72,0:05:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面是期待已久的礼物时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.30,0:05:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咚咚嘟嘟～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.07,0:06:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.88,0:06:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼镜？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.74,0:06:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很适合很适合
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.74,0:06:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外沿的曲线很漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.97,0:06:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼻夹的安定感很完美
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.87,0:06:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,额角的触感无以伦比
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.11,0:06:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯钛 β型钛 钛合金的轻便感
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.12,0:06:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这副眼镜有着能驱散一切幽灵的强烈驱魔力量
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.73,0:06:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗！？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.89,0:06:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 只要有了这个
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.48,0:06:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就什么都不用怕了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.15,0:06:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.68,0:06:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小奈流谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.14,0:06:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是最让人开心的礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.70,0:06:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用客气
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.29,0:06:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「红羽妹妹 生日快乐」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.42,0:06:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的～
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.27,0:06:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫前辈～
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.24,0:06:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个 是小佐美前辈亲手做的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.02,0:06:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我姑且算是手艺部的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.73,0:07:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.72,0:07:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天开始 要和近卫前辈一起睡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.32,0:07:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咚咚嘟嘟～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.49,0:07:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 开始礼物第二弹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.17,0:07:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.20,0:07:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 宇佐美前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.01,0:07:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 真的要来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.60,0:07:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.24,0:07:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸣海奈香流作品
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.66,0:07:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《眼镜回忆》特别篇
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.83,0:07:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《次郎金和巴鲁斯 某个夏天的回忆》
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.94,0:07:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始开始
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.07,0:07:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.95,0:07:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁～斯 啊 真不敢相信…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.56,0:07:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就在我的臂弯中…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.62,0:07:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次 次郎金 再抱紧点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.92,0:07:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁～斯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.11,0:07:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算这是最后的夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.33,0:07:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对你的爱也是永恒的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.07,0:07:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 奈香流 过头了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.44,0:08:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请继续 这可是给红羽妹妹的生日礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.03,0:08:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次 次郎金
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.96,0:08:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对你和你眼镜的爱也是永恒的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.81,0:08:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着就是…进行二人的誓约之吻
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.51,0:08:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是小佐美前辈！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.73,0:08:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么巴鲁斯和次郎金啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.89,0:08:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不明显是笨蛋胆小鬼和昴大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.74,0:08:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀！是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.78,0:08:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我注意到啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.93,0:08:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咚咚嘟嘟～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.12,0:08:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 开始礼物第三弹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.74,0:08:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家移动到第二会场
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.58,0:08:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二会场？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.61,0:08:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.99,0:09:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 近卫前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.09,0:09:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二会场就是这里 Maid In Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.95,0:09:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,16岁生日快乐 红羽妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.31,0:09:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.03,0:09:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位都知道我的生日吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.53,0:09:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.47,0:09:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说奈香流 为什么是这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.08,0:09:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.38,0:09:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是这位大小姐包场
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.60,0:09:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽情享受吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.32,0:09:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 小兔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.95,0:09:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想再看一次小兔的女仆装呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.85,0:09:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别叫我小兔！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.34,0:09:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.90,0:09:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么大家准备好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.96,0:09:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好了～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.55,0:09:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预备 开始
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.78,0:10:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.23,0:10:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.20,0:10:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 沉默的羔羊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.42,0:10:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 近卫前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.33,0:11:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.00,0:11:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是谢谢大家了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.83,0:11:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.36,0:11:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 是8岁生日时的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.60,0:11:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要 不要 不要～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.13,0:11:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.37,0:11:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 我要见爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.19,0:11:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要见～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.90,0:11:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽 红～羽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.89,0:11:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 你的生日礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.23,0:11:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.65,0:12:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小熊就叫它熊五郎吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.85,0:12:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从哥哥那里收到礼物了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.28,0:12:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 把自己的零用钱全部用来给我买礼物了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.29,0:12:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个好哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.41,0:12:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.45,0:12:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很美好的回忆呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.19,0:12:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.79,0:12:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 合体倒割
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.79,0:12:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}（注：小川直也和桥本真也的格斗合体技）
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.04,0:12:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为主人 注入爱心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.49,0:12:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ROUND1 FIGHT！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.29,0:12:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你打得落花流水
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.25,0:12:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙 居然瞒着我穿内裤！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.45,0:13:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从以前就一直想把自己作为对战角色来使用
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.72,0:13:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 算是没有白做
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.73,0:13:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正是用了很恶毒的手法强迫别人做的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.01,0:13:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 为什么只有笨蛋胆小鬼没穿衣服？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.46,0:13:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裸…裸体
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.21,0:13:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 准确来说 应该是穿了一条内裤
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.75,0:13:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法因为那是哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.53,0:13:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要戴着眼镜就OK
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.15,0:13:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.11,0:13:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫耳和过膝袜究极
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.39,0:13:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼镜和吊袜带最高
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.42,0:13:35.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然那个人是变态呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.56,0:13:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在游戏里也是喜好一览无余啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.18,0:13:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是青春的迸溅啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.75,0:13:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽不是怪兽啦～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.51,0:13:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只穿一条内裤的次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.18,0:13:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在便利店里追着妹妹跑
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.67,0:13:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级场面啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.60,0:13:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么和什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.55,0:13:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.52,0:13:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布鲁马之拳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.68,0:14:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 输掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.72,0:14:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要挑战我？还早了16年！哈哈哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.26,0:14:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.28,0:14:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少在游戏中让次郎同学赢一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.99,0:14:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真空虚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.97,0:14:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人 再来一次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.27,0:14:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.72,0:14:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次我不会输的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.35,0:14:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ROUND2 FIGHT！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.63,0:14:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是最棒的生日
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.99,0:14:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.65,0:14:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用谢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.89,0:14:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个秋千
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.83,0:14:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.15,0:14:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是10岁生日时候的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.16,0:14:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最讨厌妈妈了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.30,0:15:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈在等你 回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.11,0:15:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是你的生日派对
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.38,0:15:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.65,0:15:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.35,0:15:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.90,0:15:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.74,0:15:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候来接我的哥哥的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.84,0:15:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到现在还记得
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.85,0:15:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好开心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.54,0:15:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.64,0:15:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个好哥哥呢 次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.18,0:15:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.00,0:15:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12岁的生日一整天都在陪我玩游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.80,0:15:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,13岁的生日在牧场买了冰激淋给我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.72,0:15:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,14岁的生日和我一起放焰火
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.86,0:15:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一次的生日都记着吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.37,0:16:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.40,0:16:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年是怎么过的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.00,0:16:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.83,0:16:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.00,0:16:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是～嗨～今天是～嗨～
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.58,0:16:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,8月28日～呼～8…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.56,0:16:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 你去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.80,0:16:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑濑说他拿到了演唱会的门票
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.95,0:16:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太幸运了 很难得的票哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.80,0:16:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见啦 妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.31,0:16:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.46,0:16:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.28,0:16:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.72,0:16:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.73,0:16:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不错吧 这件T恤
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.85,0:16:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是最后一件了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.20,0:16:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一生都会好好保存的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.73,0:16:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.80,0:17:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了怎么了怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.97,0:17:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好过分
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.87,0:17:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然把妹妹的生日忘了 太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.05,0:17:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.00,0:17:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥这个笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.97,0:17:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 红羽 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.96,0:17:14.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋笨蛋笨蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.39,0:17:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的对不起 对不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.20,0:17:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.74,0:17:25.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥这个笨蛋 笨蛋 笨蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.73,0:17:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了这样的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.58,0:17:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然把唯一的妹妹的生日忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.06,0:17:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真拿次郎同学没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.72,0:17:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年妈妈也因为去了国外不在家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.71,0:17:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是大家给我庆祝了一整天 我已经很高兴了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.83,0:17:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说红羽妹妹 来我家吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.62,0:17:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天开始别做次郎同学的妹妹了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.33,0:17:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来当我的妹妹吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.43,0:17:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,践踏妹妹心灵的次郎同学没有当哥哥的资格
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.52,0:18:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是大小姐 谁都会有犯糊涂的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.08,0:18:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然这么说的话 昴去当次郎同学的妹妹如何
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.43,0:18:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当的话也不是妹妹 而是弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.96,0:18:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.14,0:18:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 但是哥哥他在我中学毕业典礼上代替妈妈来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.97,0:18:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后 我第一次穿上高中制服的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.56,0:18:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还称赞我「制服很合身哦」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.99,0:18:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且 一直在当我的练习对象
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.87,0:18:41.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在向哥哥撒娇
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.01,0:18:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我已经16岁了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.81,0:18:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多也该离开哥哥独立了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.13,0:18:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 即使哥哥忘了我的生日也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.79,0:19:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为哥哥不管什么时候都很照顾我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.85,0:19:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.69,0:19:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他礼物回头寄给你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.76,0:19:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学今年会记得吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.95,0:19:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定不要紧的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.89,0:19:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.50,0:19:44.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.51,0:19:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 这是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.34,0:19:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…难道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.91,0:19:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽 生日快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.14,0:19:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以打开吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.78,0:19:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.52,0:20:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好大的玩偶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.54,0:20:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯白的可爱狗狗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.03,0:20:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉红羽 那是白熊…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.10,0:20:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 谢谢 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.50,0:20:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 真的太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.01,0:20:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋笨蛋笨蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.69,0:20:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着那时的红羽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.79,0:20:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓不会让同样的错误再次发生
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.56,0:20:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽 去年不好意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.40,0:20:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 这么开心的生日还是第一次 实在太开心了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.20,0:20:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.67,0:20:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然好想对哥哥撒娇
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.43,0:20:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱一下就好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.55,0:20:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.13,0:20:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢哥哥了！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.36,0:21:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢哥哥了…最喜欢了…最喜欢了…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.31,0:21:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是这种下场吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.50,0:21:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy birthday～my sister！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.08,0:21:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？黄泉的兔子？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.72,0:21:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 这个不吉利的标题
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.16,0:21:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 也给你一份礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.29,0:21:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正也没觉得会是什么好东西
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.45,0:21:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再继续努力
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.96,0:21:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月奏！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.12,0:21:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会输给你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.69,0:21:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.23,0:21:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.26,0:21:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点给我放手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.88,0:21:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我一个人得救就足够了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.19,0:21:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么肮脏的内心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.22,0:22:06.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,GAME OVER了哦 小兔子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.48,0:22:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月奏！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.15,0:23:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐 我可以抱你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.07,0:23:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴 别这样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.42,0:23:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 我想把脸埋在大小姐的胸部蹭蹭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.23,0:23:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想亲吻您的脸颊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.79,0:23:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想永远闻着您头发的芳香
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.43,0:23:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.09,0:23:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.41,0:23:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴 你也被附体了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.17,0:23:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到那句话的人都被附体了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.93,0:24:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶魔的咒语 魔性的呓语 被诅咒的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.59,0:24:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.48,0:24:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集「迷茫管家与懦弱的我」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.90,0:24:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第11话 「啾！」


