[Script Info]
Title:Mayochiki BD 02 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: opjp,DFPMaruGothic-SB,17,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正粗圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,8,1
Style: edcn,华康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.36,0:01:03.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.21,0:01:06.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.17,0:01:11.80,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}抱きしめて翔べ　遙か遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.67,0:01:29.74,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ゲームセットなんてない日々　イメージして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.79,0:01:35.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}叶えたい未来　数えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.15,0:01:41.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}打ち明け合ったら約束　あきらめない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.23,0:01:46.14,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夢を形にするまで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.18,0:01:51.69,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}好きなこと　全力で追いかけようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.82,0:01:54.45,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一緒に…ね!?　楽しくね!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.48,0:01:59.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}希望の羽広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.36,0:02:03.20,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.23,0:02:06.13,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.22,0:02:10.75,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.84,0:02:11.81,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.82,0:02:14.56,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}未知数のドアだって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.60,0:02:17.28,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怖がらず開けてね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.31,0:02:19.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.86,0:02:25.43,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}舞い上がれ　彼方へと
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.36,0:01:03.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.21,0:01:06.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.17,0:01:11.80,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怀着这份心情 飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.67,0:01:29.74,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想像着没有尽头的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.79,0:01:35.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}细数着想要实现的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.15,0:01:41.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}说出心里话的我们约定 不要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.23,0:01:46.14,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}直到将梦想变成现实
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.18,0:01:51.69,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}喜欢的东西 就要全力追寻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.82,0:01:54.45,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一起来吧 很开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.48,0:01:59.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}张开希望的羽翼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.36,0:02:03.20,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.23,0:02:06.13,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.22,0:02:10.75,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}带着勇气启程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.84,0:02:11.81,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.82,0:02:14.56,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}就算是未知数的门
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.60,0:02:17.28,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}也能毫不畏惧地打开
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.31,0:02:19.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.86,0:02:25.43,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飞扬空中 直至彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}声に出して　楽しいって言っちゃったら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雲一つ無い青空　この胸に広がってくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハートシグナル　キュンと立てて　飛び込んだ世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はみ出しちゃえ!　私と言うキャパシティ拡張　楽しいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}止まらないスピードになって恋してたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}急ごっ!　二人だけの時空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3　飛び越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に逢いたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}突き抜ける風になって届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうちょっと　可愛くアプローチ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハート型の未来になって
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君にご奉仕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そばにいたいから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只要将快乐说出声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}万里无云的蓝天 就会在这心中展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在突然闯入的世界 怦然心跳地发射心灵的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}冲破界线 我将快乐的容量扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想以无法停止的速度恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧 只属于两人的时空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3 越过阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想与你相见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想化作穿透一切的风向你传递
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}略带可爱地接近
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变成心形的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为您效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因为想在你身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.65,0:00:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看看…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.86,0:00:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇啊啊啊啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.10,0:00:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不知悔改啊 小雨
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.90,0:00:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我姐姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.34,0:00:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 还是快点为大小姐准备早饭…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.70,0:00:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上为您准备的是蘑菇奶酪蛋包饭
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.23,0:00:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.41,0:00:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来啊 大小姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.34,0:00:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴 为什么 最近都是先出门！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.18,0:00:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静一点 小雨
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.21,0:00:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一讲到昴你就太过失控
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.84,0:00:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平胸和妹属性是最高级的美食
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.97,0:00:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说 今后的发展估计也十分美味呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.42,0:00:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奏小姐所喜欢的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.54,0:00:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是些意想不到的有趣东西呢
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.22,0:02:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得好喜欢！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.34,0:02:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.89,0:02:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你会和昴大人一起上学啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.38,0:02:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过是在半路正好遇到而已
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.53,0:02:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「其实昴大人是女生 而我仅仅被女生碰到就会流鼻血」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.21,0:02:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\fsp-1}「被抓住了把柄 所以为了让昴大人的秘密不被泄露而被监视着」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.05,0:02:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这怎么说得出口
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.43,0:03:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个 果然有特殊关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.24,0:03:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.37,0:03:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心哦 传闻S4已经出动了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.47,0:03:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,S4？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.71,0:03:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Shooting Star Subaru Sama」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.86,0:03:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个浪岚学园以势力最大为傲
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.88,0:03:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫昴的地下粉丝会
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.02,0:03:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人狂热的粉丝
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.50,0:03:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定会嫉妒你们的关系放刺客过来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.67,0:03:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.59,0:03:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请放心
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.16,0:03:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们「用温暖的目光守护昴大人会」已经为您击退了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.45,0:03:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.79,0:03:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从S4分裂出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.30,0:03:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于想法不同所以和那边正在暗地里争斗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.14,0:04:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.60,0:04:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只希望你能告诉我…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.30,0:04:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是攻谁是受…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.96,0:04:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腐女吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.69,0:04:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了不少苦头呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.65,0:04:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不是都因为你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.63,0:04:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了表示歉意…给你这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.41,0:04:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs22\fad(0,100)}（管家券 撕掉的话可以命令昴一次）
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.99,0:04:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.40,0:04:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(250,323)\fs20}hitsuji
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.40,0:04:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(308,323)\fs20}sitsuji
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.40,0:04:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羊和管家的双关
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.04,0:04:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要用了这个 你就能命令昴一次
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.13,0:04:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命令…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.37,0:04:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.79,0:04:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上半身脱光 一边往胸部上抹蜂蜜一边…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.36,0:04:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.42,0:04:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然的话就是这样那样之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.73,0:04:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.22,0:04:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.75,0:04:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.24,0:04:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.34,0:04:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我舔…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.36,0:04:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没有那么愉快的嗜好！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.75,0:05:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那放学后再见咯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.56,0:05:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食欲都没了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.51,0:05:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢 为什么是游戏中心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.17,0:05:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次约会嘛 我觉得这样刚刚好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.20,0:05:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.10,0:05:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了治好你的女性恐惧症
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.86,0:05:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想最好就是去适应普通的女生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.74,0:05:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你在哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.85,0:05:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在附近的漫咖看漫画
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.87,0:05:38.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是悠闲的身份啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.91,0:05:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换昴听电话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.23,0:05:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.60,0:05:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么昴 「脱掉」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.68,0:05:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.92,0:05:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.52,0:05:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没叫你在此时此地脱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.04,0:05:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去换衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.65,0:06:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别那样盯着看！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.17,0:06:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像胸也变大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.69,0:06:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为平时缠着布
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.70,0:06:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且今天大小姐准备了带胸垫的胸罩
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.04,0:06:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊 好像是没这么大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.30,0:06:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在回想什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.24,0:06:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱…抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.24,0:06:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.22,0:06:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.72,0:06:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.06,0:06:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把钱放进去然后有技巧地抓玩偶的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.88,0:06:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.31,0:06:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我帮你拿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.35,0:06:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.99,0:07:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.95,0:07:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs22}（第一次拍大头贴）\N（昴 近次郎）
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.42,0:07:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.68,0:07:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.57,0:07:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.58,0:07:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是为了治疗你才来的 我却玩得那么开心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.81,0:07:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.22,0:07:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底为什么这么怕女生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.12,0:07:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道坂町朱美吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.50,0:07:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是个职业女摔跤手…别名「鲜血的女王」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.25,0:07:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人…是我的妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.46,0:07:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不止是妈妈 连妹妹都非常喜欢格斗技
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.53,0:07:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从小时候起就作为她们两个的沙包
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.41,0:07:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十多年来天天被虐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.11,0:07:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是结果
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.67,0:07:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又为什么会流鼻血啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.41,0:08:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是成习惯了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.00,0:08:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流了鼻血就不会继续被虐了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.51,0:08:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是家人的温柔呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.11,0:08:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不对
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.67,0:08:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是因为会弄脏房间
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.93,0:08:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 肯定能治好的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.27,0:08:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我也想快点治好这病
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.05,0:08:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治好后和女生接触！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.21,0:08:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备活动还顺利吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.41,0:08:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.70,0:08:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那开始任务的第二阶段
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.88,0:08:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐的指令来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.94,0:08:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.26,0:08:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,程序1
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.99,0:09:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,程序2
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.80,0:09:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.20,0:09:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.59,0:09:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.29,0:09:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换次郎同学接
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.94,0:09:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 还没流鼻血吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.52,0:09:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还 还好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.31,0:09:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那作为奖励可以用掉管家券哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.52,0:09:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咩
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.96,0:09:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你会拿着那个！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.07,0:09:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.73,0:09:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您有什么吩咐吗 主人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.88,0:09:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.86,0:09:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}主人 主人…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.58,0:09:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我不喜欢服侍大小姐以外的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.21,0:09:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.58,0:09:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管家券和大小姐的命令是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.72,0:10:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管家券是绝对的命令呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.13,0:10:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了！ 无论是什么事您只管吩咐！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.48,0:10:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.78,0:10:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我不是那种变态！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.98,0:10:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 你试着说下「咩～」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.16,0:10:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咩…咩…咩～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.84,0:10:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽可能命令了简单的事 却感觉做了不该做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.90,0:10:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 因为我是主人的管家
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.96,0:10:45.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已 已经可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.54,0:10:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 主人 您头上有灰尘
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.46,0:10:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.80,0:10:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然哆哆嗦嗦地抖成这样 是冷吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.35,0:10:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不让我来温暖您吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.58,0:11:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平胸 是最佳角度
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.83,0:11:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奏小姐 LOVE
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.94,0:11:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.28,0:11:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽 你在这种地方做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.29,0:11:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的台词！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.57,0:11:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说哥哥在和男生交往
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.73,0:11:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很担心所以从早上跟到现在了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.38,0:11:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟踪我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.19,0:11:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后没想到…你竟然有这种秘密！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.75,0:11:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.40,0:11:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到前辈竟然是有女装癖的变态！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.64,0:11:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.91,0:11:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.87,0:11:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如哥哥送玩偶给女装的前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.60,0:11:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还互相将身体紧紧挨着
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.51,0:12:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后…明明都是男人还想接吻吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.12,0:12:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从你来家里接哥哥的时候我就觉得奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.64,0:12:10.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在色诱我哥哥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.82,0:12:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.90,0:12:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这只狐狸精
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.18,0:12:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我的哥哥 还给我！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.81,0:12:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.15,0:12:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算…什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.67,0:12:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样…这样是犯规的啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.24,0:12:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是意外的结局啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.74,0:12:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.28,0:12:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都看到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.66,0:12:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么有趣的事 没有理由错过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.12,0:12:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我并没有打算那么用力踢的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.23,0:12:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.47,0:12:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不那么做的话 是阻止不了红羽的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.29,0:12:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.63,0:13:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么明天学校见
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.84,0:13:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.55,0:13:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 红羽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.75,0:13:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经回来了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.01,0:13:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熊 熊五郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.28,0:13:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我不在的时候 一直是你担任红羽的沙包吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.09,0:13:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.22,0:13:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过红羽那家伙 受了相当大的打击啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.31,0:13:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.06,0:13:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹的误会 还没有解开吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.10,0:14:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是前途堪忧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.59,0:14:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么换上体操服之后 男生都去保健室
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.57,0:14:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.41,0:14:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有照做了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.84,0:14:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是体检啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.72,0:14:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要检查身体的各个部位的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.77,0:14:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 大小姐却…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.49,0:14:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然去年说突然生病让你请假了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.68,0:14:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但今年就两个人一起渡过难关吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.53,0:14:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题吧 昴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.96,0:14:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直是在这里换衣服的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.57,0:14:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.60,0:14:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然我怎么想都觉得行不通啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.38,0:14:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.97,0:14:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的 我做给你看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.43,0:14:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身高 体重 座高
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.73,0:14:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到这里虽然没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.83,0:15:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,测胸围很不妙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.63,0:15:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的 布比平时缠得更多
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.34,0:15:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般都不会缠的吧 那种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.71,0:15:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总能蒙混过去的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.51,0:15:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个 近卫昴同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.59,0:15:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.56,0:15:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.98,0:15:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请拿掉 不能好好测了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.74,0:15:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看招
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.72,0:15:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女生？ 近卫是女生？！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.21,0:15:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请等一下 近卫他 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.43,0:15:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他相当怕生人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.55,0:15:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来测近卫的胸围！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.44,0:15:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.89,0:15:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂 坂町
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.99,0:16:01.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,7…78公分
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.44,0:16:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂町 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.20,0:16:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个 坂町近次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.54,0:16:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不妙了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.15,0:16:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么今年是护士
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.62,0:16:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明一直都是男医生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.19,0:16:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的胸围由我来测
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.20,0:16:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请让我来测
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.14,0:16:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的话 已经有点习惯了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.48,0:16:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.20,0:16:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.63,0:16:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我才是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.35,0:16:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,视力听力倒没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.02,0:16:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 在那之后是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.73,0:16:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 把胸露出来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.19,0:16:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你缠着什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.81,0:16:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我拿掉！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.88,0:16:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个 近卫昴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.62,0:16:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 把胸露出来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.81,0:16:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来给近卫放听诊器
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.25,0:17:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也太说不过去了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.06,0:17:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.26,0:17:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要渡过这个难关的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.43,0:17:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好软…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.96,0:17:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.99,0:17:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.35,0:17:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体检呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.93,0:17:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,托你的福 逃掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.72,0:17:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.12,0:17:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没有坚持到最后有点不甘心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.06,0:17:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐听说我们互测胸围的事好像很满足
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.07,0:17:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传闻又增加了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.83,0:17:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午休吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.70,0:17:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 可以的话 一起吃午饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.72,0:17:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是想要和你一起吃午饭哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.68,0:18:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我请你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.69,0:18:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为不想欠你人情
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.43,0:18:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巧克力卷和 炒面面包
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.55,0:18:10.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有可乐饼面包和 咖喱面包
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.37,0:18:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}还要炸猪肉串和炸肉饼外加草莓牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.09,0:18:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙居然对昴大人下手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.73,0:18:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个混蛋眼镜男
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.54,0:18:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.22,0:18:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.47,0:18:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体检的时候也表现得很亲热的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.66,0:18:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是一直在玩扮医生游戏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.50,0:18:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.57,0:18:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 快点买
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.56,0:18:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干吗 快坐下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.59,0:18:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.86,0:18:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说来 凉月呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.27,0:18:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 别无视我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.37,0:18:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直和别人这样吃饭吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.18,0:18:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 和黑濑一起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.94,0:19:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那家伙从初中起就一直在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.89,0:19:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初中吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.84,0:19:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有去过 不是很了解
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.48,0:19:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和大小姐都是从高中开始上学的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.22,0:19:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前只是在学校挂名
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.18,0:19:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后请家庭教师来上课的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.72,0:19:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以没有和别人一起吃过午饭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.15,0:19:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你一样 和朋友一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.54,0:19:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么首先从叫名字开始
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.12,0:19:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫还没有好好叫过我的名字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.78,0:19:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以叫次郎就好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.61,0:19:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.37,0:19:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.36,0:19:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 像朋友一样叫名字
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.81,0:19:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.64,0:19:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.61,0:19:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起「咩」这样叫简单多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.57,0:19:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 那么我叫了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.76,0:20:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次…次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.70,0:20:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不是不错吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.37,0:20:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎 次郎吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.77,0:20:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼻血 不是没有出来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.97,0:20:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是任务有一点成果了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.73,0:20:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.38,0:20:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.08,0:20:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴会在别人的身边睡着
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.22,0:20:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是因为紧张得以放松了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.62,0:20:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧张？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.02,0:20:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道什么时候秘密会暴露
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.59,0:20:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以在学校一直紧绷神经 不让任何人靠近身边
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.43,0:20:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 终于找到了能成为朋友的人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.72,0:20:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.27,0:20:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是因为你知道她的秘密 所以才能成为朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.35,0:20:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子也用自己的方式努力了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.21,0:21:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是昴的主人 不是这孩子能从心底当作朋友的人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.91,0:21:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然以前都叫我小奏 关系也很好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.31,0:21:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.34,0:21:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.21,0:21:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.27,0:21:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 问你一件事可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.97,0:21:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.80,0:21:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥和近卫前辈在交往吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.44,0:21:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 那家伙只是普通的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.80,0:21:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.99,0:21:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…有喜欢的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.05,0:21:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这样的感觉还是第一次 怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.06,0:21:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢的对象难道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.47,0:21:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥的朋友…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.24,0:21:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫前辈虽然怪怪的 可是又强又帅
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.21,0:21:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好喜欢他
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.90,0:22:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了 天国的老爸
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.84,0:22:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的女儿 喜欢上了女孩子啊
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.33,0:23:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽妹妹 知道最能让女孩子幸福的地方是哪里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.76,0:23:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是擂台上
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.36,0:23:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽妹妹答错了哦 让姐姐告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.20,0:23:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.24,0:23:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是爽得要叫出声的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.55,0:24:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是擂台上啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.72,0:24:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集「迷茫管家与懦弱的我」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.21,0:24:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第3话 「当然 是在床上」


