[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-02-27 14:20:20
; // 版本: 0.74
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:STAR DRIVER 輝きのタクト
Original Script:shinjico@popgo
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes


[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.8,0.4,2,10,10,8,1
Style: note1,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,21,&H000FE3DE,&H00FFFFFF,&H000F0F0F,&H001C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: note2,FZZhunYuan-M02,26,&H00213A3D,&H00FFFFFF,&H00C9E2E2,&H00F3F3F3,-1,0,0,0,90,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title,@FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H1E4BC2D3,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,85,100,2,-90.00,1,1,0,7,30,30,10,1
Style: staff,FZZhunYuan-M02,24,&H00EBEBEB,&H00000000,&H28000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,15,15,10,1
Style: OPCN1,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,25,&H00FAFAFA,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H28000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: EDCN1,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00A71ADD,&H1E941471,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,4,1
Style: OPCN2,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,24,&H00FAFAFA,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,6,1
Style: EDCN2,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00F02015,&H1E380118,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,4,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.18,0:00:21.79,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(900,0)\pos(733,342)\blur6\fs36}（画中彩虹）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.17,0:24:02.28,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(600,600)\pos(424,12)\fsp-1\fs22}翻译：晶晶电脑   AKIRA
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.29,0:24:06.57,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(600,600)\pos(424,12)\fsp-1\fs22}后期：SHINJICO  X  SHINJICO
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.61,0:24:11.47,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(600,600)\pos(424,12)\fs22}漫游字幕组\N{\fsp-1\fnArial\fs18\b0}http://popgo.net/bbs
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------OPCN2-----------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.80,0:01:08.32,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}仰望天空 广阔梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.38,0:01:12.26,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}打开未来的门扉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.39,0:01:19.26,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}此刻依然无限光芒照耀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.06,0:01:29.57,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}明朗的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.62,0:01:34.03,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}打开窗便有阳光洒下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.15,0:01:36.57,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}微风拂过
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.68,0:01:40.51,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}拭去昨日的泪水
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.57,0:01:44.00,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}寂寞之时
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.08,0:01:47.77,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}总是寻找着看不见的星星
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.85,0:01:51.15,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}不知它近在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.20,0:01:56.40,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}依然不断追求
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.46,0:01:57.78,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}（you are the shining star）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.80,0:02:01.29,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}仰望天空 广阔梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.35,0:02:05.23,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}打开未来的门扉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.33,0:02:11.86,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}此刻依然无限光芒照耀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.94,0:02:15.37,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}星空闪烁的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.47,0:02:19.40,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}不计其数的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.48,0:02:25.73,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}如今依然等待着你去实现
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.77,0:02:30.44,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}所以迈步前进吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------EDCN2-----------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.14,0:22:29.09,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}决心不会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.16,0:22:31.56,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}无论多少次
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.63,0:22:34.77,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,400)\be1}都能重新起跑
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.89,0:22:48.40,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}轻飘飘地随风飘扬
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.53,0:22:52.58,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}飒爽而来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.64,0:22:56.40,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}若只想消磨时间
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.41,0:23:00.30,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}就给我认真点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.38,0:23:03.20,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}黑白的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.26,0:23:08.00,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}你应该也早已厌倦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.13,0:23:11.86,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}被弄脏也不会放手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.95,0:23:18.36,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}紧拥着唯一的自尊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.45,0:23:20.30,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}梦想不会就此终结
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.32,0:23:22.00,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}你依然保持本色
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.10,0:23:26.19,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}随时都可以重生
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.28,0:23:30.81,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}摄人心魄的疯狂刺激
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.92,0:23:33.98,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}才能拯救爱 woo
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.02,0:23:36.12,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}决心不会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.21,0:23:37.74,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}谁也无法破坏
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.79,0:23:42.11,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}给人添麻烦又如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.14,0:23:43.92,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}想要继续呐喊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.03,0:23:46.31,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}无论多少次
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.44,0:23:49.56,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}都能重新起跑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.80,0:23:54.43,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}「想要的只是时代的一页」
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------PREV------------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.61,0:00:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久没看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.95,0:00:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 其实常见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.50,0:00:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,素体Qophlite（针孔）的复原很完美
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.54,0:00:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明知有生命危险却毫不迟疑地投入复原程序
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.93,0:00:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话我很佩服你们
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.52,0:00:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,窗之星的素体到底在耽搁什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.83,0:00:44.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Heigent（窗）正在协助进行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.24,0:00:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所开发系统的实证试验
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.80,0:00:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是能打赢Tauburn的新玩具
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.44,0:00:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几时才能玩？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.66,0:01:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到最终调整结束至少还要一周
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.82,0:01:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.21,0:01:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽量快点哦
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------TXTA------------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.62,0:02:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.22,0:02:55.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解除零时到外面的瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.66,0:03:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这岛遭受核攻击的可能性也是有的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.69,0:03:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据科学协会的计算
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.03,0:03:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,素体足以抵御核攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.17,0:03:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是那时没有驯化素体的人怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.51,0:03:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.18,0:03:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打破皆水巫女封印的瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.31,0:03:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事先驯化素体比较安全啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.85,0:03:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最保险的做法是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.51,0:03:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驾驶素体的我亲自打破皆水封印
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.48,0:03:33.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以现在第三阶段的状态走出零时之外
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.45,0:03:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也能将世界掌握在我们手中吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.50,0:03:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海德的秘密也太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.49,0:03:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逆日死之巫女是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.65,0:03:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不能告诉我们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.86,0:03:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到秘密是彼此彼此吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.21,0:03:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前我和驼之星你玩过飞镖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.43,0:03:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说你们曾经用飞镖决定战斗顺序
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.81,0:04:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明明那么厉害却为何总是会输
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.27,0:04:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这点真令人想不通啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.01,0:04:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.60,0:04:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为害怕素体复原程序的风险
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.96,0:04:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以故意输的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.84,0:04:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有证据就怀疑同伴可不好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.83,0:04:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒也是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.06,0:04:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.36,0:04:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅我吧 驼之星
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.69,0:04:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种笑法
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.84,0:04:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那时相比你还是一点也没变
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.99,0:04:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.28,0:04:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字是津名志时生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.68,0:04:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.20,0:04:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片城龙助
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.67,0:04:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙助吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.35,0:05:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我们的婚约是父母决定
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.30,0:05:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是每天都来接我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.27,0:05:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是耿直啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.15,0:05:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的名字叫空
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.71,0:05:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时在大学研究室工作的我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.60,0:05:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经参加了岛上地下遗迹的机密研究计划
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.06,0:05:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而 那工作也是父母给的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.85,0:05:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.57,0:05:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.28,0:05:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么漂亮的彩虹 我第一次见
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.94,0:06:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可真棒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.55,0:06:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想总算雨停了 就出来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.78,0:06:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟能看到如此美丽的彩虹呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.99,0:06:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加在画上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.37,0:06:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次看到那幅画时的情景
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.04,0:06:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我至今依然历历在目
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.35,0:06:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一瞬间就被迷住了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.35,0:06:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此后我一有时间就会去时生那里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.54,0:06:48.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 要找到在岛上四处出没的他还真不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.85,0:06:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.62,0:06:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是这个岛上夕阳最美丽的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.77,0:06:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绘画真好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.80,0:07:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能将这瞬间的记忆留存到永远
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.92,0:07:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,津名志时生君
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.58,0:07:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的签名为什么是R？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.28,0:07:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的雅号
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.42,0:07:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是未来的名字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.67,0:07:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.79,0:07:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能让空小姐当我的模特？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.17,0:07:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那份美丽有永久保留的价值
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.08,0:07:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 拓人少爷
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.07,0:07:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你做这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.27,0:07:33.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.03,0:07:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是食客嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.80,0:07:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听凭差遣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.16,0:07:48.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是和子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.35,0:07:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她好像从小就很喜欢那里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.15,0:07:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经常在那里午睡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.66,0:07:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像猫一样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.69,0:08:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.94,0:08:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是三年级的椋学长吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.85,0:08:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周日也要学习？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.03,0:08:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化学实验部的部长大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.38,0:08:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.77,0:08:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姜汁汽水
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.29,0:08:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.47,0:08:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绮罗星
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.96,0:08:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绮罗星
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.68,0:08:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是第三队九重葛的代表「沉醉」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.11,0:09:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放逐时代的驼之星吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.02,0:09:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.28,0:09:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有空不都是附身在动物身上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.35,0:09:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在岛上四处晃悠的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.57,0:09:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的第一阶段你自然是了若指掌嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.11,0:09:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.70,0:09:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前擅自使用了Heigent吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.52,0:09:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想来海德一直很纵容你的行动
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.30,0:09:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 他对我有意思吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.06,0:09:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也有印记
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.38,0:09:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要想想你是剩下的哪台素体的驭星者
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.09,0:09:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就大致知道你的身份了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.67,0:09:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密总比自己想象的暴露得快吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.68,0:09:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海德为什么不接触你的封印？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.41,0:09:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逆日死之巫女小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.58,0:09:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时机未到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.77,0:10:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是医院的设备比较完备…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.44,0:10:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 要以防万一
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.81,0:10:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爱她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.18,0:10:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.86,0:10:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下要不要三人一起上街玩去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.88,0:10:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然有秘密组织
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.60,0:10:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,企图暗中复活岛下发现的奥利哈康素体
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.55,0:11:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为外人的你怎么知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.95,0:11:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你还是其成员之一
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.76,0:11:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继承家族代代相传的印记而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.85,0:11:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的一生不过是顺着铺好的轨道走下去罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.56,0:11:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真羡慕自由的你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.13,0:11:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有一切的人反而嫉妒一无所有的人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.28,0:11:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家本也有印记
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.35,0:11:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲却不让我这个独生子继承
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.89,0:11:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的爱她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.20,0:11:41.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空可是对你…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.99,0:11:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时生所描绘的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.31,0:11:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我从未察觉的现实之美的精确结晶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.51,0:11:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能画出这种画的时生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.80,0:12:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却执着于地下遗迹的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.87,0:12:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我觉得很怪异
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.70,0:12:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他本想成为奥利哈康素体的共生能力者
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.26,0:12:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那并非希望就能实现
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.35,0:12:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.22,0:12:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那眼袋是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.49,0:12:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是牧羽信悟
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.07,0:12:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他似乎愿意把印记给我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.18,0:12:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.84,0:12:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.09,0:12:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了岛上传承的王与巫女的印记外
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.45,0:12:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该都可以随持有者的意识转移继承
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.13,0:12:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种东西 时生想要就给你好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.22,0:12:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不觉间他找到了印记的持有者
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.26,0:13:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至约定了继承
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.24,0:13:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我惊讶于他的手段之高
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.92,0:13:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.68,0:13:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天起我就不是时生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.74,0:13:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是雅令治了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.27,0:13:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反应周期变短
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.06,0:13:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎快要觉醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.04,0:13:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.88,0:13:35.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海德也害怕素体复原的风险
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.52,0:13:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以从信悟那里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.74,0:13:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继承新的印记和素体之前
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.71,0:13:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不肯让阶段提前
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.91,0:13:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 不都是为了他自己方便
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.20,0:13:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 打破皆水封印不需要等待
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.57,0:14:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------TXTB------------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.96,0:14:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.36,0:14:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是 岛上我最中意的场所
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.50,0:14:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈还活着的时候 常来散步
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.23,0:14:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.45,0:14:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡拉OK的古式阿姨是？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.31,0:14:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.13,0:14:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.36,0:14:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.65,0:14:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我唱歌的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.85,0:14:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的有替我保密
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.97,0:14:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长和须方和子他们从小认识吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.21,0:14:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们俩…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.84,0:14:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 还是算了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.77,0:14:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.29,0:14:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们从小就亲密无间
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.69,0:15:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿时经常一起玩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.89,0:15:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我都挺好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.73,0:15:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我时常觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.15,0:15:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己莫非是个碍事的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.29,0:15:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.41,0:15:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.87,0:15:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被蝮蛇咬了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.86,0:15:35.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.75,0:15:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打完血清就没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.86,0:15:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.14,0:15:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,零时空间？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.72,0:16:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拓人的样子有古怪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.67,0:16:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驯化
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.40,0:16:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星剑 珊瑚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.87,0:17:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的身体看你能坚持多久
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.25,0:17:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来 刚才的蝮蛇是驼之星的一阶能力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.85,0:17:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思啦 Tauburn
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.03,0:17:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.42,0:17:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分离攻击？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.44,0:17:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.19,0:17:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皆水巫女我要了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.99,0:17:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和子！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.01,0:17:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一阶的攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.76,0:17:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对第三阶的素体行不通
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.41,0:17:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想打破皆水封印？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.35,0:17:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,针之星
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.68,0:17:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驯化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.99,0:17:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.89,0:17:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和子！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.21,0:17:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.88,0:18:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Qophlight
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.64,0:18:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思 针之星
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.42,0:18:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还要问你呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.11,0:18:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,窗之星的素体还未复原
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.07,0:18:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许擅自解除零时空间
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.93,0:18:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内讧吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.52,0:18:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.90,0:18:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,It's a chance
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.54,0:18:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 针之星
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.24,0:18:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 不好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.36,0:18:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银河之光啊 集于此身
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.75,0:18:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪耀流星
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.18,0:18:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Tauburn
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.85,0:18:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞弹
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.77,0:19:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一群蠢货
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.84,0:19:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 好了 拓人君
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.60,0:19:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拓人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.59,0:19:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精神一好就胡闹
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.53,0:19:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好凉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.07,0:19:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和子也来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.70,0:19:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别 Stop Stop
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.74,0:19:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浑身湿透
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.26,0:19:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.89,0:19:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～好凉快
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.83,0:19:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陷入了沉睡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.82,0:20:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明约定把印记转让于我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.96,0:20:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信悟却逃入了梦乡
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.42,0:20:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时生相当在意那个男人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.66,0:20:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢他的画
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.12,0:20:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也喜欢作画时的他
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.84,0:20:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.06,0:20:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的他被野心占据
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.12,0:20:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想其他
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.12,0:20:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,画也好 你也好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.46,0:20:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近常想
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.65,0:20:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们三人的关系为什么不能更融洽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.50,0:20:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么发展成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.75,0:20:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.33,0:20:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有孩子了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.31,0:20:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时生并没有变
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.57,0:20:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从遇见他当初到现在都没有变
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.52,0:20:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少相比于你…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.47,0:21:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从没在乎过我不是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.43,0:21:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.76,0:21:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.55,0:21:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没骗你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.98,0:21:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空不久后就离开岛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.02,0:21:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出生的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.09,0:21:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被托付给时生的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.91,0:21:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而她的去向 至今不明
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.13,0:21:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我的印记给你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.56,0:21:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种力量 我不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.26,0:21:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这份力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.35,0:21:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从最初就看清了你和空的事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.00,0:21:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.95,0:21:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想方设法不看到
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.89,0:22:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以一只眼睛成了这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.57,0:22:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说马上会苏醒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.38,0:22:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件事 总想不起来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.02,0:22:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空是几时离开岛上的？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.82,0:22:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然你的心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.04,0:22:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也已被零时空间禁锢
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------NEXT------------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.55,0:24:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绮罗星十字团科学公会制造了超阶系统
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.20,0:24:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以让素体超越第三阶的状态
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.09,0:24:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是极具威胁的新兵器
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.25,0:24:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集 驭星者
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.58,0:24:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欲望的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.98,0:24:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的银河 已然闪耀
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------TVCM------------------------------------


