[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成 2011-03-06 15:30:33
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:MM!06
Original Script:澄空×华盟
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H32000000,&HB4000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,5,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,7,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE3,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,8,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFGCraftYu-W5,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00A11419,&H967A0D11,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,20,20,5,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H005B12E3,&H965C13B7,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,10,25,5,1
Style: NEXT,华康少女文字W5(P),28,&H3C001698,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H50000000,&H50FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC2,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,1,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------STAFF------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.39,0:03:01.38,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}翻译: 艾哀 天地有正气　校对: TurtleIzzy　打杂: HySauce、魔动小贤、9416-kun
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.39,0:03:01.38,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20\fad(300,300)}澄空学园×华盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.24,0:02:50.49,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}我家大骚动
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.24,0:02:50.49,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}我家大骚动
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.24,0:02:50.49,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}我家大骚动
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.58,0:01:17.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.20,0:01:21.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.67,0:01:26.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.00,0:01:32.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこの迷えるオマエ　悲壮感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.67,0:01:37.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すがるワラも見捨てりゃ　それもしょーがないか？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.01,0:01:42.41,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,運命は今日も（迷走）イジワルだから（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.49,0:01:48.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめてわたしが　味方してたい何かできるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.74,0:01:51.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.32,0:01:53.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まかせてみて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.47,0:01:55.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.67,0:02:00.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ギリギリの線じゃヌルい　破滅しちゃってゼロってそんで？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.43,0:02:05.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,かたくななDNA　ムリは禁物
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.13,0:02:07.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強制終了5秒前（寸前）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.47,0:02:09.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生まれかわれそうな予感？（全然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.71,0:02:14.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現場主義更生させちゃえばGo to へブン
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.49,0:02:19.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ウムを言わさず　あの手この手で
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.18,0:02:23.06,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今すぐ正してあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.12,0:02:27.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと存在感以上に気になるフォーリンラブ未満が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.56,0:02:32.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情けない顔してほっとけないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.47,0:02:36.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生観変えるような出会いしたんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.73,0:02:41.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あとはされるがまま　流されちゃえばいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.90,0:02:44.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へ！ル！プ！いくよ！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.58,0:01:17.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.20,0:01:21.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.67,0:01:26.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.00,0:01:32.59,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的迷途小羔羊　满是悲壮感的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.67,0:01:37.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连救命稻草都不要了　这也是无可奈何的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.01,0:01:42.41,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为今天的命运也在（横冲直撞）刁难人（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.49,0:01:48.22,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我想　成为你的伙伴帮你一把
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.74,0:01:51.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.32,0:01:53.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.47,0:01:55.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.67,0:02:00.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,极限的界线太温和　全部毁灭归零会怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.43,0:02:05.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顽固的DNA　勉强是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.13,0:02:07.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在强制结束5秒之前（迫在眉睫）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.47,0:02:09.69,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是有脱胎换骨的预感？（完全没有）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.71,0:02:14.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改改你的现场主义就能Go to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.49,0:02:19.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论有无　就让我用尽手段
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.18,0:02:23.06,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就让你走上正途
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.12,0:02:27.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点超出存在感让人在意的恋人未满
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.56,0:02:32.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一脸可怜的样子让人无法置之不理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.47,0:02:36.59,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这已是改变人生观的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.73,0:02:41.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后只要任凭摆布　随波逐流就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.90,0:02:44.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,HE! L! P!开始吧!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.29,0:21:22.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.36,0:21:25.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.54,0:21:28.21,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.27,0:21:30.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.94,0:21:36.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.08,0:21:37.45,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.47,0:21:41.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}それとも…いいの？ よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.48,0:21:46.23,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.32,0:21:46.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.77,0:21:48.06,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.06,0:21:49.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.37,0:21:51.97,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.00,0:21:53.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}愛には恋は緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.37,0:21:56.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}純情文武両立させて insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.91,0:21:59.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.39,0:22:03.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}嫌われてもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.27,0:22:09.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.12,0:22:14.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}どうして？ そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.08,0:22:16.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.54,0:22:19.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.72,0:22:21.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.84,0:22:24.45,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめて達成しなくちゃ　胸、痛い。
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.48,0:22:30.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}とにかく気持ちが止まらないの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.19,0:22:32.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.38,0:22:35.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめて挑戦したいよ　したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.43,0:22:38.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.12,0:22:40.80,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.84,0:22:47.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}だって特別キミは特別…押して！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.29,0:21:22.34,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.36,0:21:25.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少为达成目的也要不择手段？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.54,0:21:28.21,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸气呼气这是告白的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.27,0:21:30.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}但我一直无法安心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.94,0:21:36.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}那个一定是特别的…万岁！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.08,0:21:37.45,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}靠近一点…会讨厌吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.47,0:21:41.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}还是说…可以？ 一进一退背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.48,0:21:46.23,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}恐怖和笑容说不定很像 靠近围观我很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.32,0:21:46.72,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}是吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.77,0:21:48.06,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}爱和恋我都不擅长应付
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.06,0:21:49.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}纯情单方片面的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.37,0:21:51.97,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}商量和子弹 da-dan-da down load 对啦！对啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.00,0:21:53.34,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}爱和恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.37,0:21:56.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}纯情的文武双全 insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.91,0:21:59.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我想做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.39,0:22:03.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}就算被讨厌也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.27,0:22:09.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}在我的眼中你是如此耀眼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.12,0:22:14.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}为什么？ 对啦…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.08,0:22:16.52,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}但是请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.54,0:22:19.69,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}只有一个位子所以要不择手段！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.72,0:22:21.76,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.84,0:22:24.45,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少也要达到目的 胸口好疼。
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.48,0:22:30.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}总而言之我的心意已经无法阻挡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.19,0:22:32.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.38,0:22:35.40,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少想挑战一下 挑战一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.43,0:22:38.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸气这是同意的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.12,0:22:40.80,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}答应想要安心的我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.84,0:22:47.76,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}因为是特别的你 就让我特别地…推倒你！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.25,0:00:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎不管怎么看都这么帅啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.39,0:00:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住啦 亲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.49,0:00:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 正到好时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.26,0:00:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野岚子！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.58,0:00:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小测验复习了吗？加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.95,0:00:46.70,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(242,150)\frz3}早上好太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.95,0:00:46.70,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(211,280)\frz3}小测验复习了吗？加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.97,0:00:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是哪根葱啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.75,0:00:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.72,0:00:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来想和太郎一起度过清晨的休憩时光的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.26,0:00:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.02,0:00:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全是岚子的邮件
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.69,0:01:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道她盯上太郎了！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.39,0:01:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静香
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.31,0:01:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.73,0:01:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要阻止
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.11,0:01:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.87,0:02:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了可不算完 你这条蛆虫
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.24,0:02:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个超M三等兵
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.86,0:03:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,匍匐前进的时候你笑个毛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.44,0:03:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让我把你干掉么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.15,0:03:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,办不到的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.81,0:03:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么办不到的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.82,0:03:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要通过军训练成不输于超M体质的精神力
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.74,0:03:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的超M体质就画上句号了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.07,0:03:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是本小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.96,0:03:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看个毛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.51,0:03:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以侮辱长官罪送你上军事法庭去！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.16,0:03:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我重新来过
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.45,0:03:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 别让长官大人等你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.11,0:03:43.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快给我爬到地上滚过来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.02,0:03:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算这么说…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.61,0:03:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这地雷阵是怎么回事啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.03,0:03:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许顶嘴！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.77,0:03:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛆虫！猪虫！猪太郎虫！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.14,0:03:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎虫…太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.37,0:04:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 蔑视污秽的我的那眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.51,0:04:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是到达终点的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.27,0:04:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石动长官
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.82,0:04:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猪太郎平安无事地到达长官的玉足之下了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.46,0:04:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干的不错啊 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.32,0:04:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为奖励就用鞋底好好地践踏你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.08,0:04:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这土的味道让人真HIGH
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.80,0:04:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个变态混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.20,0:04:27.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就爽了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.96,0:04:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是无可救药的小虫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.47,0:04:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我就过去让您践踏
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.63,0:04:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.72,0:04:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶心死啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.07,0:04:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是虫子吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.67,0:04:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你莫非是想像着用你那肮脏的肚皮摩擦着地面
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.87,0:05:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爬到我的脚边的情景就会感到很兴奋？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.02,0:05:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜对了啊 真是的这孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.00,0:05:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我美绪大人的指尖 粘到了你的变态分泌液啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.96,0:05:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你的变态传染给我了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.29,0:05:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要怎么负责啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.85,0:05:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 一副像是到了极乐世界的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.43,0:05:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很恶心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.32,0:05:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太可悲了 可悲到我都无话可说了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.91,0:05:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这只大变态猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.06,0:05:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为你让我感到恶心的惩罚
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.95,0:05:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我做一千个俯卧撑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.85,0:05:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单单是俯卧撑太轻松了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.53,0:05:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚想到了一个正适合你的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.03,0:05:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我骑在你的背上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.56,0:05:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然以我的体重来说应该没什么意义
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.21,0:05:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这 这是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.38,0:06:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑马游戏？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.47,0:06:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.54,0:06:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁让你向前跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.95,0:06:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.98,0:06:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这只 劣马！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.78,0:06:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说也太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.52,0:06:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这么脏的地方还要特训
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.47,0:06:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是作战会议室
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.88,0:06:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卫生员！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.55,0:06:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.20,0:06:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 结野？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.46,0:06:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你穿成这样是？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.79,0:06:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.80,0:06:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到战场的天使那就是护士吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.60,0:06:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你要是不喜欢的话还是拒绝的好…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.77,0:06:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真没礼貌 好像人家逼她穿似的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.47,0:06:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…是我要穿的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.16,0:06:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.77,0:06:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直很憧憬护士服的…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.52,0:06:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我没有美绪学姐那么漂亮…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.89,0:06:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是很奇怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.31,0:07:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不会 没这回事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.50,0:07:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？合适吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.16,0:07:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我觉得不错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.22,0:07:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.53,0:07:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 合适吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.93,0:07:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很合适哦 在某种意义上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.28,0:07:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 态度是不是差太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.44,0:07:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过岚子护士真的很可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.96,0:07:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 给猪太郎治疗真是太浪费了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.49,0:07:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没这回事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.42,0:07:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那开始治疗了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.07,0:07:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.79,0:07:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.14,0:07:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生好可怕哦对不起！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.15,0:07:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.25,0:07:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 这次也失败了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.15,0:07:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这猪太郎到底想怎么样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.41,0:07:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经不行了…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.64,0:07:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个混蛋 给我咬紧牙关！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.51,0:08:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.99,0:08:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎么啦太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.43,0:08:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先去洗澡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.45,0:08:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把衣服脱了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.35,0:08:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来来快点快点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.88,0:08:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}行啦我自己会脱的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.65,0:08:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也脱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.00,0:08:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在干嘛啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.72,0:08:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起洗澡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.35,0:08:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可以一起洗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.30,0:08:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我出去！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.69,0:08:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎好过分哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.22,0:08:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目标物到手了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.20,0:08:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干的漂亮静香
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.99,0:08:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱的邮件检查
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.51,0:08:41.01,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be3}刚才真是对不起\N \N太郎 刚才真是对不起…\N我想快点把男性恐怖症治好\N就不会再打太郎了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.25,0:08:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.17,0:08:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是那个岚子啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.98,0:08:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎的邮件啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.48,0:09:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.79,0:09:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 谁会在这休息日上门啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.38,0:09:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.54,0:09:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来看你了哦 身体怎么样了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.09,0:09:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.54,0:09:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为我你才感冒了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.32,0:09:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.50,0:09:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.69,0:09:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是太郎不是发来邮件说…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.18,0:09:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邮件？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.16,0:09:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 太郎的朋友吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.84,0:09:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.30,0:09:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老姐 老妈！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.18,0:09:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎是我的东西！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.74,0:09:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点说你们是什么关系！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.26,0:09:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.82,0:10:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是让她们两个看到结野…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.64,0:10:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.48,0:10:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是太…不是…我是砂户太郎的同学结野岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.75,0:10:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次见面
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.30,0:10:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次见面
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.18,0:10:16.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎一直承蒙您照顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.32,0:10:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是太郎的妈妈智子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.25,0:10:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是太郎的姐姐静香
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.18,0:10:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教 结野同学
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.20,0:10:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎！？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.67,0:10:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这状况 到底是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.59,0:10:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.84,0:10:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干嘛呢 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.64,0:10:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点带结野同学进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.90,0:10:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.01,0:10:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.23,0:10:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.75,0:10:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地狱宅邸
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.00,0:11:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得 有点紧张啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.60,0:11:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.05,0:11:10.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么我能帮忙的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.26,0:11:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野就好好在旁休息吧 毕竟是客人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.74,0:11:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.50,0:11:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 帮我拿一下盘子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.71,0:11:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.52,0:11:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着也来帮我一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.45,0:11:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.55,0:11:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就行了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.52,0:11:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.30,0:11:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 帮我拿一下这个
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.05,0:11:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.48,0:11:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着交给我们就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.01,0:11:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 有什么事就叫我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.48,0:11:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.56,0:11:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好丰盛的料理
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.78,0:11:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 请吃得饱饱的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.49,0:11:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.03,0:11:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.38,0:11:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.81,0:11:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 太郎家里一直都这么丰盛吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.63,0:11:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.94,0:12:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来进行顺利呢 静香
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.29,0:12:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着进入第二阶段
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.15,0:12:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 结野同学
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.73,0:12:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用客气尽管吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.49,0:12:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.86,0:12:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.88,0:12:18.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.43,0:12:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能合结野同学的口味真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.62,0:12:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我因为一点也不会做料理 所以很是敬佩
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.64,0:12:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种程度的话很容易就能做到的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.40,0:12:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么什么 如果是平常的话 一旦和我的事扯上关系
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.64,0:12:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会进入超麻烦的白痴模式的两个人居然…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.41,0:12:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么下次一起做料理试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.86,0:12:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}本来以为会直接就把结野赶出去的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.58,0:12:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.85,0:12:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难以置信
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.18,0:12:46.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 结野和太郎是什么样的关系啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.90,0:12:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 和砂户同学是同一个班的 也是同一个社团的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.69,0:12:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也一起放学回家的…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.25,0:12:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野 那是地雷啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.40,0:13:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 就像是恋人一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.91,0:13:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说已经开始交往了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.26,0:13:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 还没有…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.17,0:13:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就是有这个打算了哦？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.31,0:13:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 这很符合常识的对话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.33,0:13:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像结野同学这样可爱的女生的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.66,0:13:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为家长也可以放心了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.15,0:13:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}这是做梦吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.11,0:13:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}不 难道说是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.14,0:13:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人终于觉醒成为普通的家人了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.82,0:13:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明一点也不悲伤 但是眼泪却止不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.44,0:13:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.35,0:13:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和面对玩偶时不一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.88,0:13:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉灵魂都要被带走了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.02,0:13:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然只能进入第三阶段了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.84,0:13:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有问题
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.00,0:14:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我一生都不会忘记今天这耀眼的一天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.41,0:14:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 结野 谢谢你 世界
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.08,0:14:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎真奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.37,0:14:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 请进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.44,0:14:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么情况
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.48,0:14:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 散乱成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.46,0:14:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个该怎么说呢 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.51,0:14:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.36,0:14:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽然不会做料理 但是很擅长打扫的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.20,0:14:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.19,0:14:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.95,0:14:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.71,0:14:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太 太郎难道是喜欢那种的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.72,0:14:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.41,0:14:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是喜欢肌肉我也不是很…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.54,0:14:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是误会
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.88,0:14:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有这种兴趣的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.63,0:15:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我没有搜集过这些东西的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.95,0:15:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红茶 冷了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.43,0:15:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要重泡一杯吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.76,0:15:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.57,0:15:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是对不起 很多方面上
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.20,0:15:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没这回事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.79,0:15:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.51,0:15:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.00,0:15:33.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和男生单独相处 对你来说很不舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.68,0:15:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有发觉到真是对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.27,0:15:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先回去下面吧 和老姐和老妈一起的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.20,0:15:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.97,0:15:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.42,0:15:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.86,0:15:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实啊 可能确实有些害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.69,0:15:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 已经没关系了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.37,0:16:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是太郎 所以没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.17,0:16:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 怎么了 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.51,0:16:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊 和男生独处的时候别说刚才的话比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.98,0:16:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.57,0:16:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什 什么为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.07,0:16:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但 但是如果是太郎的话 我…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.50,0:16:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.19,0:16:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 刚才那粉红色的气氛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.57,0:16:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是接吻寸前的气氛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.78,0:16:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.15,0:16:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第四阶段 解禁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.26,0:16:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野同学
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.09,0:16:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.28,0:16:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要比和太郎在一起的时间的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.75,0:16:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可比你要多得多
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.49,0:16:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的相册
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.10,0:16:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}看吧 这是刚出生的太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.90,0:16:57.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 很可爱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.66,0:16:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 很可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.08,0:17:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直叫着「姐姐」「姐姐」都没放开过手哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.99,0:17:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道这样的太郎的只有我们而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.43,0:17:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}快停下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.09,0:17:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说着「我是为了来见智子而出生的 I LOVE U」的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.56,0:17:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了「姐姐 长大了就结婚吧」的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.83,0:17:18.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 别捏造啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.36,0:17:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎可是最喜欢我的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.41,0:17:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说在前面 太郎出生后第一个碰触的女人可是我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.96,0:17:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都一把年纪了 该面对现实了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.33,0:17:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs18}给妈妈的\N锤肩券\N太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.57,0:17:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个如何 在母亲节太郎所给的锤肩券
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.81,0:17:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 在15岁生日时送的礼物项链
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.49,0:17:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷偷画的处女作搞笑漫画
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.18,0:17:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次买的黄书
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.45,0:17:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}静香 从刚才开始为什么一直和我较劲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.35,0:17:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的饶了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.24,0:17:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}这是我才要说的 第四阶段什么的见鬼去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.96,0:18:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 今天咱们净胡闹了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.50,0:18:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是在胡闹呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.18,0:18:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相册 有7册吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.95,0:18:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 就像小时候的每分每秒都被拍下了一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.92,0:18:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真让人羡慕
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.34,0:18:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来之后很快就明白了 太郎的家很温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.46,0:18:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很温暖？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.07,0:18:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 气氛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.86,0:18:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都和家人一起生活 给人这种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.92,0:18:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊 家人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.99,0:18:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.65,0:18:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.04,0:18:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听完能不笑我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.38,0:19:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.60,0:19:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.64,0:19:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 绝对的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.09,0:19:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我啊 有一个梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.97,0:19:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要长大以后 和最喜欢的人结婚 创建温馨的家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.69,0:19:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果 果然很奇怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.28,0:19:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明因为男性恐惧症而打男生的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.47,0:19:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.64,0:19:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.59,0:19:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点都不奇怪哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.96,0:19:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.28,0:19:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我这么说的 太郎是第一个
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.99,0:19:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.18,0:19:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 所以就是秘密了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.78,0:19:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只属于我们两人的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.09,0:19:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 替我和你妈妈她们问好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.43,0:19:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结 结野
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.70,0:19:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那明天见了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.03,0:20:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野同学真是个好孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.71,0:20:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为罪恶感 胸口就像快裂开了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.30,0:20:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 那是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.63,0:20:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.44,0:20:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.39,0:20:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.76,0:20:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就觉得奇怪啊 没想到居然做到这个地步
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.94,0:20:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 这就太不对了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.67,0:20:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.11,0:20:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跑 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.51,0:20:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小满老师
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.12,0:20:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 砂户太郎 反射性的把她们抓住了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.43,0:20:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说是你的家人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.86,0:20:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很可惜是的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.67,0:20:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 既年轻又美丽 真想拍摄啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.44,0:20:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.28,0:20:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随你喜欢 任你处置吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.32,0:21:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是校园泳衣配上眼镜也可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.86,0:21:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.78,0:21:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.93,0:21:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裸体围裙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.86,0:21:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.01,0:21:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.60,0:21:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户太郎 你现在实在太棒了
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.65,0:22:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.84,0:22:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈 你这身打扮是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.13,0:23:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于结野同学我们是知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.61,0:23:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是石动美绪这女生还是很让人在意
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.64,0:23:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连老姐都…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.85,0:23:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以下次就是潜入学校了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.21,0:23:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是早安之吻是最优先的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.17,0:23:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 早安之吻
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.31,0:23:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这俩家伙一点都没学乖
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.52,0:23:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了太郎的话什么都做得到哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.76,0:23:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是寂寞了 一起睡啊 裸体啊 上位什么的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.96,0:23:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是 为了太郎的话 一起洗澡 互相擦洗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.40,0:23:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我适可而止
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.77,0:23:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 最喜欢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.92,0:23:40.38,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.92,0:23:40.38,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.92,0:23:40.38,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.92,0:23:40.38,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,280)}盛夏的三角恋爱？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.92,0:23:40.38,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,280)}盛夏的三角恋爱？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.92,0:23:40.38,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,280)}盛夏的三角恋爱？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
