[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成 2011-05-02 22:08:13
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:MM!09
Original Script:澄空×华盟
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H32000000,&HB4000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,5,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,7,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE3,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,8,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFGCraftYu-W5,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00A11419,&H967A0D11,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,20,20,5,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H005B12E3,&H965C13B7,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,10,25,5,1
Style: NEXT,华康少女文字W5(P),28,&H3C001698,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H50000000,&H50FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC2,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,1,10,10,10,1
Style: INJP,DFGCraftYu-W5,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H005B12E3,&H965C13B7,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,15,20,5,1
Style: INCN,方正卡通简体,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H005B12E3,&H965C13B7,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,10,25,5,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------STAFF------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.72,0:02:30.98,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}翻译: 艾哀 天地有正气　校对: TurtleIzzy　打杂: バカばっかのHY、魔动小贤、9416-kun
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.72,0:02:30.98,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}澄空学园×华盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.72,0:02:30.98,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}MFC的华丽阴谋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.72,0:02:30.98,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}MFC的华丽阴谋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.72,0:02:30.98,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}MFC的华丽阴谋
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.23,0:00:57.80,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.85,0:01:02.19,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.32,0:01:07.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.65,0:01:13.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そこの迷えるオマエ　悲壮感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.32,0:01:18.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}すがるワラも見捨てりゃ　それもしょーがないか？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.66,0:01:23.06,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}運命は今日も（迷走）イジワルだから（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.14,0:01:28.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめてわたしが　味方してたい何かできるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.39,0:01:31.85,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}NO!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.97,0:01:34.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}まかせてみて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.12,0:01:36.28,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.32,0:01:40.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ギリギリの線じゃヌルい　破滅しちゃってゼロってそんで？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.08,0:01:45.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}かたくななDNA　ムリは禁物
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.78,0:01:48.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}強制終了5秒前（寸前）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.12,0:01:50.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}生まれかわれそうな予感？（全然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.36,0:01:55.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}現場主義更生させちゃえばGo to へブン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.14,0:01:59.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ウムを言わさず　あの手この手で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.83,0:02:03.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}今すぐ正してあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.77,0:02:08.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ちょっと存在感以上に気になるフォーリンラブ未満が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.21,0:02:13.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}情けない顔してほっとけないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.12,0:02:17.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}人生観変えるような出会いしたんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.38,0:02:22.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}あとはされるがまま　流されちゃえばいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.55,0:02:25.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}へ！ル！プ！いくよ！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.23,0:00:57.80,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.85,0:01:02.19,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.32,0:01:07.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.65,0:01:13.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}那边的迷途小羔羊　满是悲壮感的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.32,0:01:18.57,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}连救命稻草都不要了　这也是无可奈何的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.66,0:01:23.06,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}因为今天的命运也在（横冲直撞）刁难人（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.14,0:01:28.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少我想　成为你的伙伴帮你一把
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.39,0:01:31.85,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}NO!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.97,0:01:34.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}交给我试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.12,0:01:36.28,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.32,0:01:40.94,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}极限的界线太温和　全部毁灭归零会怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.08,0:01:45.72,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}顽固的DNA　勉强是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.78,0:01:48.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}在强制结束5秒之前（迫在眉睫）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.12,0:01:50.34,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}是不是有脱胎换骨的预感？（完全没有）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.36,0:01:55.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}改改你的现场主义就能Go to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.14,0:01:59.76,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}不论有无　就让我用尽手段
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.83,0:02:03.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}现在就让你走上正途
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.77,0:02:08.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}有点超出存在感让人在意的恋人未满
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.21,0:02:13.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}一脸可怜的样子让人无法置之不理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.12,0:02:17.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}因为这已是改变人生观的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.38,0:02:22.52,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}之后只要任凭摆布　随波逐流就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.55,0:02:25.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}HE! L! P!开始吧!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.99,0:21:59.04,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.06,0:22:02.17,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.24,0:22:04.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.97,0:22:07.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.64,0:22:12.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.78,0:22:14.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.17,0:22:18.16,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それとも…いいの？ よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.18,0:22:22.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.02,0:22:23.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.47,0:22:24.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.76,0:22:26.03,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.07,0:22:28.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.70,0:22:30.04,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛には恋は緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.07,0:22:33.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情文武両立させて insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.61,0:22:36.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.09,0:22:39.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌われてもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.97,0:22:46.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.82,0:22:50.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうして？ そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.78,0:22:53.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.24,0:22:56.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.42,0:22:58.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.54,0:23:01.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ　胸、痛い。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.18,0:23:06.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とにかく気持ちが止まらないの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.89,0:23:09.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.08,0:23:12.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて挑戦したいよ　したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.13,0:23:14.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.82,0:23:17.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.54,0:23:24.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって特別キミは特別…押して！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.99,0:21:59.04,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.06,0:22:02.17,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少为达成目的也要不择手段？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.24,0:22:04.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气呼气这是告白的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.97,0:22:07.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我一直无法安心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.64,0:22:12.70,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个一定是特别的…万岁！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.78,0:22:14.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠近一点…会讨厌吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.17,0:22:18.16,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说…可以？ 一进一退背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.18,0:22:22.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖和笑容说不定很像 靠近围观我很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.02,0:22:23.42,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.47,0:22:24.76,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋我都不擅长应付
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.76,0:22:26.03,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情单方片面的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.07,0:22:28.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商量和子弹 da-dan-da down load 对啦！对啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.70,0:22:30.04,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.07,0:22:33.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情的文武双全 insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.61,0:22:36.02,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.09,0:22:39.88,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被讨厌也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.97,0:22:46.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的眼中你是如此耀眼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.82,0:22:50.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？ 对啦…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.78,0:22:53.22,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.24,0:22:56.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一个位子所以要不择手段！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.42,0:22:58.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.54,0:23:01.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达到目的 胸口好疼。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.18,0:23:06.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总而言之我的心意已经无法阻挡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.89,0:23:09.02,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.08,0:23:12.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少想挑战一下 挑战一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.13,0:23:14.75,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气这是同意的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.82,0:23:17.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答应想要安心的我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.54,0:23:24.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是特别的你 就让我特别地…推倒你！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------INJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.90,0:09:09.32,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハレルヤ学び舎　もーにんもーにん今日も
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.66,0:09:15.43,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晴れたや学ぼーや　出欠とるよ(Hey teacher)
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.43,0:09:20.84,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハレルヤ学び舎　おはよう今日も
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.22,0:09:26.79,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晴れたね学ぼーね　会いにきたよ(Dear friends)
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.15,0:09:32.85,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感情二乗気丈に炎上　浮かれた男女ちょっとローカ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.87,0:09:38.43,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情事情世情の同情　校則の範囲で
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.74,0:09:44.08,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盛り上がるんだるんだ　グッデイグッデイ今日も
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.42,0:09:49.96,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,セイシュン進化進化　出血サービス(もひとつ)
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.42,0:09:55.69,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はじけちゃうんだうんだ　おおいに今日も
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.07,0:10:01.77,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キャラなりソレなり　意外性(開眼☆)
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.22,0:10:12.90,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主張したりしなかったり(ゆらゆら～)難しいお年頃です
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.09,0:10:17.04,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まずは席に着いて
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.12,0:10:22.34,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キーンコーンカーンコーン
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.66,0:10:23.67,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はじめるよっ!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.88,0:10:29.32,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハレルヤ?スタディスタディ おベンキョしましょ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.49,0:10:35.31,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,パパパヤ?ラーニンラーニン セイシュクに(のびのび～)
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.43,0:10:40.97,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハレルヤ?スタディスタディ 居眠り禁止
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.24,0:10:46.19,INJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,パパパヤ?ラーニンラーニン 学びましょ
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------INCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.90,0:09:09.32,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈利路亚学堂　今天也是morningmorning
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.66,0:09:15.43,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晴天和学习　我要翘课了(Hey teacher)
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.43,0:09:20.84,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈利路亚学堂　今天也是早安
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.22,0:09:26.79,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晴天要学习　我去见你了(Dear friends)
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.15,0:09:32.85,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感情的平方燃烧的坚强　走廊有点欢闹的男女
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.87,0:09:38.43,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情理由世故和同情　都在校规的范围内
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.74,0:09:44.08,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沸腾起来起来　今天也是gooddaygoodday
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.42,0:09:49.96,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青春进化进化　出血杀必死(再来一个)
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.42,0:09:55.69,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑袋脱线脱线　今天也很多
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.07,0:10:01.77,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据性格应对　意外性(开眼☆)
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.22,0:10:12.90,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在固执和妥协之间(摇摇摆摆)复杂的年龄
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.09,0:10:17.04,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先在位子上坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.12,0:10:22.34,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叮咚叮当
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.66,0:10:23.67,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始了！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.88,0:10:29.32,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈利路亚studystudy　来学习吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.49,0:10:35.31,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哒哒哒哒runningrunning　安静点哦(长高长高～)
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.43,0:10:40.97,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈利路亚studystudy　别打瞌睡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.24,0:10:46.19,INCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哒哒哒哒runningrunning　来学习吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.10,0:00:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天樱守祭就要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.65,0:00:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请大家秉承樱守高中学生的态度
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.69,0:00:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有节制地享受这次的学园祭
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.50,0:00:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.72,0:00:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.07,0:00:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得砂户同学是第二义工社的社员吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.84,0:00:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么展出吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.23,0:00:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了展现社团 我们会解决同学们遇到的麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.25,0:00:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果班长有什么问题想解决 请不要客气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.44,0:00:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？ 我没事…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.27,0:00:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有执行委员的工作 先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.90,0:00:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有问题是再好不过了
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.15,0:02:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.23,0:02:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.25,0:02:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说结野去哪儿了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.07,0:03:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发邮件来说会晚点到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.47,0:03:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为和你联系不上很担心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.75,0:03:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 手机忘带了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.40,0:03:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这 这里能帮人解决问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.30,0:03:15.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对对 交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.02,0:03:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？ 这不是砂户同学吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.94,0:03:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的熟人？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.80,0:03:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我打工的便利店的店长
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.03,0:03:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的恋人琉璃琉璃失踪了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.35,0:03:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋人失踪？ 这是大事件啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.84,0:03:36.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微一走神就不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.11,0:03:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋人？ 是不是最近刚买的等身大抱枕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.28,0:03:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.17,0:03:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琉璃琉璃不是抱枕！是我重要的恋人！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.49,0:03:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琉璃琉璃～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.26,0:03:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长只对二次元感兴趣 是个很有个性的人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.47,0:04:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 这家伙是个把抱枕当妹子的变态啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.12,0:04:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我自己去找！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.04,0:04:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您好 小猫咖啡厅营业中
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.28,0:04:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请务必光临
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.17,0:04:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想和太郎一起去看看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.33,0:04:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 抱枕在这里…哦不对 是琉璃琉璃…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.27,0:04:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是被人绑架了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.79,0:04:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 是不是被当作失物拿走了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.07,0:04:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.75,0:04:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.10,0:04:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好想你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.64,0:04:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琉璃琉璃～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.70,0:04:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 你很寂寞吧 绝对不会再让你孤身一人了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.02,0:04:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个人的啊 我正准备当作可疑物品处理掉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.12,0:04:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学 我有点事 想和第二义工社商量
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.17,0:04:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎去帮人找东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.23,0:05:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 我去找他
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.80,0:05:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.59,0:05:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看这个 好像是送到樱守祭执行委员会的恐吓信
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.11,0:05:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐吓信！？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.69,0:05:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被诅咒的学生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.55,0:05:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由深重之罪孽而招来灾祸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.37,0:05:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受这因果之报吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.27,0:05:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了在事件发生前解决
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.09,0:05:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们让我们协助寻找犯人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.80,0:05:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我认为这应该是恶作剧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.97,0:05:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 这才是我想要的事件
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.12,0:05:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走吧 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.05,0:05:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 要去哪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.04,0:05:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么找犯人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.51,0:05:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.48,0:05:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.06,0:05:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现可疑人士？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.38,0:05:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,57元 切
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.38,0:05:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.68,0:06:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.12,0:06:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.45,0:06:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我把可丽饼买来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.34,0:06:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.87,0:06:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快给我去 你这个慢性子的混蛋猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.97,0:06:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.98,0:06:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.29,0:06:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.46,0:06:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有破绽！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.60,0:06:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛呢学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.15,0:06:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是巧克力味啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.31,0:06:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.28,0:06:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.66,0:06:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么想吃的话就吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.68,0:06:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的！？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.07,0:06:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.07,0:06:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.95,0:07:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18}（校内巡逻中）
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.57,0:07:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.32,0:07:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪儿了 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.22,0:07:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,章鱼～章鱼～章鱼～章鱼～章鱼～烧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.53,0:07:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃的圆圆的章鱼烧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.01,0:07:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.80,0:07:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过现在有点口渴了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.35,0:07:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要我请客啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.48,0:07:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次我请你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.79,0:07:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18}（免费饮料招待券）
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.35,0:07:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走啦 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.18,0:07:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.57,0:07:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野应该会很喜欢这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.07,0:07:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.12,0:07:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.76,0:07:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.08,0:07:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.65,0:08:02.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这里的饮料免费…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.17,0:08:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啦 不行啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.90,0:08:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.21,0:08:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.87,0:08:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到你啦 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.06,0:08:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去转转吧 好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.33,0:08:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.30,0:08:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.00,0:08:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.51,0:08:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 你没忘了我们的使命吧 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.00,0:08:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使命？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.11,0:08:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给第二义工社的委托啊白痴！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.17,0:08:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对对 我们正在校内巡逻
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.79,0:08:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.20,0:08:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像选美开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.91,0:08:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯人很有可能为了展现自己的犯罪行为
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.78,0:08:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特地把惨剧的舞台设在大规模活动之中
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.80,0:09:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.46,0:09:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么接下来 5号选手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.02,0:09:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉·安东尼特十六世小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.05,0:09:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呵呵呵
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.23,0:09:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这群下贱的平民应该也知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.48,0:09:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是这所樱守高中里最为美丽的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.87,0:09:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 愚民们 全心全意地崇拜我的美貌吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.46,0:09:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个恶心变态在干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.84,0:09:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来 有请6号选手 静香小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.25,0:09:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 欢呼吧 我是静香哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.52,0:09:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老姐…为什么会在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.25,0:09:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静香会加油获得优胜的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.23,0:09:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选美的优胜奖奖品是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.92,0:09:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双人温泉旅行券
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.07,0:09:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙 老姐是动真格的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.92,0:09:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 不要被骗了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.45,0:09:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这声音…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.68,0:10:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位请看
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.99,0:10:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然静香长得这么娇小
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.43,0:10:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但却是个货真价实的大学生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.65,0:10:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是樱守高中的学生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.55,0:10:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 死老太婆
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.64,0:10:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然在这种时候揭我老底
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.92,0:10:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是确实的不正当行为 请立即勒令其退场
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.55,0:10:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外我是最佳优胜候补 智子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.93,0:10:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老 老妈…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.04,0:10:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 人家是货真价实水灵灵的女高中生啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.09,0:10:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}那个大婶在干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.74,0:10:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说自己是女高中生 没搞错吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.60,0:10:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18}（世界cosplay写真馆）
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.22,0:10:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 恐吓信啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.74,0:10:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是不太平啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.91,0:11:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是就是不知道要怎么把犯人抓出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.39,0:11:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 被诅咒的学生 越来越有恐怖片的味道了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.34,0:11:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得是喜欢这方面的人的恶作剧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.15,0:11:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到恐怖片的话 听说发明部的恐怖小屋做的很好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.60,0:11:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖小屋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.21,0:11:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 很好 太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.49,0:11:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 上衣再多脱一点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.38,0:11:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}发明部吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.95,0:11:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 很好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.71,0:11:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好可爱 心灵被治愈了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.48,0:11:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样怎样 舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.50,0:11:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电话也打不通 太郎 你在做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.08,0:11:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这里啊 广受好评的恐怖小屋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.04,0:11:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面很暗 就算有悲鸣也没什么奇怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.32,0:11:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很适合作为惨剧的舞台啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.54,0:11:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.35,0:11:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐~怖~
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.43,0:11:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来发明部的恐怖小屋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.82,0:12:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是集合了科学的精华所成就的杰作啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.33,0:12:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请往这走
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.06,0:12:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊 还没进就被吓成这样了啊 快给我进去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.68,0:12:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 那个 别推我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.74,0:12:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得很有气氛啊 不愧是发明部
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.42,0:12:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.18,0:12:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.98,0:12:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是有够废柴的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.83,0:12:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么学姐一点也不在意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.09,0:12:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是非常害怕的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.88,0:12:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里好像有什么东西在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.78,0:12:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真拿你没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.48,0:12:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等等 学姐 不要走那么快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.51,0:13:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙是猫怪吧 而且还挺可爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.54,0:13:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.98,0:13:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫… 猫…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.66,0:13:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 难道说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.14,0:13:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是猫 讨厌 求你了 快走开吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.74,0:13:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}怕猫吗 所以那个时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.52,0:13:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 喂 快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.60,0:13:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 已经没事了 猫已经不在了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.63,0:13:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.03,0:13:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫 猫 好可怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.76,0:13:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没事了啦 请不要哭了 呐 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.70,0:13:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子很怕那种地方的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.93,0:13:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.30,0:13:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就去其它地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.02,0:13:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.86,0:13:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.10,0:13:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.71,0:14:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手 让你牵起来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.07,0:14:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是怕鬼怪的吗 所以我让你牵住我的手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.95,0:14:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.39,0:14:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真拿你没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.07,0:14:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦 快点牵住吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.72,0:14:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.49,0:14:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.29,0:14:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎你 被诅咒的学生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.05,0:14:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什 什么人 你们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.75,0:14:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 班长
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.41,0:15:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里我不是班长
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.05,0:15:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是MFC的会长 绫濑川雾乃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.50,0:15:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的人都是我的同志
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.15,0:15:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MFC？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.97,0:15:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MFC就是 美绪大人后援会的简称
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.18,0:15:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 这是什么意思…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.92,0:15:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年 被选为樱守小姐的石动美绪大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.08,0:15:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对其美貌尊敬 崇拜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.72,0:15:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且对胆敢藐视美绪之人加以惩罚的组织
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.68,0:15:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惩罚是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.86,0:15:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 那个恐吓信是班长…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.96,0:15:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把猪太郎弄到哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.90,0:15:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么我一点也不懂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.24,0:15:48.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不快点说的话就把你吊到屋顶上
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.69,0:15:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.73,0:15:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.01,0:15:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.56,0:15:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.65,0:16:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开门见山的说了 砂户同学和美绪大人是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.58,0:16:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋人关系 吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.75,0:16:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.45,0:16:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有情报称美绪大人和砂户同学以前约会过
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.96,0:16:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.18,0:16:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.81,0:16:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 今天的樱守祭也是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.44,0:16:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是班长送来恐吓信才会… 这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.92,0:16:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 就是说和美绪大人不是恋人关系了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.67,0:16:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.35,0:16:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到这个我就放心了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.96,0:16:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被诅咒的学生啊 接受你的惩罚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.08,0:16:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果说是恋人关系的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.08,0:16:55.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很令人悲伤 但也可以原谅你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.52,0:17:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人的笑容 哭脸 生气的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.00,0:17:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这些全部独占 也是理所应当的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.08,0:17:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.51,0:17:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不过是个社团的后辈而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.69,0:17:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然还敢独占美绪大人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.08,0:17:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是绝对不可允许的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.14,0:17:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很碍眼 你这连美绪大人鞋底的口香糖都不如的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.81,0:17:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在樱守祭过程中一直缠着美绪大人的混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.63,0:17:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法原谅你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.41,0:17:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 要是吃下那个鞭子的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.45,0:17:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定 绝对 确确实实地超M全开 没错的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.73,0:17:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 开始惩罚了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.39,0:17:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 学姐不会希望这种事发生的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.96,0:17:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又懂美绪大人的什么了 不是恋人的你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.81,0:17:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐只是想要实现愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.01,0:17:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是尊敬啊 崇拜什么的 所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.34,0:17:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.15,0:17:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎 没事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.16,0:17:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.91,0:18:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.93,0:18:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.23,0:18:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把猪太郎绑架起来想做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.41,0:18:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么目的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.08,0:18:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我是美绪大人后援会的会长 绫濑川雾乃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.53,0:18:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 美绪大人后援会
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.46,0:18:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们赞颂石动美绪大人的美貌
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.81,0:18:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尊敬 崇拜着石动美绪大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.93,0:18:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.62,0:18:34.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尊敬 崇拜什么的我才不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.73,0:18:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美 美绪大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.09,0:18:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人对我们说话了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.10,0:18:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么威风凌凌的身姿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.09,0:18:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然能这么接近
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.25,0:18:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.62,0:18:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 你来救我了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.14,0:18:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得让你牵住我的手 别随随便便就松开了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.48,0:18:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 知道了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.65,0:19:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.82,0:19:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人 很抱歉给您添麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.87,0:19:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MFC就此解散
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.10,0:19:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的使命已经结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.11,0:19:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 谢谢你们陪我至今
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.08,0:19:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.92,0:19:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.46,0:19:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是 谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.76,0:19:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是很开心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.45,0:19:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MFC万岁
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.60,0:19:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 是我的原因吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.12,0:19:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说点什么打个圆场会比较好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.54,0:19:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.57,0:19:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们啊 要是再有什么奇怪的举动可不会简单了事了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.64,0:19:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.88,0:19:45.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是有愿望的话就来第二义工社
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.36,0:19:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荣幸之至
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.20,0:19:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 解散
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.49,0:19:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.82,0:20:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年的樱守小姐是学姐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.48,0:20:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.21,0:20:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,优胜奖品是双人温泉旅行劵的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.30,0:20:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 学姐是和谁…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.80,0:20:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么 很在意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.33,0:20:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.54,0:20:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是小满姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.39,0:20:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和谁去都是我的自由吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.50,0:20:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.53,0:20:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.05,0:20:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 也好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.45,0:20:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今 今天谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.48,0:20:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.42,0:20:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.88,0:20:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 美绪学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.19,0:20:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.17,0:21:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人 好像很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.91,0:21:05.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎和美绪学姐今天一直在一起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.78,0:21:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还两人手牵着手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.74,0:21:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}不 那个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.50,0:21:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 那是猪太郎他…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.35,0:21:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也 很想和太郎牵着手一起逛的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.59,0:21:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.46,0:21:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要碰我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.48,0:21:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是你先碰我的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.35,0:21:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.93,0:21:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在这里发动超M啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.61,0:21:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 啊 好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.84,0:21:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子的话 超M不就暴露给大家了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.64,0:21:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来把这家伙搞晕掉 岚子也过来帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.03,0:21:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没搞清楚状况 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.05,0:21:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩子好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.95,0:21:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是太幸福了啊
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.34,0:23:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不可思议 为什么砂户无法理解个中美妙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.86,0:23:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是人生的缺憾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.93,0:23:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明二次元的女孩子们有如此的魅力
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.21,0:23:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 女孩子果然还是二次元的好 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.00,0:23:40.98,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.00,0:23:40.98,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.00,0:23:40.98,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.00,0:23:40.98,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,280)}虐待狂岚子大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.00,0:23:40.98,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,280)}虐待狂岚子大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.00,0:23:40.98,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,280)}虐待狂岚子大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
