[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成 2011-02-17 20:10:26
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H32000000,&HB4000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,5,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,7,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE3,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,8,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFGCraftYu-W5,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00A11419,&H967A0D11,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,20,20,5,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H005B12E3,&H965C13B7,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,10,25,5,1
Style: NEXT,华康少女文字W5(P),28,&H3C001698,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正黑体_GBK,22,&H507DC1B3,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------STAFF------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.20,0:03:00.03,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻译: 艾哀 天地有正气　校对: 一　打杂: HySauce、魔动小贤、9416-kun
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.20,0:03:00.03,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}澄空学园×华盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.74,0:03:00.03,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}因你而有的Dog Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.74,0:03:00.03,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}因你而有的Dog Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.74,0:03:00.03,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}因你而有的Dog Fight
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.32,0:01:26.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.88,0:01:31.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.41,0:01:35.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.74,0:01:42.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そこの迷えるオマエ　惰性感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.37,0:01:47.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}すがるワラを探して　他力本願バンザイ？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.64,0:01:52.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ここに来ただけ（相当）お利口ねボウヤ（上等）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.23,0:01:57.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}聞いてあげるわ　早くゲロっていっそGo to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.48,0:02:00.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}（No!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.06,0:02:03.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}神の仕事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.21,0:02:05.37,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}（YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.41,0:02:10.03,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}試行錯誤のevery day　いくら足掻いたトコで無駄
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.17,0:02:14.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}神に従ってれば　万事OKでしょ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.87,0:02:17.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}身の程わきまえて、さあ （呆然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.21,0:02:19.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}逆らうヤツらはお仕置きよ（当然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.45,0:02:23.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}結果主義更生させなくちゃGo to Hell →Deaaaath!!!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.23,0:02:32.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}絶対的で革新的な　チカラ見せつけてあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.73,0:02:37.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ちょっと存在感異常のイカレタ趣味くらいノープロブレム
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.30,0:02:42.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そこにひざまずいて教えを請いなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.21,0:02:46.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}人生観変えるような出会いになるから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.47,0:02:51.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そんなビビってないで　全部あずけりゃいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.64,0:02:54.27,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ヘ!ル!プ!いくよ!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.32,0:01:26.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.88,0:01:31.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…　YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.41,0:01:35.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…　YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.74,0:01:42.22,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}那边的迷途小羔羊　满是惰性的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.37,0:01:47.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}寻找可以依靠的救命稻草　坐享其成万岁？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.64,0:01:52.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}都来到这里了（相当）聪明的孩子 （很好）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.23,0:01:57.96,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我就听一下吧　快点坦白从宽干脆地Go to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.48,0:02:00.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}（No!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.06,0:02:03.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}神的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.21,0:02:05.37,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}（YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.41,0:02:10.03,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}不断尝试的every day　无论怎样挣扎都没用
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.17,0:02:14.81,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}只要服从神明　就能万事OK
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.87,0:02:17.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}掂掂自己的份量（呆然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.21,0:02:19.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}敢反抗的家伙要惩罚（当然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.45,0:02:24.20,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}不改改你的结果主义就给我Go to Hell →Deaaaath!!!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.23,0:02:32.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}让你见识下　绝对革新的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.73,0:02:37.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}存在感有点异常的疯狂兴趣No problem
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.30,0:02:42.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}给我跪在那边求我告诉你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.21,0:02:46.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}这将会成为改变人生观的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.47,0:02:51.61,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}所以别害怕 全部交给我就行
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.64,0:02:54.27,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}HE! L! P!开始吧!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.89,0:21:58.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.96,0:22:02.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.14,0:22:04.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.87,0:22:07.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.54,0:22:12.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.68,0:22:14.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.07,0:22:18.06,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}それとも…いいの？ よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.08,0:22:22.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.92,0:22:23.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.37,0:22:24.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.66,0:22:25.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.97,0:22:28.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.60,0:22:29.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}愛には恋は緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.97,0:22:33.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}純情文武両立させて insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.51,0:22:35.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.99,0:22:39.78,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}嫌われてもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.87,0:22:46.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.72,0:22:50.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}どうして？ そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.68,0:22:53.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.14,0:22:56.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.32,0:22:58.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.44,0:23:01.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめて達成しなくちゃ　胸、痛い。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.08,0:23:06.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}とにかく気持ちが止まらないの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.79,0:23:08.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.98,0:23:12.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめて挑戦したいよ　したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.03,0:23:14.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.72,0:23:17.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.44,0:23:24.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}だって特別キミは特別…押して！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.89,0:21:58.94,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.96,0:22:02.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少为达成目的也要不择手段？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.14,0:22:04.81,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸气呼气这是告白的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.87,0:22:07.52,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}但我一直无法安心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.54,0:22:12.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}那个一定是特别的…万岁！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.68,0:22:14.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}靠近一点…会讨厌吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.07,0:22:18.06,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}还是说…可以？ 一进一退背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.08,0:22:22.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}恐怖和笑容说不定很像 靠近围观我很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.92,0:22:23.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}是吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.37,0:22:24.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}爱和恋我都不擅长应付
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.66,0:22:25.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}纯情单方片面的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.97,0:22:28.57,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}商量和子弹 da-dan-da down load 对啦！对啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.60,0:22:29.94,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}爱和恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.97,0:22:33.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}纯情的文武双全 insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.51,0:22:35.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我想做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.99,0:22:39.78,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}就算被讨厌也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.87,0:22:46.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}在我的眼中你是如此耀眼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.72,0:22:50.61,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}为什么？ 对啦…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.68,0:22:53.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}但是请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.14,0:22:56.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}只有一个位子所以要不择手段！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.32,0:22:58.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.44,0:23:01.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少也要达到目的 胸口好疼。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.08,0:23:06.72,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}总而言之我的心意已经无法阻挡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.79,0:23:08.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.98,0:23:12.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少想挑战一下 挑战一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.03,0:23:14.65,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸气这是同意的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.72,0:23:17.40,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}答应想要安心的我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.44,0:23:24.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}因为是特别的你 就让我特别地…推倒你！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.45,0:00:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.77,0:00:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么会在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.40,0:00:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.93,0:00:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呜…这个触感…真怀念…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.04,0:00:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}我说由美…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.41,0:00:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.19,0:00:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样…由美…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.92,0:00:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱起来真舒服啊…岚子的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.05,0:00:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的…太郎在看着啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.19,0:00:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.60,0:00:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前你电话里提到的小狗就是他啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.97,0:00:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次见面就把别人称为狗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.36,0:00:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位是间宫由美 我的好友
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.98,0:00:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说她以前好像和辰吉交往过
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.24,0:00:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非他就是初中时那个有名的变态超M砂户太郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.76,0:00:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和这种家伙在一起 那个…治好了？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.62,0:00:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…还没有…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.57,0:00:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么还和他在一起？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.42,0:01:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我和他同班又是同一社团 而且他只是只小狗而已
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.40,0:01:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.41,0:01:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 不管你是狗还是什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.96,0:01:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许你再接近岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.34,0:01:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说由美…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.11,0:01:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.97,0:01:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你再想要接近岚子也是不可能的了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.08,0:01:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为岚子要转校到我在读的女子高中了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.75,0:01:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.99,0:03:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烫…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.53,0:03:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就能烤得香喷喷了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.35,0:03:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那么爽还治疗个毛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.67,0:03:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs18}（烤猪太郎 你的超M全都被我看穿了！作战）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.78,0:03:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊 就一点也不关心岚子吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.27,0:03:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.27,0:03:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子转校了也无所谓吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.79,0:03:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.22,0:03:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易觉得你有点优点 想对你刮目相看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.72,0:03:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.44,0:03:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和岚子交换过邮·箱·地·址吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.59,0:03:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.26,0:03:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子的事就交给你了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.38,0:03:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我认真点！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.12,0:03:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.93,0:03:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然说交给我了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.29,0:03:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉冈学长的那件事之后 我就变得很害怕男性了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.24,0:04:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算只是擦肩而过的男性我都怕的不得了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.34,0:04:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 最让人难受的 是学校的同学们变了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.85,0:04:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.38,0:04:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉冈学长在学校里说我是个淫乱的女人…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.49,0:04:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从此之后大家都对我冷眼相待…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.54,0:04:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来过来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.97,0:04:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.32,0:04:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不信任他人么…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.35,0:04:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.08,0:04:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.91,0:04:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来接你了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.30,0:04:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.02,0:04:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真拿你没辙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.27,0:04:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天我去参观岚子的社团活动
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.43,0:04:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.36,0:05:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想见一见传说中的美绪学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.66,0:05:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别自作主张啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.58,0:05:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系啦没关系啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.17,0:05:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位就是美绪学姐？好可爱啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.02,0:05:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.05,0:05:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然这么可爱…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.50,0:05:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我摸摸看吧 可以吗？可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.80,0:05:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你身边怎么都是些怪人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.09,0:05:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是结野的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.29,0:05:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 美绪学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.15,0:05:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子就算啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.94,0:05:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在说这个恶心猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.93,0:05:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在嘀咕些什么啊 很恶心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.56,0:05:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想按摩！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.01,0:05:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.45,0:05:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好硬啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.12,0:05:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 我们来做舒服的事情吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.97,0:05:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.11,0:05:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说由美
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.06,0:06:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个按摩术 不可小视啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.62,0:06:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美在间宫流按摩术的继承人中
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.56,0:06:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被称作十年一遇的天才
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.38,0:06:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做到那份上了我也没法阻止她了…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.90,0:06:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用阻止
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.84,0:06:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…老师？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.33,0:06:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人已经没救了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.06,0:06:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 爽吗？很爽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.56,0:06:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不爽…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.65,0:06:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会让你更爽的…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.96,0:06:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…住手…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.21,0:06:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是美少女值得让我按摩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.28,0:06:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎…快来救我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.07,0:06:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？为什么是我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.94,0:06:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 学姐不喜欢你这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.96,0:06:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少来碍事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.48,0:07:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…这样不是挺好的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.41,0:07:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.29,0:07:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生好可怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.80,0:07:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.73,0:07:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.62,0:07:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 太郎 我又激动了…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.22,0:07:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一看到可爱的女生就会忍不住…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.94,0:07:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要不是岚子的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.15,0:07:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我非得让你缝上十五针不可
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.37,0:07:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你是来干嘛的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.21,0:07:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子要是转校了就得离开第二义工社
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.73,0:07:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来打声招呼的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.07,0:07:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男性恐惧症的问题就交给我们来办吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.68,0:07:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会想办法治好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.66,0:07:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种地方岚子的心灵创伤只会越来越重
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.08,0:07:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还和这种变态同处一室 太不可思议了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.98,0:07:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为转校了就能解决一切问题？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.79,0:08:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 那样岚子也会更幸福的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.16,0:08:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果真如此么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.01,0:08:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些问题只有这里能解决
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.79,0:08:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.21,0:08:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 就是这个第二义工社
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.30,0:08:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.68,0:08:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美 美绪学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.18,0:08:35.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我选哪个都不是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.63,0:08:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.22,0:08:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无故缺课…很少见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.86,0:09:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么关心结野吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.38,0:09:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋…没这回事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.54,0:09:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是感冒了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.13,0:09:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说昨天回家的时候我看到她了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.20,0:09:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去不像身体不适的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.58,0:09:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子 到底怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.99,0:09:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您所拨打的用户不在服务区…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.32,0:09:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子这家伙 感冒什么的我们也能治啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.71,0:09:38.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿成这样治吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.01,0:09:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干…干嘛 有意见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.72,0:09:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,形式上的治疗也是很重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.58,0:09:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这不是很奇怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.76,0:09:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说这衣服不适合我？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.76,0:09:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的是结野的事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.52,0:09:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发了几次邮件 可是她都没有回
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.40,0:10:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是被人家讨厌了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.27,0:10:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我也很在意 打过几次电话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.65,0:10:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但一次也没有接
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.66,0:10:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连小满姐也…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.20,0:10:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.48,0:10:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再打一次
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.74,0:10:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您所拨打的用户…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.34,0:10:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说昨天回家的时候我看到她了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.17,0:10:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 有件很在意的事 我去确认一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.54,0:10:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.22,0:10:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的事？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.58,0:10:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我看到她和一个男人在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.58,0:10:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得是初中时高我们一级的学长…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.62,0:10:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太感谢你了 辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.04,0:10:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是早点察觉到就好了！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.99,0:10:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野 你在吧 我开门了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.70,0:10:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野…大家都很担心你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.43,0:11:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…别过来！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.35,0:11:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.75,0:11:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.07,0:11:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别过来…请别过来…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.31,0:11:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.38,0:11:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了…不要…不要再打我了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.45,0:11:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.74,0:11:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}别过来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.45,0:11:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我啊 太郎啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.25,0:11:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.62,0:11:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 把这根木棍捡回来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.25,0:11:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我扔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.89,0:11:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 不好好捡回来可是不行的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.10,0:11:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坏孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.50,0:11:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用您的拳头 好好地教训我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.45,0:11:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汪汪 我是您的小狗汪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.32,0:11:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎…？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.35,0:11:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 你是超M的变态
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.37,0:11:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被女生打也不会想还手的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.25,0:12:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 我是专业沙包啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.32,0:12:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.20,0:12:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.20,0:12:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我偶然遇到吉冈学长了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.34,0:12:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他向我搭话了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.67,0:12:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家之后 他又打了好几次电话过来…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.05,0:12:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我不要把初中的事说出去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.11,0:12:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很害怕…一直很害怕…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.62,0:12:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我犯下什么滔天大罪了吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.48,0:12:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要这样对我…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.31,0:12:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…想要消失掉算了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.08,0:12:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 结野在自己家里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.37,0:12:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.79,0:12:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你在听吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.87,0:13:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你谁啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.34,0:13:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬之太郎
Comment: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.01,0:13:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个… 我就先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.57,0:13:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是吉冈吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.36,0:13:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.25,0:13:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野岚子 你应该知道的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.81,0:13:40.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 这有什么问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.37,0:13:43.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打了不少威胁性质的电话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.45,0:13:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.55,0:13:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装傻了 我可是全都听结野说过了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.88,0:13:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 那个女人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.66,0:13:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是啊 只要她蹲在家里我这就平安无事了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.73,0:14:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太差劲了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.37,0:14:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女人 竟然伤了我的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.59,0:14:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是想起来就一肚子火
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.08,0:14:10.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.88,0:14:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你绝对…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.50,0:14:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.17,0:14:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣 那就稍微陪你玩玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.79,0:14:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.10,0:14:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小白 你不知道我是拳击部的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.41,0:14:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.34,0:14:51.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有趣啊 不管你怎么叫唤也不会有人来帮你的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.72,0:14:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.50,0:14:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没用没用 看这招
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.09,0:14:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔用脚踢也不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.62,0:15:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畜生 还没输 还没输
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.14,0:15:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 你很吵啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.57,0:15:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 可恶 倒下 倒下 倒下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.46,0:15:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛 虽然超痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.09,0:15:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是她的伤痛可不只是这样而已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.41,0:15:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.49,0:15:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能因为这种程度的伤痛而倒下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.16,0:15:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.01,0:15:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是纯粹的超M
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.29,0:15:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是美少女的拳头 能承受这种程度的一百倍
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.30,0:16:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体的构成不一样哦 和你这种家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.31,0:16:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么胡话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.54,0:16:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野怎么了啊 说到底不过是别人的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.13,0:16:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要自己过得好不就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.08,0:16:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「想要消失掉算了」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.17,0:16:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才刚成为高中生的女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.69,0:16:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说「想要消失掉算了」… 了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.83,0:16:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野的疼痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.62,0:16:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他体会一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.57,0:16:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.81,0:17:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好体会下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.68,0:17:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 果然扁人一点都不会觉得爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.18,0:17:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棒球棍 啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.68,0:17:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 为什么会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.29,0:17:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可惜 看来还是慢了一步
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.89,0:17:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是学姐 帮了我一把吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.23,0:17:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是个喜欢被女孩子蹂躏的变态
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.87,0:17:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然会和男生干架啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.81,0:17:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然马上就想来帮你了 但是因为看起来太认真了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.30,0:17:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就觉得「我是不是不该在这出场啊」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.51,0:18:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「但是 只是帮一点点的话应该没关系吧」就这样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.80,0:18:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那果然是神的加护啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.61,0:18:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样弄得遍体鳞伤… 是为了岚子的努力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.79,0:18:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉有一点 帅哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.37,0:18:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是要倒下的话还稍有些早
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.68,0:18:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 岚子可是在等你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.74,0:18:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.58,0:18:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小满老师 间宫
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.31,0:18:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得很有男子汉气概了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.22,0:18:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个 是你做的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.64,0:18:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户太郎该干的时候还是挺能干的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.21,0:18:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拍男人还真无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.98,0:18:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉冈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.87,0:19:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对无法原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.03,0:19:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.80,0:19:15.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.18,0:19:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 你的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.17,0:19:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用在意 只是擦伤
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.68,0:19:26.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起那个 我有礼物给你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.64,0:19:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18}（天诛）（我干坏事了）（反省中）（变态）
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.86,0:19:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他发誓了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.64,0:19:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从此以后 绝对不会接近结野 也不会打电话来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.88,0:19:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果违反的话 就把这照片散播出去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.58,0:19:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以已经没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.83,0:19:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 你的伤是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.12,0:19:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不 那个 不用在意
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.67,0:19:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊 真的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.75,0:19:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是 一个大笨蛋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.41,0:20:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能做到的只有这些啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.44,0:20:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.34,0:20:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只要这一句话 就满足了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.69,0:20:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给大家添麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.34,0:20:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也谢谢由美为我担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.01,0:20:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 本还以为能和岚子一起上女校了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.02,0:20:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 由美
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.13,0:20:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我害怕男生 但并不是想活在没有男生的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.25,0:20:46.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 这里还有太郎 美绪学姐 小满老师在
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.45,0:20:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都很关心我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.06,0:20:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我想更了解大家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.90,0:20:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要留在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.60,0:21:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 岚子 你变了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.87,0:21:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.21,0:21:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离我远点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.87,0:21:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.13,0:21:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次离太远了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.12,0:21:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 不是按你说的做了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.62,0:21:20.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 想和主人顶嘴吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.75,0:21:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 别这样 要是在这里爽起来的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.21,0:21:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就要看太郎的表现了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.80,0:21:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关系挺好的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.18,0:21:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美 怎么了啊 这身衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.61,0:21:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我转学过来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.86,0:21:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然岚子一定要我在旁保护啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.31,0:21:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.93,0:21:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 我可还没有承认你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.29,0:21:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,间宫流按摩术
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.66,0:21:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接招吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.16,0:21:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过分强烈的也很 有效啊
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.97,0:23:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治愈着日常疲惫的心 是为美少女之名
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.20,0:23:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 要试穿看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.05,0:23:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个线条更能体现出美吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.57,0:23:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会害怕只有一开始的时候啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.02,0:23:41.02,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(220,253)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.02,0:23:41.02,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(220,253)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.02,0:23:41.02,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(220,253)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.02,0:23:41.02,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(343,290)}反正就是一对笨蛋情侣啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.02,0:23:41.02,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(343,290)}反正就是一对笨蛋情侣啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.02,0:23:41.02,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(343,290)}反正就是一对笨蛋情侣啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.30,0:00:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.30,0:00:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.30,0:00:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.30,0:00:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.30,0:00:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.30,0:00:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.30,0:00:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
