[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成 2011-02-20 19:47:06
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H32000000,&HB4000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,5,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,7,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE3,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,8,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFGCraftYu-W5,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00A11419,&H967A0D11,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,20,20,5,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H005B12E3,&H965C13B7,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,10,25,5,1
Style: NEXT,华康少女文字W5(P),28,&H3C001698,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&H32FFFFFF,&H50FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,1,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC2,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,1,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------STAFF------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.00,0:02:28.43,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻译: 艾哀 天地有正气　校对: 一　打杂: HySauce、魔动小贤、9416-kun
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.00,0:02:28.43,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}澄空学园×华盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.14,0:02:28.43,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}反正就是一对笨蛋情侣啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.14,0:02:28.43,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}反正就是一对笨蛋情侣啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.14,0:02:28.43,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}反正就是一对笨蛋情侣啦
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.33,0:00:54.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.38,0:00:59.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.91,0:01:04.17,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.24,0:01:10.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そこの迷えるオマエ　惰性感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.87,0:01:15.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}すがるワラを探して　他力本願バンザイ？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.14,0:01:20.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ここに来ただけ（相当）お利口ねボウヤ（上等）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.73,0:01:26.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}聞いてあげるわ　早くゲロっていっそGo to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.98,0:01:29.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}（No!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.56,0:01:31.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}神の仕事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.71,0:01:33.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}（YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.91,0:01:38.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}試行錯誤のevery day　いくら足掻いたトコで無駄
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.67,0:01:43.31,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}神に従ってれば　万事OKでしょ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.37,0:01:45.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}身の程わきまえて、さあ （呆然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.71,0:01:47.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}逆らうヤツらはお仕置きよ（当然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.95,0:01:52.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}結果主義更生させなくちゃGo to Hell →Deaaaath!!!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.73,0:02:01.17,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}絶対的で革新的な　チカラ見せつけてあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.23,0:02:05.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ちょっと存在感異常のイカレタ趣味くらいノープロブレム
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.80,0:02:10.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そこにひざまずいて教えを請いなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.71,0:02:14.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}人生観変えるような出会いになるから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.97,0:02:20.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そんなビビってないで　全部あずけりゃいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.14,0:02:22.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ヘ!ル!プ!いくよ!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.33,0:00:54.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.38,0:00:59.86,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…　YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.91,0:01:04.17,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…　YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.24,0:01:10.72,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}那边的迷途小羔羊　满是惰性的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.87,0:01:15.98,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}寻找可以依靠的救命稻草　坐享其成万岁？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.14,0:01:20.65,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}都来到这里了（相当）聪明的孩子 （很好）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.73,0:01:26.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我就听一下吧　快点坦白从宽干脆地Go to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.98,0:01:29.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}（No!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.56,0:01:31.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}神的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.71,0:01:33.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}（YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.91,0:01:38.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}不断尝试的every day　无论怎样挣扎都没用
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.67,0:01:43.31,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}只要服从神明　就能万事OK
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.37,0:01:45.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}掂掂自己的份量（呆然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.71,0:01:47.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}敢反抗的家伙要惩罚（当然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.95,0:01:52.40,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}不改改你的结果主义就给我Go to Hell →Deaaaath!!!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.73,0:02:01.17,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}让你见识下　绝对革新的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.23,0:02:05.74,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}存在感有点异常的疯狂兴趣No problem
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.80,0:02:10.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}给我跪在那边求我告诉你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.71,0:02:14.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}这将会成为改变人生观的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.97,0:02:20.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}所以别害怕 全部交给我就行
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.14,0:02:22.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}HE! L! P!开始吧!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.39,0:21:58.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.46,0:22:01.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.64,0:22:04.31,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.37,0:22:07.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.04,0:22:12.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.18,0:22:13.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.57,0:22:17.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}それとも…いいの？ よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.58,0:22:22.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.42,0:22:22.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.87,0:22:24.16,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.16,0:22:25.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.47,0:22:28.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.10,0:22:29.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}愛には恋は緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.47,0:22:32.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}純情文武両立させて insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.01,0:22:35.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.49,0:22:39.28,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}嫌われてもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.37,0:22:45.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.22,0:22:50.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}どうして？ そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.18,0:22:52.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.64,0:22:55.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.82,0:22:57.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.94,0:23:00.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめて達成しなくちゃ　胸、痛い。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.58,0:23:06.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}とにかく気持ちが止まらないの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.29,0:23:08.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.48,0:23:11.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめて挑戦したいよ　したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.53,0:23:14.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.22,0:23:16.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.94,0:23:23.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}だって特別キミは特別…押して！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.39,0:21:58.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.46,0:22:01.57,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少为达成目的也要不择手段？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.64,0:22:04.31,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸气呼气这是告白的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.37,0:22:07.02,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}但我一直无法安心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.04,0:22:12.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}那个一定是特别的…万岁！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.18,0:22:13.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}靠近一点…会讨厌吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.57,0:22:17.56,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}还是说…可以？ 一进一退背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.58,0:22:22.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}恐怖和笑容说不定很像 靠近围观我很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.42,0:22:22.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}是吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.87,0:22:24.16,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}爱和恋我都不擅长应付
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.16,0:22:25.43,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}纯情单方片面的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.47,0:22:28.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}商量和子弹 da-dan-da down load 对啦！对啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.10,0:22:29.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}爱和恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.47,0:22:32.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}纯情的文武双全 insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.01,0:22:35.42,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我想做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.49,0:22:39.28,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}就算被讨厌也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.37,0:22:45.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}在我的眼中你是如此耀眼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.22,0:22:50.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}为什么？ 对啦…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.18,0:22:52.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}但是请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.64,0:22:55.79,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}只有一个位子所以要不择手段！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.82,0:22:57.86,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.94,0:23:00.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少也要达到目的 胸口好疼。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.58,0:23:06.22,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}总而言之我的心意已经无法阻挡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.29,0:23:08.42,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.48,0:23:11.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少想挑战一下 挑战一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.53,0:23:14.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸气这是同意的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.22,0:23:16.90,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}答应想要安心的我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.94,0:23:23.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}因为是特别的你 就让我特别地…推倒你！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.14,0:00:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.33,0:00:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我交往
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.99,0:00:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.24,0:00:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说让你做我的男友
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.69,0:00:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪学姐 你这是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.90,0:00:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电视剧里不是经常有这样的情节吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.98,0:00:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人公因为爱的力量而摆脱心理障碍
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.47,0:00:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.26,0:00:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用爱拯救猪太郎作战！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.24,0:00:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.81,0:00:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然让人讨厌的想吐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.81,0:00:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这也是神的工作啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.12,0:00:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是期限只到你的超M体质治愈为止
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.96,0:00:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…无视我的意见吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.95,0:00:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说 你和我从现在开始就是情侣了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.00,0:00:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这方法能治好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.85,0:00:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然是第一次约会 具体的安排就交给我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.96,0:02:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.09,0:02:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 砂户太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.87,0:02:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你了解这次约会中自己的任务吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.39,0:02:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.61,0:02:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概的行程我已经告诉美绪了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.38,0:02:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后有事件的时候我会做出指示 放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.07,0:02:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.03,0:02:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你好运
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.76,0:02:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.72,0:02:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的没问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.96,0:02:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.50,0:03:02.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等很久了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.53,0:03:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…三十分钟左右吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.64,0:03:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢款待！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.84,0:03:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒的美腿
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.95,0:03:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候要说「我也才刚到」才对 你这只贱猪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.17,0:03:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.23,0:03:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.25,0:03:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始给我更多的调教吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.00,0:03:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是约会了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.96,0:03:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 一开始去哪里啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.43,0:03:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小满老师说已经告诉学姐你了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.29,0:03:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.64,0:03:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.93,0:03:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很烦啊 只是为了制定计划而通宵了而已啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.81,0:03:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 累死了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.23,0:03:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喏
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.11,0:03:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.24,0:03:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋！约会的时候当然要牵手啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.61,0:04:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小满姐说了 在约会时候尽量像情侣一样手牵手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.98,0:04:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.75,0:04:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干嘛啊慢性子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.24,0:04:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐的手 原来这么柔软温热啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.20,0:04:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来第一阶段成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.10,0:04:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.44,0:04:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然啦 我亲手做的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.55,0:04:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐亲手做的！？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.85,0:04:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是小满姐在一旁全程指导我做的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.22,0:04:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吃饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.49,0:04:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 你手指上的伤…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.80,0:04:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.38,0:04:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了我居然弄成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.78,0:04:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有受伤啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.58,0:04:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小满姐告诉我这么做的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.25,0:04:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然会被这种小把戏骗到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.19,0:05:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说你单细胞好呢还是什么好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.14,0:05:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是很失望啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.61,0:05:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那能做成这样值得表扬啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.50,0:05:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点给我吃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.66,0:05:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之情况还算过得去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.17,0:05:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么在被喂食啊 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.88,0:05:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…这是要去哪里啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.82,0:05:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.83,0:05:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.34,0:05:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像这样在公园里随便走走才像约会嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.55,0:05:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.92,0:05:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.56,0:05:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.77,0:05:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会要干些什么才好？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.16,0:05:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要问我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.37,0:05:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是和间宫同学在交往吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.26,0:05:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有…在初中毕业由美搬走后
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.30,0:05:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就自然分手了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.27,0:05:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.51,0:06:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是过去的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.08,0:06:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底现在还喜不喜欢由美 我自己也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.76,0:06:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 约会的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.66,0:06:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干些让对方开心的事情不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.58,0:06:15.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我知道的话就不用愁了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.63,0:06:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.09,0:06:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.25,0:06:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃冰淇淋吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.63,0:06:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.73,0:06:33.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.36,0:06:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有话快说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.17,0:06:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.15,0:06:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在什么啊 快把美绪脸上粘的冰淇淋擦掉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.58,0:06:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.07,0:06:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事做不到啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.73,0:06:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.44,0:06:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁打的？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.41,0:06:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 粘到脸上了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.07,0:07:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我就好了啦 我自己会擦掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.99,0:07:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐真可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.81,0:07:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.72,0:07:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 美绪的好感度上升了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.69,0:07:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.19,0:07:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像刚才那样 在约会途中会出现各种选项
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.94,0:07:20.86,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(60,160)}帮她擦掉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.94,0:07:20.40,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(60,255)}装作没看见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.16,0:07:28.82,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(60,155)}帮她擦掉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.16,0:07:29.28,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(60,235)}装作没看见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.51,0:07:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据你的选择 美绪的好感度会发生变化
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.16,0:07:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是好感度太低了…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.52,0:07:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会就失败了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.92,0:07:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会在众人的面前被美绪狠踹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.35,0:07:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的超M体质不就曝光了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.33,0:07:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺带一提 我会做出怎样的指示 美绪也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.59,0:08:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？脸好红啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.83,0:08:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道 学姐也很紧张吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.67,0:08:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呵呵呵呵…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.16,0:08:14.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 看看谁才是合适的约会对象
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.51,0:08:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就用爱的力量和我一决胜负吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.66,0:08:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贫乳庶民
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.24,0:08:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说谁贫乳啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.78,0:08:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18}你是不可能赢得了我的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.07,0:08:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你没事吧辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.51,0:08:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 主人…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.14,0:08:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主…主人！？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.94,0:08:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么牵挂我的身体…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.04,0:08:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你你你…你们在干什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.74,0:08:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.24,0:08:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你你你…你们是这种关系吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.57,0:09:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接接接…接吻的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.15,0:09:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.52,0:09:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在惊讶什么啊 这是爱人之间理所当然的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.07,0:09:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理所当然你妹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.05,0:09:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连接吻的觉悟都没有 你还想治好这位的超M体质？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.17,0:09:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你敢接吻吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.41,0:09:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.88,0:09:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就算我赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.23,0:09:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会变成这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.06,0:09:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光会生气 你的贫乳会变得更小的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.45,0:09:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区一个不男不女的恶心变态
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.57,0:09:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会才刚刚开始呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.71,0:09:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.59,0:09:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.43,0:09:54.93,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(380,133)\fad(0,100)}小满老师
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.43,0:09:54.93,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(236,210)\fad(0,100)}在摩天轮内
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.43,0:09:54.93,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(185,333)\fad(0,100)}砂户太郎给美绪膝枕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.68,0:10:00.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给学姐膝枕什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.59,0:10:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愿意的话就算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.72,0:10:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.36,0:10:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别乱动 很挤的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.62,0:10:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.65,0:10:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.06,0:10:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.23,0:10:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才真是帮了我大忙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.55,0:10:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同为变态同胞不是跟你很配吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.96,0:10:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不想了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.62,0:10:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初吻…果然还是要和喜欢的女生一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.92,0:10:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区一个变态还搞什么少女情怀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.50,0:10:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和变态没关系啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.72,0:10:37.97,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\move(355,102,355,117)}小满老师
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.72,0:10:37.97,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\move(269,152,269,167)}保持这个姿势
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.72,0:10:37.97,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\move(233,240,233,255)}相互告诉对方自己喜欢\N对方的哪一点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.10,0:10:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.79,0:10:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相互告诉对方自己喜欢对方的哪一点…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.00,0:10:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有喜欢的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.34,0:10:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.56,0:10:49.36,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(358,115)\fs14\fad(100,0)}小满老师
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.56,0:10:49.36,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(325,141)\fs14\fad(100,0)}今天
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.56,0:10:49.36,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(252,227)\fs14\fad(100,0)}你们两个人是情侣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.07,0:10:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次又是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.93,0:10:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们两个人是情侣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.43,0:10:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从哪里偷看的啊 小满姐真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.66,0:10:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.69,0:11:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先说啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.39,0:11:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…喜欢你…脸长得很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.74,0:11:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轮到学姐了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.37,0:11:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.36,0:11:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M变态让人恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.91,0:11:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是讨厌的地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.40,0:11:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右撇子？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.49,0:11:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数人都这样啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.25,0:11:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 总在固定的地方上厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.28,0:11:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把我当什么了！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.58,0:11:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.72,0:11:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会是想不出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.36,0:11:38.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再说…行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.11,0:11:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叹什么气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.01,0:11:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.24,0:11:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和太郎约会的人 应该是我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.76,0:11:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18\fad(100,0)}（小满指示 选择真实的爱！）
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.27,0:12:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到连岚子都出场了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.01,0:12:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我不会把这家伙让给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.66,0:12:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪学姐 难道你对太郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.87,0:12:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一决胜负吧 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.91,0:12:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正合我意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.38,0:12:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来来 开始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.16,0:12:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会输给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.95,0:12:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许说话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.70,0:12:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎选我比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.07,0:12:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要扯碎啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.90,0:12:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.19,0:12:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能输给你啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.61,0:12:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没…没事…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.99,0:12:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生好可怕啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.56,0:12:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 这个约会要到什么时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.22,0:12:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多是这里了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.52,0:12:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.35,0:13:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 其实得了不治之症
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.96,0:13:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 因为太想和太郎约会了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.24,0:13:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就偷偷跑出医院
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.35,0:13:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 这是番茄汁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.26,0:13:22.01,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(216,102)}小满老师
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.26,0:13:22.01,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(177,131)}向美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.26,0:13:22.01,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(80,290)}请和我结婚吧 ①
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.26,0:13:22.01,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(80,315)}回医院去吧 ②
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.31,0:13:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 请和我结婚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.07,0:13:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 真的吗 我真的可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.20,0:13:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非学姐不可
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.50,0:13:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好开心
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.85,0:13:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于到最终事件了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.99,0:13:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小满老师
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.82,0:13:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就是你们的结婚仪式了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.23,0:14:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人宣誓永远相爱 相互拥抱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.37,0:14:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太过火了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.01,0:14:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且用爱的力量来治疗我超M体质什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.65,0:14:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 做不到的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.56,0:14:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又为什么要…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.78,0:14:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的约会不是为了你 其实是为了美绪而办的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.53,0:14:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.92,0:14:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后就交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.29,0:14:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.56,0:14:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 有什么奇怪的地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.63,0:14:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不 非常的漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.33,0:14:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说有成效了呢… 啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.58,0:14:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.95,0:14:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有穿习惯 感觉有点奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.01,0:15:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 你啊 是不是喜欢上我了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.64,0:15:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个 应该说是两码事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.90,0:15:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掩饰也没有用的哦 这才是约会的目的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.07,0:15:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 到最后的高潮了 这样你就会彻底爱上我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.64,0:15:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M体质什么的很快就能治好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.03,0:15:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 不管怎么说拥…拥抱什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.89,0:15:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个我决定取消了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.97,0:15:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊 那种…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.91,0:15:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相爱的两人 接吻才自然啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.22,0:15:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不…不会是认真的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.09,0:15:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵什么啊 快闭上眼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.58,0:15:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.05,0:15:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是学姐也该是开玩笑的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.87,0:15:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且一脸生气的样子也不会接吻的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.98,0:16:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你干什么啊… 猪太郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.97,0:16:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.85,0:16:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要和我这种人接吻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.56,0:16:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要说吗 当然是为了治好你的超M体质…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.02,0:16:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是为了这种事？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.70,0:16:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女装变态不也说了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.07,0:16:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相爱的人之间接吻很正常
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.48,0:16:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接吻很正常？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.69,0:16:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我是神啊 所以要实现你的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.05,0:16:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐已经习惯了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.95,0:16:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对学姐来说 接吻对谁来说都能像打招呼一样地…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.90,0:16:41.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不可能的吧 我可是第一次的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.90,0:16:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.34,0:16:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 「别开玩笑了」！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.64,0:16:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发什么火啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.58,0:16:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要和根本一点都不喜欢的人接吻
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.94,0:16:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是 想要把你的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.79,0:16:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经够了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.48,0:17:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.99,0:17:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.66,0:17:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是「事件」吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.64,0:17:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.33,0:17:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定又是… 我可不会上当了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.24,0:17:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多开适可而止…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.15,0:17:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烧得很重啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.18,0:17:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被发现了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.27,0:17:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从什么时候开始的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.90,0:17:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都干了些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.72,0:17:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要这么勉强自己啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.74,0:17:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 因为想要实现你的愿望…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.90,0:17:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐是大笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.68,0:17:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.32,0:17:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上 就要到 医院了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.90,0:18:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 为了我这种人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.23,0:18:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哭吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.19,0:18:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 原来是雨啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.96,0:18:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 擅自亲了你 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.17,0:18:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会生气也是理所当然的啊 对象是我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.69,0:18:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 这样的 这样的学姐 好不自然啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.79,0:18:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 亏人家还特地…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.62,0:18:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种耳光 我一点也不会爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.84,0:18:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请像平常一样狠狠地打我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.72,0:19:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个 变态
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.02,0:19:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 你还是 要由我来…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.05,0:19:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.40,0:19:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.95,0:19:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.99,0:19:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.28,0:19:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了别人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.33,0:19:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了别人 而付出全力的地方我很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.25,0:19:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 一点不像你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.91,0:19:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是失职啊 作为保健医
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.17,0:19:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她最擅长在这种时候装成什么事也没有的样子了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.49,0:19:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 今天的约会说是为了学姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.81,0:19:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.14,0:20:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子从小时候开始就没怎么和朋友一起玩过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.87,0:20:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不擅长和别人交流
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.24,0:20:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让她多少能克服一点…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.17,0:20:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.62,0:20:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天辛苦你了 好好休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.61,0:20:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我要留在学姐身边
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.04,0:20:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.49,0:20:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 真让我担心啊 姐姐来照看你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.17,0:20:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 请张嘴 啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.82,0:20:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流汗了吧 让姐姐来帮你擦掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.28,0:20:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静香 请不要妨碍我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.76,0:20:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈才是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.16,0:20:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 照看是母亲的职责 绝对不让给你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.62,0:20:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 姐姐来照看你…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.66,0:20:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了 给我出去！！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.31,0:20:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.56,0:20:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太慢了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.74,0:21:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.12,0:21:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.40,0:21:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都休息三天了 肯定好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.41,0:21:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢 我喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.51,0:21:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭上眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.10,0:21:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.82,0:21:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是命令 快
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.64,0:21:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.64,0:21:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本没治好嘛 果然爱的力量还是不靠谱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.58,0:21:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来爱的力量是啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.96,0:21:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在才说这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.50,0:21:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的以为要亲嘴了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.76,0:21:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 没救了呢 你这只猪
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.94,0:23:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天 我也会说
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.25,0:23:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「欢迎回来 太郎」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.77,0:23:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「先吃饭？ 还是先洗澡？」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.60,0:23:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「还是说要…」什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.76,0:23:35.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后两人相互凝视 手牵起手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.15,0:23:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 男生好可怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.46,0:23:40.46,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(220,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.46,0:23:40.46,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(220,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.46,0:23:40.46,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(220,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.46,0:23:40.46,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(343,280)}天才少女暴走剧！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.46,0:23:40.46,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(343,280)}天才少女暴走剧！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.46,0:23:40.46,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(343,280)}天才少女暴走剧！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.90,0:00:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.90,0:00:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.90,0:00:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.90,0:00:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.90,0:00:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.90,0:00:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.90,0:00:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
