[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成 2011-01-13 00:26:49
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H32000000,&HB4000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,5,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,7,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE3,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,8,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFGCraftYu-W5,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00A11419,&H967A0D11,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,20,20,8,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通简体,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H005B12E3,&H965C13B7,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,10,25,8,1
Style: EDJP,DCPHoLeiSho-W3,15,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00C6B397,&H64E6DDD7,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,10,20,10,1
Style: EDCN,方正隶变_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00C6B397,&H64E6DDD7,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,8,25,10,1
Style: NEXT,华康少女文字W5(P),28,&H3C001698,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正黑体_GBK,22,&H507DC1B3,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&H64000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------STAFF------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.38,0:23:29.38,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,100)}翻译: 艾哀 天地有正气 校对: 一
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.39,0:23:32.39,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,100)}撸轴: 好孩子Z〇 打杂: HySauce、魔动小贤、9416-kun
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.40,0:23:35.40,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}澄空学园×华盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.14,0:02:19.43,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(20,0)}同类的距离
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.14,0:02:19.43,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(20,0)}同类的距离
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.14,0:02:19.43,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(20,0)}同类的距离
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.52,0:00:45.97,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.08,0:00:50.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.61,0:00:54.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.94,0:01:01.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そこの迷えるオマエ　惰性感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.57,0:01:06.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}すがるワラを探して　他力本願バンザイ？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:11.35,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ここに来ただけ（相当）お利口ねボウヤ（上等）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.43,0:01:17.16,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}聞いてあげるわ　早くゲロっていっそGo to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.68,0:01:20.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}（No!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.26,0:01:22.38,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}神の仕事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.41,0:01:24.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}（YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.61,0:01:29.23,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}試行錯誤のevery day　いくら足掻いたトコで無駄
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.37,0:01:34.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}神に従ってれば　万事OKでしょ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.07,0:01:36.38,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}身の程わきまえて、さあ （呆然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.41,0:01:38.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}逆らうヤツらはお仕置きよ（当然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.65,0:01:43.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}結果主義更生させなくちゃGo to Hell →Deaaaath!!!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.43,0:01:51.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}絶対的で革新的な　チカラ見せつけてあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.93,0:01:56.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ちょっと存在感異常のイカレタ趣味くらいノープロブレム
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.50,0:02:01.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そこにひざまずいて教えを請いなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.41,0:02:05.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}人生観変えるような出会いになるから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.76,0:02:10.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そんなビビってないで　全部あずけりゃいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.84,0:02:13.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ヘ!ル!プ!いくよ!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.20,0:00:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.52,0:00:45.97,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.08,0:00:50.56,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…　YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.61,0:00:54.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…　YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.94,0:01:01.42,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}那边的迷途小羔羊　满是惰性的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.57,0:01:06.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}寻找可以依靠的救命稻草　坐享其成万岁？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:11.35,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}都来到这里了（相当）聪明的孩子 （很好）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.43,0:01:17.16,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我就听一下吧　快点坦白从宽干脆地Go to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.68,0:01:20.02,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}（No!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.26,0:01:22.38,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}神的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.41,0:01:24.57,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}（YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.61,0:01:29.23,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}不断尝试的every day　无论怎样挣扎都没用
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.37,0:01:34.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}只要服从神明　就能万事OK
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.07,0:01:36.38,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}掂掂自己的份量（呆然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.41,0:01:38.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}敢反抗的家伙要惩罚（当然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.65,0:01:43.40,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}不改改你的结果主义就给我Go to Hell →Deaaaath!!!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.43,0:01:51.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}让你见识下　绝对革新的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.93,0:01:56.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}存在感有点异常的疯狂兴趣No problem
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.50,0:02:01.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}给我跪在那边求我告诉你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.41,0:02:05.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}这将会成为改变人生观的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.67,0:02:10.81,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}所以别害怕 全部交给我就行
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.84,0:02:13.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}HE! L! P!开始吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.19,0:21:58.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.26,0:22:01.37,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.44,0:22:04.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.17,0:22:06.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.84,0:22:11.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.98,0:22:13.35,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.37,0:22:17.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それとも…いいの？ よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.38,0:22:22.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.22,0:22:22.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.67,0:22:23.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.96,0:22:25.23,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.27,0:22:27.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.90,0:22:29.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛には恋は緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.27,0:22:32.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情文武両立させて insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.81,0:22:35.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.29,0:22:39.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌われてもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.17,0:22:45.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.02,0:22:49.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうして？ そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.98,0:22:52.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.44,0:22:55.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.62,0:22:57.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.74,0:23:00.35,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ　胸、痛い。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.38,0:23:06.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とにかく気持ちが止まらないの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.09,0:23:08.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.28,0:23:11.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて挑戦したいよ　したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.33,0:23:13.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.02,0:23:16.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.74,0:23:23.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって特別キミは特別…押して！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.20,0:00:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.19,0:21:58.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.26,0:22:01.37,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少为达成目的也要不择手段？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.44,0:22:04.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气呼气这是告白的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.17,0:22:06.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我一直无法安心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.84,0:22:11.90,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个一定是特别的…万岁！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.98,0:22:13.35,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠近一点…会讨厌吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.37,0:22:17.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说…可以？ 一进一退背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.38,0:22:22.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖和笑容说不定很像 靠近围观我很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.22,0:22:22.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.67,0:22:23.96,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋我都不擅长应付
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.96,0:22:25.23,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情单方片面的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.27,0:22:27.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商量和子弹 da-dan-da down load 对啦！对啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.90,0:22:29.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.27,0:22:32.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情的文武双全 insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.81,0:22:35.22,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.29,0:22:39.08,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被讨厌也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.17,0:22:45.40,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的眼中你是如此耀眼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.02,0:22:49.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？ 对啦…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.98,0:22:52.42,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.44,0:22:55.59,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一个位子所以要不择手段！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.62,0:22:57.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.74,0:23:00.35,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达到目的 胸口好疼。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.38,0:23:06.02,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总而言之我的心意已经无法阻挡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.09,0:23:08.22,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.28,0:23:11.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少想挑战一下 挑战一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.33,0:23:13.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气这是同意的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.02,0:23:16.70,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答应想要安心的我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.74,0:23:23.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是特别的你 就让我特别地…推倒你！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.23,0:00:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烫好烫好烫好烫！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.48,0:00:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的声音是怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.19,0:00:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs18}（猪太郎的超M体质矫正大计划）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.19,0:00:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs18}（热水泡猪 起名为「奶油炖汤理论大作战」）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.06,0:00:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你们在做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.76,0:00:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烫好烫好烫好烫…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.05,0:00:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样不断地承受痛苦 本来早就该感觉腻了的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.22,0:00:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是超M的砂户太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.89,0:00:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙真是个经历千锤百炼的变态
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.21,0:00:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没辙 考虑一下个作战计划吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.30,0:00:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活着的意义是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.60,0:00:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不…不要！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.66,0:00:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚洗完澡来一拳 太棒了
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------CM-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.03,0:02:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 今天也悲剧了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.61,0:02:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.38,0:02:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这种人…你这种人…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.61,0:02:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干…干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.30,0:02:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.29,0:02:55.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来揍我 狠狠地责骂我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.22,0:03:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到居然和把我变成超M体质的人在一个社团
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.34,0:03:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和她一起乘车总觉得有点…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.66,0:03:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等下一班吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.73,0:03:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.34,0:03:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂…砂户？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.10,0:03:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你再等也不会有座位的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.96,0:03:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.87,0:03:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么不上车？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.93,0:04:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.65,0:04:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为…为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.23,0:04:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要是放着你不管先回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.04,0:04:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会被学姐和小满老师整得很惨的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.08,0:04:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里不舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.13,0:04:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我对男性…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.54,0:04:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男性？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.63,0:04:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离我远点！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.87,0:04:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.25,0:04:30.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.55,0:04:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很害怕…男性
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.41,0:04:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男性恐怖症？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.14,0:04:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要和男性在一起 就会觉得很恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.28,0:04:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你才迟迟不上电车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.63,0:04:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的时候也可以忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.90,0:04:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非经常迟到缺课也是因为这个？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.22,0:04:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然听上去只会让人觉得是借口
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.59,0:04:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你每次揍我也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.08,0:05:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只要被男性碰到就会很害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.22,0:05:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一不留神就会…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.61,0:05:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像那个 在被打之前先下手为强…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.12,0:05:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太乱来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.98,0:05:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别摆出那副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.20,0:05:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有觉得自己不对的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.73,0:05:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心 我会离你一段距离的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.07,0:05:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.06,0:05:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 这次又有什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.71,0:05:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字叫太郎吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.34,0:05:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.67,0:05:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可…可以叫你太郎吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.20,0:05:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.35,0:05:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前养的小狗就叫太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.41,0:05:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是小狗太郎…小狗太郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.67,0:05:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狗！？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.56,0:05:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是男性人类…不害怕不害怕…完全不害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.35,0:05:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙在自我暗示…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.01,0:05:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 就让我好好说她一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.92,0:06:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我是岚子大人的肮脏丑陋下流的小狗太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.06,0:06:04.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请您给小的下命令吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.65,0:06:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…又觉醒了么…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.31,0:06:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈哈哈哈哈哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.89,0:06:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那么好笑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.05,0:06:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…哈哈哈哈哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.54,0:06:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然从初中的那件事发生以来一直很棘手
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.51,0:06:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但结野的笑容 真的很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.15,0:06:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那明天见
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.57,0:06:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.30,0:06:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.15,0:06:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个请求
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.27,0:06:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其…其实我不想拜托你的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.52,0:06:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说说看啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.19,0:06:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就要到期中考试了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.58,0:06:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让你教教我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.69,0:06:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为没法拜托班上其他人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.95,0:06:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是让我来…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.62,0:06:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那让石动学姐教你怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.58,0:07:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…美绪学姐好像不太擅长学习…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.96,0:07:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以拜托你了 算是一生的请求了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.82,0:07:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.23,0:07:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.14,0:07:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想就我一个人的话还是会让结野不太自在
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.10,0:07:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说太郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.50,0:07:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野 其实这家伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.21,0:07:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是辰吉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.32,0:07:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叶山同学！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.75,0:07:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拜托的是太郎啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.09,0:07:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙成绩很好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.31,0:07:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样戴上假发 结野也不会觉得他是男性了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.67,0:07:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 除了美绪学姐以外
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.67,0:07:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没见过这么漂亮的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.18,0:07:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么看都是女生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.27,0:07:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别 别一直盯着看啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.90,0:07:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺带一提衣服是我亲自缝制的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.14,0:07:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是小满姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.26,0:08:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 现在的我是不是很奇怪啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.74,0:08:04.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没这回事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.94,0:08:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 很可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.26,0:08:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.01,0:08:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿出自信 你很美丽的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.69,0:08:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 头稍微歪一下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.69,0:08:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.20,0:08:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 算是及格吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.25,0:08:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然远不及我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.92,0:08:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和美少女这个词真是绝配
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.64,0:08:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没在除你之外的人面前穿成这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.72,0:08:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好开心啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.93,0:08:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.18,0:08:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…很美丽…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.77,0:08:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.27,0:08:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…很美丽…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.60,0:08:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呵呵呵呵 我的美丽世界第一
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.86,0:08:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死老百姓们 更多地赞美我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.60,0:08:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…辰吉小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.67,0:08:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以不要用这种平民的口气叫我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.29,0:09:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下辈子要是投胎做贵族的话 和你跳一支舞也行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.90,0:09:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呵呵呵呵…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.23,0:09:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的人格出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.94,0:09:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？一个变态小鬼在说些什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.17,0:09:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真实之美是超越性别的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.01,0:09:15.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你这
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.81,0:09:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是贫瘠的胸部啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.51,0:09:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才应该反省下自己到底是不是女性
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.25,0:09:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混混混混…混蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.12,0:09:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区一个恶心变态 居然…居然敢摸我的胸！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.79,0:09:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐冷静一下 他和我不一样 再这样下去的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.08,0:09:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我变成人肉渣吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.85,0:09:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样 学习会开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.32,0:09:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然在相处不佳的学姐和辰吉中有点小麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.69,0:09:51.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但无论如何 放学后的学习会顺利进行着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.17,0:09:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于 明天就是考试当天了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.53,0:09:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.14,0:09:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.87,0:10:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.81,0:10:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.02,0:10:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.58,0:10:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让我送你一程吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.09,0:10:14.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁让你送了…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.92,0:10:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你非送不可的话就让你送一程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.42,0:10:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我的超M体质是不会有反应的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.10,0:10:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是 请务必让我送你一程 岚子公主
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.98,0:10:29.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真没办法呢…既然你都这么说了就让你送我一程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.63,0:10:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 别走在我旁边啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.87,0:10:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我后面保持三米的距离
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.00,0:10:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距离这么远的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.30,0:10:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被人袭击的时候可能救不了你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.58,0:10:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就两米
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.81,0:10:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里人还没回来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.63,0:11:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天的考试没问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.85,0:11:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 都那么努力了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.03,0:11:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 说的也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.64,0:11:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.20,0:11:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.97,0:11:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.55,0:11:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…你一直教我学习到今天…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.57,0:11:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很…很…很…很…很谢…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.25,0:11:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用客气 岚子公主
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.64,0:11:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等会儿还要学习 你快点给我回去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.03,0:11:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.16,0:11:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢两个字要好好说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.28,0:11:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.49,0:11:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.02,0:11:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少有90分吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.90,0:11:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉老师真行啊
Comment: 0,0:00:00.70,0:00:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------CM-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.74,0:12:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很努力呢 岚子 了不起 了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.70,0:12:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天都用功到很晚呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.50,0:12:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了你们 看来不会挂红灯笼了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.08,0:12:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 砂户太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.49,0:12:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.55,0:12:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好一人一张 大家一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.89,0:12:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动物园吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.12,0:12:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔去一次很不错的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.76,0:12:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是和我们去的话结野她…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.58,0:12:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动物园？ 小满老师谢谢你 我非常期待
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.36,0:12:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪学姐 是动物园哦 动物园
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.46,0:12:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子最喜欢动物园了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.55,0:12:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.83,0:12:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她知道是和我们一起去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.65,0:12:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？ 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.61,0:12:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.61,0:12:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 不许不来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.08,0:12:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管感冒发烧还是出了什么事故都得来 知道了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.10,0:12:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.51,0:13:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜喵
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.67,0:13:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜喵？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.70,0:13:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 老姐 又擅自跑进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.10,0:13:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想和太郎一起度过早上贵重的时间而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.00,0:13:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是单纯的欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.66,0:13:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里单纯了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.03,0:13:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 闹铃
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.75,0:13:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 明明设定好在8点的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.22,0:13:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我按掉的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.42,0:13:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.49,0:13:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们两人之间的恋爱之地容不下其它东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.18,0:13:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么恋爱之地啊 你这个游手好闲大学生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.61,0:13:41.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被太郎生气地骂了 哎嘿嘿 感觉挺幸福的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.47,0:13:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太狡猾了 我也有接受甜美又严厉训斥的权利啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.32,0:13:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.22,0:13:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 太郎 坏心眼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.00,0:13:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也让我一起睡Please
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.62,0:14:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我迟到了 哎 这不是谁都没到么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.39,0:14:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都是不遵守时间的家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.13,0:14:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.52,0:14:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 只有太郎一个人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.67,0:14:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 这么匆匆忙忙的真是亏了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.17,0:14:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.13,0:14:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉如何 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.25,0:14:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 早就过时间了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.90,0:14:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.30,0:14:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.25,0:14:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么今天就两个人加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.46,0:14:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.28,0:14:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是两个人一起好好享受动物园的意思啊 反正我们是不去了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.97,0:14:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也听不懂你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.63,0:14:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我好好听着 变态冠军
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.96,0:14:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是改善超M体质和克服男性恐惧症的一环
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.49,0:14:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你们很像呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.00,0:14:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和结野吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.65,0:14:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从来自女性的痛苦中感受到快感的你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.50,0:15:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接近女性对你来说也是一种恐惧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.21,0:15:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后岚子对男性这种存在本身就恐惧无比
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.90,0:15:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.59,0:15:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是人类是有适应能力的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.28,0:15:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的你们需要的就是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.79,0:15:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 岚子就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.07,0:15:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等 学姐 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.28,0:15:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18}（非洲象）
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.31,0:15:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大 鼻子好长 好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.34,0:15:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这该不会… 就是所谓的「约会」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.62,0:15:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊看啊 太郎 过来看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.57,0:15:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你们最近的气氛挺不错的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.34,0:15:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就把岚子交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.74,0:15:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 结野为什么会有男性恐惧症的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.10,0:15:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事你去问她本人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.26,0:15:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.23,0:15:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.22,0:15:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.95,0:16:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 和我在一起不开心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.53,0:16:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有这回事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.66,0:16:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才有电话来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.52,0:16:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.37,0:16:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被小满老师说了 「必须要适应男孩子」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.26,0:16:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「现在太郎和我在这里就是为了这个」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.52,0:16:16.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.46,0:16:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪她们正努力帮着我 所以我也想要努力加油
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.50,0:16:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你不过是狗一样的存在而已
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.81,0:16:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 这是什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.63,0:16:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.74,0:16:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我就是只狗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.67,0:16:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.47,0:16:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候真是对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.26,0:16:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.01,0:16:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初中时候的那件事 是我弄错了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.35,0:16:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 难道说是… 让我超M觉醒的那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.40,0:16:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个耳光…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.59,0:16:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 弄错是指什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.36,0:16:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候我以为好朋友要被抢走了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.59,0:16:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.57,0:17:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.87,0:17:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这丫就是只大畜生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.20,0:17:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会变成下油锅走钢丝啥都能玩的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.37,0:17:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 能和你这样爽朗的女孩子一起前往天界…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.88,0:17:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只猪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.86,0:17:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 他有点病
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.32,0:17:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是吗 保重身体啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.62,0:17:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.35,0:17:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请什么都不要说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.30,0:17:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才是我不对
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.56,0:17:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来勉强还过得去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.05,0:17:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱啊 蹭蹭 好想住在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.32,0:17:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的心灵伤痕 大概比你想象的还要深
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.89,0:17:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是啊 还是笑容最适合她
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.61,0:17:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 拜托你了 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.17,0:18:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好幸福啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.05,0:18:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是很喜欢动物园啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.42,0:18:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 而且这里是充满回忆的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.76,0:18:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回忆？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.93,0:18:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是在幼儿园的时候 来过一次 一家三口一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.79,0:18:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然约好一定还要再来的 结果到今天也还是没有来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.79,0:18:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.11,0:18:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离婚了 爸爸和妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.94,0:18:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.48,0:18:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.24,0:18:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.50,0:18:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会有男性恐惧症啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.30,0:18:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 只是有点在意啊 不想说也没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.83,0:18:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有听美绪学姐说过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.25,0:18:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要我来问本人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.31,0:18:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.81,0:18:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.79,0:18:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.15,0:18:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初中的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.68,0:19:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说的话我还是算开朗活泼的 而且还是挺受男生欢迎的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.03,0:19:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为对那种事不是很感冒 都拒绝了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.11,0:19:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在初二的时候 被高一年级的吉冈前辈…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.80,0:19:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 结野
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.52,0:19:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.34,0:19:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是OK了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.55,0:19:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有女生会不想和前辈交往的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.30,0:19:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道该怎么办 但是觉得那气氛不该拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.05,0:19:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉冈是那个 像模特一样超受欢迎的家伙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.07,0:19:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果就交往了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.94,0:19:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有一天前辈来到家里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.57,0:19:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要强行吻我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.75,0:19:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的指甲划到前辈的脸 然后血就…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.22,0:20:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊 她和我很像
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.52,0:20:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和在初中的时候因超M体质的事曝光 在班级里被孤立的我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.74,0:20:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石动学姐说我和结野很像 终于有些能理解了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.06,0:20:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是美绪学姐发来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.34,0:20:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.71,0:20:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.88,0:20:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和变态一起没事吗 没被做什么奇怪的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.71,0:20:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是弄哭岚子的话可饶不了你 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.22,0:20:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样说了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.45,0:20:55.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她那个人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.99,0:21:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪学姐和小满老师每晚都像这样打电话或是发短信来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.47,0:21:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.42,0:21:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互发短信聊天 感觉很有意思呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.06,0:21:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为以前几乎没有这种朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.54,0:21:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 你干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.34,0:21:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我的邮件地址登录进去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.34,0:21:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 你的地址我也登录到我的里面了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.37,0:21:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.78,0:21:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事做的时候 会和你发短信什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.55,0:21:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 笑什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.75,0:21:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.30,0:21:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.66,0:21:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是岚子啊 真是的 找得我好苦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.65,0:21:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美 为什么会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.29,0:21:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不小心跑来了
Comment: 0,0:00:00.70,0:00:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.48,0:23:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被石动学姐踢踹 被结野痛扁
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.20,0:23:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天超M体质也觉醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.59,0:23:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样是不行的 坚强起来吧 我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.15,0:23:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 痛痛快快地践踏我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.35,0:23:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 爽~
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.52,0:23:40.47,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(225,245)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.52,0:23:40.47,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(225,245)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.52,0:23:40.47,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(225,245)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.52,0:23:40.47,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,290)}因你而有的Dog Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.52,0:23:40.47,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,290)}因你而有的Dog Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.52,0:23:40.47,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,290)}因你而有的Dog Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
