[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成 2011-04-03 11:10:09
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:MM!08
Original Script:澄空×华盟
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H32000000,&HB4000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,5,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,7,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE3,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,8,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFGCraftYu-W5,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00A11419,&H967A0D11,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,20,20,5,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H005B12E3,&H965C13B7,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,10,25,5,1
Style: NEXT,华康少女文字W5(P),28,&H3C001698,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H50000000,&H50FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC2,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,1,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.70,0:00:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------STAFF------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.56,0:02:45.40,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻译: 艾哀 天地有正气　校对: TurtleIzzy　打杂: HySauce、魔动小贤、9416-kun
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.56,0:02:45.40,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}澄空学园×华盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.70,0:00:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.06,0:02:45.40,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}男男恋爱样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.06,0:02:45.40,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}男男恋爱样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.06,0:02:45.40,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}男男恋爱样
Comment: 0,0:00:00.70,0:00:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.68,0:01:12.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.30,0:01:16.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.77,0:01:21.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.10,0:01:27.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そこの迷えるオマエ　悲壮感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.77,0:01:33.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}すがるワラも見捨てりゃ　それもしょーがないか？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.11,0:01:37.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}運命は今日も（迷走）イジワルだから（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.59,0:01:43.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめてわたしが　味方してたい何かできるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.84,0:01:46.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}NO!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.42,0:01:48.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}まかせてみて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.57,0:01:50.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.77,0:01:55.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ギリギリの線じゃヌルい　破滅しちゃってゼロってそんで？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.53,0:02:00.17,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}かたくななDNA　ムリは禁物
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.23,0:02:02.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}強制終了5秒前（寸前）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.57,0:02:04.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}生まれかわれそうな予感？（全然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.81,0:02:09.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}現場主義更生させちゃえばGo to へブン
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.59,0:02:14.21,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ウムを言わさず　あの手この手で
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.28,0:02:18.16,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}今すぐ正してあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.22,0:02:22.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ちょっと存在感以上に気になるフォーリンラブ未満が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.66,0:02:27.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}情けない顔してほっとけないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.57,0:02:31.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}人生観変えるような出会いしたんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.83,0:02:36.97,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}あとはされるがまま　流されちゃえばいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.00,0:02:39.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}へ！ル！プ！いくよ！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.80,0:00:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.68,0:01:12.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.30,0:01:16.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.77,0:01:21.53,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.10,0:01:27.69,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}那边的迷途小羔羊　满是悲壮感的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.77,0:01:33.02,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}连救命稻草都不要了　这也是无可奈何的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.11,0:01:37.51,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}因为今天的命运也在（横冲直撞）刁难人（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.59,0:01:43.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少我想　成为你的伙伴帮你一把
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.84,0:01:46.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}NO!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.42,0:01:48.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}交给我试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.57,0:01:50.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.77,0:01:55.39,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}极限的界线太温和　全部毁灭归零会怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.53,0:02:00.17,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}顽固的DNA　勉强是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.23,0:02:02.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}在强制结束5秒之前（迫在眉睫）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.57,0:02:04.79,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}是不是有脱胎换骨的预感？（完全没有）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.81,0:02:09.56,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}改改你的现场主义就能Go to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.59,0:02:14.21,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}不论有无　就让我用尽手段
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.28,0:02:18.16,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}现在就让你走上正途
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.22,0:02:22.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}有点超出存在感让人在意的恋人未满
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.66,0:02:27.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}一脸可怜的样子让人无法置之不理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.57,0:02:31.69,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}因为这已是改变人生观的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.83,0:02:36.97,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}之后只要任凭摆布　随波逐流就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.00,0:02:39.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}HE! L! P!开始吧!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.70,0:00:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.24,0:21:58.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.31,0:22:01.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.49,0:22:04.16,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.22,0:22:06.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.89,0:22:11.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.03,0:22:13.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.42,0:22:17.41,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それとも…いいの？ よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.43,0:22:22.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.27,0:22:22.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.72,0:22:24.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.01,0:22:25.28,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.32,0:22:27.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.95,0:22:29.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛には恋は緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.32,0:22:32.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情文武両立させて insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.86,0:22:35.27,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.34,0:22:39.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌われてもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.22,0:22:45.45,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.07,0:22:49.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうして？ そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.03,0:22:52.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.49,0:22:55.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.67,0:22:57.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.79,0:23:00.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ　胸、痛い。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.43,0:23:06.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とにかく気持ちが止まらないの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.14,0:23:08.27,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.33,0:23:11.35,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて挑戦したいよ　したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.38,0:23:14.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.07,0:23:16.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.79,0:23:23.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって特別キミは特別…押して！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.24,0:21:58.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.31,0:22:01.42,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少为达成目的也要不择手段？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.49,0:22:04.16,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气呼气这是告白的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.22,0:22:06.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我一直无法安心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.89,0:22:11.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个一定是特别的…万岁！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.03,0:22:13.40,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠近一点…会讨厌吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.42,0:22:17.41,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说…可以？ 一进一退背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.43,0:22:22.18,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖和笑容说不定很像 靠近围观我很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.27,0:22:22.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.72,0:22:24.01,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋我都不擅长应付
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.01,0:22:25.28,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情单方片面的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.32,0:22:27.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商量和子弹 da-dan-da down load 对啦！对啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.95,0:22:29.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.32,0:22:32.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情的文武双全 insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.86,0:22:35.27,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.34,0:22:39.13,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被讨厌也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.22,0:22:45.45,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的眼中你是如此耀眼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.07,0:22:49.96,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？ 对啦…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.03,0:22:52.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.49,0:22:55.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一个位子所以要不择手段！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.67,0:22:57.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.79,0:23:00.40,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达到目的 胸口好疼。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.43,0:23:06.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总而言之我的心意已经无法阻挡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.14,0:23:08.27,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.33,0:23:11.35,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少想挑战一下 挑战一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.38,0:23:14.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气这是同意的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.07,0:23:16.75,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答应想要安心的我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.79,0:23:23.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是特别的你 就让我特别地…推倒你！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.70,0:00:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.89,0:00:05.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你渐渐困了…困了…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.22,0:00:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越来越困…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.26,0:00:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快给我睡着 你这只死猪！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.59,0:00:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好强 美绪学姐会催眠术啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.26,0:00:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天在电视上看的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.07,0:00:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是花了一晚上来练习的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.26,0:00:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能靠这种临阵磨枪的催眠术治好的话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.32,0:00:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不用这么辛苦了…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.68,0:00:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.02,0:00:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神没有办不到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.33,0:00:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.48,0:00:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快试试看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.43,0:00:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我想想…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.25,0:00:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不管说什么 都要在句尾加上「巨乳」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.41,0:00:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.63,0:00:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般般啦巨乳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.13,0:00:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎么回事石动学姐巨乳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.33,0:00:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说石动学姐巨乳…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.51,0:01:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呵呵呵 太完美了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.25,0:01:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚我到底…说什么巨乳了！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.98,0:01:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巨乳是什么啊巨乳！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.72,0:01:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定能成功！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.70,0:00:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.79,0:02:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越来越困…越来越困…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.99,0:02:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M治好了…你的超M治好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.69,0:03:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M治好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.93,0:03:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M治好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.70,0:03:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说…难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.85,0:03:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.51,0:03:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治好超M的你…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.61,0:03:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为诺亚的美人气质倾倒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.03,0:03:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.46,0:03:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明差一点就要成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.65,0:03:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.18,0:03:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪里呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.69,0:03:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是何等的美妙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.45,0:03:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.13,0:03:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太美了 小芭比
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.49,0:03:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太 太郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.31,0:03:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惹人怜爱的身高
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.67,0:03:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波澜不惊的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.55,0:03:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纤柔曼妙的腰身
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.25,0:04:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲珑匀称的双腿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.82,0:04:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经为你纤细的魅力所倾倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.01,0:04:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了 诺亚已经抓住砂户同学的心了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.29,0:04:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太美了甜心 我的心中已经开满了鲜花
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.34,0:04:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.97,0:04:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 柊学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.65,0:04:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 向着两人的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.16,0:04:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Let's over the rainbow!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.95,0:04:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 给我站住！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.47,0:04:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋 竟然对诺亚大人出手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.29,0:04:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接我萝莉神拳！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.37,0:04:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝莉萝莉萝莉…奥义！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.59,0:04:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别挡道 日村！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.04,0:05:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我人生中毫无遗憾！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.63,0:05:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.51,0:05:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.87,0:05:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.78,0:05:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.71,0:05:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的要把那里…但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.81,0:05:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.47,0:05:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里不行…不行！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.08,0:05:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 都说了不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.11,0:05:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在搞毛啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.39,0:05:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后还得让我砸晕你的后脑勺！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.05,0:05:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的萝莉控治好了…萝莉控治好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.96,0:05:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.27,0:05:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 当然
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.88,0:05:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.85,0:05:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.15,0:05:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.81,0:05:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生好可怕哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.76,0:05:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎 你都对岚子干了些什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.28,0:06:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 太郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.59,0:06:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样不好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.56,0:06:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样可爱的女孩子居然使用暴力
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.85,0:06:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该更加相爱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.21,0:06:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爱我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.32,0:06:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个混蛋变态！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.42,0:06:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石动学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.26,0:06:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干 干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.96,0:06:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样不好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.26,0:06:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样可爱的女孩子居然使用暴力
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.33,0:06:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样不好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.47,0:06:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.98,0:06:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我让开 我命令你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.00,0:06:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐着急的样子也很可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.73,0:06:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快给我让开你这个变态
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.90,0:06:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.72,0:06:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不纯异性交往
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.80,0:06:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寡廉鲜耻
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.60,0:06:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是三角关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.59,0:06:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花花公子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.22,0:06:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要在我身上趴多久啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.08,0:06:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纠结的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.27,0:07:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 不 是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.01,0:07:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天使的布鲁马
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.43,0:07:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太幸福了 太温暖了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.63,0:07:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的甜心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.89,0:07:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在冠冕堂皇的说些什么啊 猪太郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.29,0:07:20.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小腿万岁
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.17,0:07:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你还对我的小腿感兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.47,0:07:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小腿是世界的宝物
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.39,0:07:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然连小满姐也不放过
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.39,0:07:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个色魔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.04,0:07:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.34,0:07:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越是施加催眠术 就越不正常
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.03,0:07:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.45,0:07:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是副作用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.87,0:07:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 小满姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.54,0:07:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强制地把超M封印
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.35,0:07:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户太郎的精神可能产生了扭曲
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.07,0:08:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.71,0:08:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法 这样下去社团的评价会下降的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.58,0:08:08.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何也要让猪太郎回到正常的人生道路
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.80,0:08:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让女性也为之侧目玫瑰般的容颜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.08,0:08:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我就是被这花香吸引的蝴蝶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.19,0:08:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就停留在你的花上…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.66,0:08:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是打扰到你了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.96,0:08:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是梦 是梦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.61,0:08:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明让我不要和不喜欢的人接吻
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.76,0:08:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫉妒吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.48,0:08:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的你也很可爱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.13,0:08:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要太得意忘形了 你这个变态低等生物
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.60,0:08:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我滚回去从细胞分裂开始重新来过！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.29,0:08:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个女生那个女生胸部胸部…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.63,0:08:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个女生那个女生…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.30,0:09:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越来越严重了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.84,0:09:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定要治好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.56,0:09:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪学姐 你要干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.08,0:09:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再这样下去的话 砂户太郎就回不到正常人了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.11,0:09:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是最后一次 要是还不行的话我就罢手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.04,0:09:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会变成正常人…变成正常人…变成正常人…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.64,0:09:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.96,0:09:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己也不太清楚…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.70,0:09:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随你喜欢吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.87,0:09:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.56,0:09:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.67,0:09:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.84,0:09:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M体质不会也变回来了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.01,0:09:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼疼疼…好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.88,0:09:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪 猪太郎…！？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.96,0:09:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.63,0:09:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚刚说好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.36,0:10:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 好疼啊 一点也不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.57,0:10:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 真的吗！？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.18,0:10:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.03,0:10:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这只猪 渣滓 蛆虫 低等动物
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.33,0:10:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态生物 地球异形 太空垃圾！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.42,0:10:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不爽 石动学姐骂得我一点也不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.89,0:10:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治好了…我的超M…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.68,0:10:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 太好了真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.69,0:10:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.78,0:10:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再开心点啊 你的超M体质治好了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.90,0:10:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万 万岁！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.00,0:10:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再大声点 再兴奋点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.41,0:10:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万岁！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.92,0:10:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万岁！万岁！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.76,0:10:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}好厉害啊美绪学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.46,0:10:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}那还用说 因为我是神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.66,0:10:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终 终于 我的超M体质…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.58,0:10:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好开心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.91,0:11:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.59,0:11:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 你干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.18,0:11:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很痛吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.61,0:11:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像真的治好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.95,0:11:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不需要治疗超M了啦 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.94,0:11:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是为了辰吉做的便当掉地上了该怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.74,0:11:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 吃吧 辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.92,0:11:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我有带便当来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.59,0:11:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的东西就是你的东西 你的东西就是我的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.58,0:11:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是爱的便当交换 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.98,0:11:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱的充电
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.48,0:11:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是 有点奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.41,0:11:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会… 吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.51,0:11:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 下一个
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.49,0:11:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好的人就尽量上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.90,0:11:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.87,0:12:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.76,0:12:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想和你一起跑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.77,0:12:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么是两人三脚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.78,0:12:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.80,0:12:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.45,0:12:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一 二 一 二
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.21,0:12:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}喂 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.12,0:12:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一 二 啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.82,0:12:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让开点啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.77,0:12:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经 已经 已经 已经忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.85,0:12:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你 爱你爱得 死去活来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.96,0:12:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M确实治好了 但是这个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.24,0:12:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.23,0:12:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢上男人了吗 砂户太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.01,0:12:43.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我清醒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.42,0:12:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会好好做人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.82,0:12:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.54,0:12:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要说吗 你这只猪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.94,0:12:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.95,0:12:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个作战
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.78,0:13:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子的身体 可是非常柔软的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.55,0:13:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.92,0:13:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪学姐 果然还是太羞人了 这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.99,0:13:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是为了猪太郎 加油 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.20,0:13:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有男人会不为情色所沦陷
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.83,0:13:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.05,0:13:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 别爱男孩子了 还是要女孩子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.03,0:13:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩子和女孩子 你更喜欢哪一个
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.68,0:13:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.68,0:13:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.70,0:13:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.10,0:14:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和两位有很重要的话要说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.80,0:14:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经无法抑制自己的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.51,0:14:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了 和太郎的快乐婚礼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.56,0:14:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 已经事先查阅过礼服了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.32,0:14:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和太郎结合是出生前就决定了的命运
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.82,0:14:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新婚旅行去哪好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.46,0:14:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.27,0:14:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.06,0:14:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.47,0:14:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深爱着辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.87,0:14:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.23,0:14:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请救救我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.97,0:14:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉 你在这吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.86,0:14:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰 吉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.71,0:14:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是可惜 这里没有叶山辰吉哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.25,0:14:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 这样也没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.70,0:14:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我也来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.50,0:14:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成美少女吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.23,0:15:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 这样我和你就一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.50,0:15:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.19,0:15:07.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是觉得猪太郎很可爱的话我就输了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.45,0:15:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是男人 但是现在是美少女
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.97,0:15:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加入收藏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.06,0:15:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到 没想到居然会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.78,0:15:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能够接受你的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.23,0:15:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵安 姐姐大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.79,0:15:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 你认真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.64,0:15:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都是认真的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.39,0:15:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 让我们走起爱的舞步吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.13,0:15:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一 二 三
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.92,0:15:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是个贱民 还挺行的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.13,0:15:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱能够超越一切
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.20,0:15:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥斯卡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.18,0:15:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18}（出处：凡尔赛玫瑰）
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.68,0:15:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德烈
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.60,0:15:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经无法忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.48,0:15:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在看着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.15,0:15:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人看着就可以了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.54,0:15:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 进行爱的仪式吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.23,0:15:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样 好害羞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.92,0:15:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要害羞
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.99,0:15:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}这已经没救了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.51,0:15:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.38,0:16:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让他们两个这样继续下去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.81,0:16:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥斯卡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.06,0:16:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德烈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.91,0:16:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉 辰吉 辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.38,0:16:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs18}（危险！！请不要给它辰吉！！）
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.09,0:16:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs18}（请勿碰触 严禁开放 危险）
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.08,0:16:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是闲着的话 短信什么的都会发给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.30,0:16:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能做到的只有这些了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.09,0:16:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉 辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.72,0:16:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.82,0:16:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都被关着 肚子饿了吧 我做便当来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.58,0:16:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.08,0:16:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用 因为太郎很重要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.70,0:16:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.50,0:16:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.59,0:17:00.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.26,0:17:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我亲手做的料理满意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.59,0:17:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然亲手做的就是好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.88,0:17:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.89,0:17:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 还有喝的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.77,0:17:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.91,0:17:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想让自己的料理做得更好 来让辰吉开心地吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.37,0:17:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.47,0:17:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩子和女孩子自然而然的就会相互吸引的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.18,0:17:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最近非常的认同这个
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.71,0:17:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相互吸引吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.21,0:17:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和辰吉也是这样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.77,0:17:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 有点口渴了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.87,0:17:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 能给我喝吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.16,0:17:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 啊 但是我嘴碰过哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.17,0:17:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 就那样给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.41,0:18:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么给
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.34,0:18:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心跳得好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.68,0:18:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是因为太郎喝过了所以我才想喝的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.95,0:18:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以心跳得很厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.41,0:18:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎也心跳了吗 这可是间接接吻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.02,0:18:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子啊 要是为了真正重要的人的话什么都能做
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.79,0:18:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是女孩子的认真
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.39,0:18:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,间接接吻 我也和辰吉去试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.60,0:18:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要喜欢上男孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.11,0:18:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.41,0:18:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.88,0:19:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.85,0:19:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不体谅岚子的心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.91,0:19:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这只猪 猪 猪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.60,0:19:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪学姐 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.13,0:19:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能理解岚子鼓起的勇气吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.37,0:19:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是最差劲的人渣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.44,0:19:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.11,0:19:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于见面了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.48,0:19:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这让人怀念的感觉 你是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.70,0:19:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是你 你的另一面
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.21,0:19:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一个的 我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.50,0:20:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 伸出手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.13,0:20:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.35,0:20:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直都在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.92,0:20:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我想起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.72,0:20:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是 我是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.41,0:20:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M变态啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.43,0:20:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.45,0:20:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 美少女的飞踢 爽得不得了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.93,0:20:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快乐的波浪像漩涡一样把我卷进去 转啊转啊的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.62,0:20:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像远行回来的这种怀念感
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.13,0:20:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对不会再去任何地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.00,0:20:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.72,0:20:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.44,0:21:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变回原样了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.34,0:21:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.64,0:21:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没什么了吗 接近也没关系了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.55,0:21:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 是平常的我啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.18,0:21:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 真的太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.60,0:21:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是结局还是白忙 回原点了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.68,0:21:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就算是这样也…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎就算一直都是超M 我觉得也很喜…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.71,0:21:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.68,0:21:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.80,0:21:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(465,350)}喜？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.71,0:21:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(200,350)}喜？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.00,0:21:36.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜感～
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.75,0:21:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 结野那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.03,0:21:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这超M蠢猪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.09,0:21:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 冷不防的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.74,0:21:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天开始重新治疗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.84,0:21:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彻彻底底治好你的超M体质 觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.12,0:21:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.39,0:23:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,华丽地烧出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.86,0:23:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德烈16岁特制特别曲奇
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.81,0:23:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快拿去给平民1号
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.03,0:23:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 为什么要给太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.61,0:23:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没那方面的兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.38,0:23:40.39,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.38,0:23:40.39,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.38,0:23:40.39,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.38,0:23:40.39,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,280)}MFC的华丽阴谋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.38,0:23:40.39,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,280)}MFC的华丽阴谋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.38,0:23:40.39,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,280)}MFC的华丽阴谋
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
